We're going to build a company in three days. We're going to start out with some intros. With me, we're going to do some intros here.
Hi, I'm Lauren. I work on Grok Bot at SpaceX AI.
Hey, I'm Roshan. I work on Grok Bot and a few other things at SpaceX AI. I'm mostly focused on product and super excited.
Yeah, and I'm Matt Palmer, working developer experience. And the idea behind this livestream, what we're going to be doing for the next couple days, is that we'll be working live from a studio in San Francisco, right next to the Moscone Center at Dreamforce.
And we're going to share every step of the process in building a business. We're going to talk about how we would do this using Grok Bot, using the latest AI tools from SpaceX AI.
And there are going to be some mistakes. It's not going to be perfect. We're going to walk you through everything in the process. We actually don't even know what idea we're going to build yet.
We should probably figure that out.
We're still working on it. We should figure it out. But we're going to get to it. And through the three days, we're going to be mostly here in this room. It might get a little messy. I don't know. It's probably going to get a little crazy.
But we're also going to cut over to SpaceX team members who are going to share, number one, what Grok Bot is, how it works, and how you can use it for your job, for your life, for everything really that you care about.
And you're going to see a lot of that today as we go about building our companies. And that first session is going to be Grok Bot 101. So if you know nothing about Grok Bot, we've worked with Roman and Rita. They're excellent.
They'll walk you through everything from how it got built to what it is today. And I feel like Grok Bot can be pretty intimidating if you've never used it before. It's a bit of a new concept.
I think it will be fun to see different folks and how they use it in different ways. I think we have a really cool lineup of people. We've got some engineers, we've got some product people, we've got some sales people.
And so regardless of what you work on, hopefully you get a feel for how Grok Bot can be part of your daily workflow. But yeah, the 101 session I think is going to be really cool.
I'm super curious to see everybody's work. I mostly use Grok Bot for personal automation and some engineering work as well, but never done it for GTM or market research or anything like that. So I'd be curious to see.
I feel like I always learn something too. I don't know about you guys, but every time I see someone else use it, it's like, oh wait, I didn't know how to do that. I didn't think of this particular thing. Maybe we'll come up with some of those ourselves too.
That's why I hang around Lauren. I'm like, Lauren, teach me how to use Grok Bot. And then I'll try to communicate that with you all. So yeah, no, it'll be super exciting.
But before we dig in, I have my piece of paper here with what I'm supposed to say. There's a super important, ultra important announcement I'm supposed to tell everybody. You have a chance to win something. So you want to listen to this one.
You're going to have to watch along, follow along in the live stream because our Grok Bot Galaxy live stream challenge is now live. So we're going to break for you guys. I know this is exciting. I hear woos from the studio.
So what we're doing is we're giving away a trip to a star ship launch. So you're going to get to go to star base in Austin, Texas for yourself and a guest.
I want to go. Yeah, I can't think of anything. My girlfriend would be more excited than for me to take her to a star ship launch. So actually the and the runners up. So even if you don't win the runners up, get a tour of the SpaceX rocket factory in Hawthorne in the Bay Area.
So you're going to have to follow the at Grok accounts and the at bot accounts and the entry will be by September 29th. All the details of the contest are in there. But what we want you to do is share how you integrated Grok Bot into your work.
So you're going to quote the official post on X with a description of your bot and a share template link. All of those details are going to be from the act rock and the at bot accounts. So you just go over there, check it out. And again, you need a trip to go to star.
Really? I would love to go. I were like, we haven't even gotten this. I haven't gotten it. Maybe next week and work on that. Yeah, there's also some really cool footage of a launch on the Grok post that I see on X right now. So yeah, check it out. X.com slash Grok. And you can see some more info there on I guess how to enter and some some some details. Awesome. Awesome. Okay, cool. So, you know, we got some time. The main things we wanted to cover were just kind of like the layout how this is all going to work.
The contest and now we can just like start talking a little bit about what we're planning to do. And I also want to give you guys a little bit of more background on who we are, like what we do day to day is like, you know, that can get can be ambiguous and it's never really clearly laid out. So our goal is to show you all basically how AI can like help you get more stuff done. And more importantly, like how AI can free up your time so that you're not bogged down by all like the media tasks and the boring stuff that we all have to do every day that we've done for our
entire lives, most of us, right, whether that's like digging through Excel sheets, you're trying to figure out where that one message went that you think somebody sent you last night, but you can't quite remember. Or, you know, actually writing code and automating some of the more manual parts of software, but not just software knowledge work, making slides, making designs. And the key message, I think really is that AI frees you up to do the stuff you actually care about. And so maybe we could just go around to all like tell you a little bit more
about myself, I'll give you like kind of a little intro and what I do and I would love to for the rest of the team to share because I mean, presumably for watching this, you're gonna be spending some time with us over the next
two hours.
Really nothing to a fully functioning company. And shortly will also like lay out exactly what we mean when we say like company, right? Because there's actually a lot of confusion on this online. It's like, oh, they're building a business. I saw some quote trees like they're building a startup. They're building a multi billion dollar
company. We could maybe do all of that though. I don't know.
I mean, someone told us we should build SpaceX and I was like, so many hours. We already work for space. I feel like they got the rockets down. We can do something different. But yeah, we'll get right into it. And then again, my name is Matt Palmer. I work in developer experience. Some I know developer relations have some amazing teammates.
The Rob Eric, Milos, just great team. And largely that looks like he's our education, like teaching people how to use rock back how to use these new technologies, how to use these tools that like really nobody's ever used before. Some brand new things. And so like day to day, I'm making a lot of content, but I'm also doing a little bit of engineering work might be contributing code here or there updating our documentation.
Helping set up live streams.
Even maybe. And so it's really a combination of like content, a combination of products and talking to a lot of people just being on Twitter and understanding like how the product works, how people are using the product, all of these things.
And so I'm super excited to like bring that into what we're building today. I'll probably be thinking like I level about a lot of stuff.
We'll talk about like individual roles as we move through this. But yeah, it's a bit about me. So maybe you can dig more into like what you're doing day to day.
I'm actually curious before we do that. What's your favorite demo you've built recently? Because you make some really awesome demos.
Okay, cool. Yeah. So I shared this one yesterday, actually, since it's on my profile. Hopefully we have our Twitter handles.
Yeah, we should bring this but some more.
Maddie P. That's all you got enough. But I think this one was pretty cool. I set up Brock bot basically to do the process of like trying out new technologies.
So it goes on my X bookmarks, finds like a cool package or a cool technology.
So I'll like bookmark. Oh, like, here's a cool MPM package that can like make maps or make like a rotating globe.
And then it's like, okay, I have to find the time to sit down, spin up that repo, like, actually have this thing running to like understand really what it is or read the documentation or whatever.
And so this crock bot looks at my expert bookmarks and finds things like that. It will fire up a cursor cloud agent to start building with that technology.
And then I configured the repo using rock, but actually to do preview deploys, I think using cloud flare or something.
And so every morning I just get a message from the crock bot and says, hey, here's this technology that was in your bookmarks that you thought was cool.
And here's like a deployed version of it. That's super cool. Yeah, I have a walkthrough on my on my Twitter page of like how to do that.
So yeah, that was maybe my favorite. I like that a lot. I'm glad I asked. I feel like this is like I always learn something.
Anytime I talk to someone. I do a crock bot. You've like built crock bot.
OK, well, I guess I'll go next. I'm Roshan. I work on product at SpaceX AI.
And I think the product role has really changed in the last few months and maybe year plus, where I don't know,
depending on sort of which philosophy you subscribe to, everyone is sort of a builder now.
But I don't know. I think a lot of what I spend my time thinking about is how to build the right things for customers and how to kind of bring that customer feedback and like what people want out of their use of AI tools kind of into the product.
And so, you know, in day to day thinking about things in crock bot, we've built a ton of really great connectors into the crock bot marketplace.
And so trying to get more and more of those connectors in place.
But then also just thinking about how we think about what to build next, like what the next frontier ought to be.
And I'm actually kind of excited to get into some of this today because it's not often that you get to like start from scratch on a new business or a new entity.
Like oftentimes you're working on an existing platform and it's like, what do we do next?
But I think what's going to be really cool here is we're going to get to do a lot of the zero to one stuff together. Right.
So, you know, how do we go find data for what we should build or like what does what's the world saying about ideas and how do we go do some user research and maybe go like set up some interviews and kind of like run the whole product development process and the whole product development playbook.
So, yeah, I'm pretty excited for that.
I think it'll be pretty fun to get into get into the zero to one parts of it.
And then, of course, you know, a lot of fun decisions to make with the various, you know, hopefully we'll make them bots.
But we have a designer bot that can help us design some cool stuff.
We'll have a marketing bot that can help us market some cool stuff.
So, yeah, I'm excited to figure out how we coordinate all that.
I think that'll be a lot of fun.
Yeah. Lauren, you want to go next?
Yes, I am Lauren.
I am potato on Twitter.
And I use GrokBot for a lot of like really crazy things, I think, like really random things.
So a couple of weeks back, I tweeted out this kind of a joke where I said, like, if you want to summon me on X, just say potato, potato, potato.
And then, like, I will disappear and say something.
Of course, I have I have to automate that because there's no way I can respond to so many mentions.
So I used GrokBot for that.
Also do a lot of engineering work on GrokBot.
So I think coming on the livestream and talking to you all and working together, it's going to be really fun because usually I feel like I'm stuck in my cave, my goblin cave at home, you know, just coding.
I work on GrokBot.
So I'm really obsessed about performance.
And so I'm just constantly just working on making the app faster and faster and faster.
So I really love doing that.
We're all thankful for this.
Yeah. And another thing I really like or I spent a lot of time on is setting up the GrokBot code base so that anyone, right, like whether you're a PM or designer to contribute to the code and have it be good by default.
So I'm looking forward to like setting something up like that here too so that all three of us can be building and iterating really quickly together on.
I don't even know what we're going to build.
Yeah. Yeah. I think it'll be a lot of fun.
Yeah. Oh, I'm excited for that.
Because I love the GrokBot DevEx just like coming in from the outside.
It's super easy to understand the way you laid things out there.
We have like, you know, channels where if there's an issue, we just post what the issue is and like some cloud agent somewhere.
Yeah. And also usually you like it's kind of shocking how fast you like appear when issues arise.
Of course.
Starts working. Right. And I love that.
And so I mean, today, like when we're building, we're going to use all the same tools you would use to start a company.
Like if you just sat down with three friends, you'd probably like, I don't know, set up somewhere to talk, set up somewhere to like take notes.
And then start building using using your favorite tools.
And so the cool thing about working at SpaceX is like, OK, well, cool.
We have cursor. We have GrokBot.
We're going to use cursor, write some code, but then we're going to use GrokBot and we're going to like figure out all the hard manual parts, which is kind of like, OK, well, like, I don't know.
We probably want to sell something.
So we need to figure out what the idea is.
Well, yesterday we asked you all and also SpaceX employees like, hey, what should we build?
Like, do we have any good ideas?
And so we have thousands of responses.
The first step is probably like ask GrokBot to look at those responses, right?
It's to do market research.
So we're going to do some do some market research here to kick it off.
And then we're probably just going to like, I don't know, figure out what we want to build.
Maybe announce that. I guess probably this morning is good.
Yeah. We'll have to try three days.
It feels like we should have an idea in day one that feels that feels good.
OK, cool. Yeah. So the goal is to have an idea in day one.
Maybe it's a good time to talk about exactly what we mean when we say we're going to build a business.
Yeah. Yeah.
So it's like, what is a business?
I was going to ask you what is a business?
I guess when you all say, when you all think like, OK, we're building a business, what
does that mean to you?
Yeah, I don't know.
For me, it's like I think you want to make something useful.
I don't know.
I kind of go back to the build something people want mentality, right?
I think we need to build something useful, something people want, maybe something we use
ourselves.
Yeah.
You know, that's often a good way to I think we'll have a lot of empathy for what
we're doing if it's something that we'd want to build and use ourselves to.
What do you guys think?
I like the dog food part because for me, one of the things I really love about working on
Grokbot is that I use it to work on itself.
So it's just really nice loop of being able to dog food your own product and make it
better. You know, be the ultimate power user of your own thing.
So I feel like we definitely want to have something like that for our business idea.
But yeah, when it comes to business, I guess, I don't know, I think
it definitely involves maybe making a little bit of money.
Oh, we should make the team wants to make money.
It's not a real business until we got to have that, you know, she see the dollar
flowing into the bank account.
OK, that's going to be great.
So business dollars to bank accounts, building dog food, testing out the product,
building something people want.
Yeah, if I was going to add anything, I would just say that I think it's easy
to forget, especially in like we're all terminally online.
Like you're watching the stream, you're part of like X, which is where people go.
They want to know stuff. Right.
Like that's where X is where people go.
But that also means a lot of people are online a lot on X.
I am the biggest. I'm the most guilty of this.
I'm on Twitter. X way too much.
But like what it means to build a business is ultimately to serve humans.
Right. And there are, you know, even agents, well, serve humans or agents
potentially. But the person asking the agent to do something is human.
Right. And so at the end of the day, it does kind of tie back to like a human
experience of like if I buy a T-shirt online and that gets delivered to me,
that might be a business idea. Right.
But it's about the process of you created this thing for a human being.
Or if you make Grokbot, we are creating Grokbot for human beings to interact
with a computer. Right.
And so it is very a very human process.
And it's something that at the end of the day is like how do we create
something that you want as the viewer, something that you find like magical
or add some sort of value to your life?
And so I think my favorite part is just like it really becomes about people.
And how do you make a person happy?
Have you enough to like give you money?
It's like, can you do this again? You know, or their agent.
Yeah, I keep coming to this idea like, you know, in Grokbot, you can give your
bot a credit card now, like a link, a striped card, I guess, link card.
So I think it'll be fun to kind of play around with some cool ideas.
Yeah. Yeah.
What could we make that maybe a human could come in and buy something or maybe
a bot could also come in and buy something?
And maybe do the same thing. Maybe they're different.
Yeah. Yeah. That could be interesting.
Yeah. That could be kind of fun, too.
Maybe for all the people watching, they'd want to like create a Grokbot account
if they don't already have one and like get their bots to buy something.
That could be kind of interesting. Yeah. Yeah. I mean, check it out.
We're not going to like we're just going to build the thing to this
this week or these three days.
But you're more than welcome to follow along.
Yeah. So I think the process of like human connection is something we'll explore.
The process of like physicality, like I don't know.
Do we build a digital product?
Do we build like a place where you can go buy like coffee beans
and have them delivered to you?
Do you like or do we create something in person?
Like we're in San Francisco, like Dreamforce is going on right now.
There are like 50,000 people in the city here all excited.
That's wild. Never seen so many people in that life.
50,000 additional people in this block.
Like the streets closed. It was hard to get here.
The whole nine. Yeah.
And so to me, it would be really cool if we could like take something digital
and then use that to manifest something in the real world
that even you all can interact with.
And so like I think if I'm taking that away, like that would 100 percent be my goal
for this week. But we don't know.
Like, is that possible? We'll be able to do it.
I'm just talking and I feel like we're wasting time.
So yeah, I don't know.
I'm excited to see where it goes.
And like we're going to keep it super casual.
We're going to see us at our at our highs and at our lows.
It's going to be absolutely hopefully, hopefully entertaining.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I don't know. I think the part of the fun is going to be, you know,
we have three days, which is a lot of time, but also not much time.
But I think we'll need to, you know,
there'll be a bunch of stuff we have to set up.
Like I'm just starting to think ahead to we probably need a slack channel
for our team to chat in and maybe our bots to chat into.
We need like a notion.
So yeah, we might slack notion.
I mean, what do we use that word?
So I know some tool notion awesome tool, maybe linear for tickets.
Yeah, we can check out linear. Yeah.
Or something like that. Like you like to use linear.
Or how do you how do you like prioritize like work?
I think we can try it, but I'm also wondering if we can just
because like if we have slack, like I could just like maybe
as we use our own app and you report bugs, I guess auto fix them.
Oh, yeah. Why open an issue when you can open a PR?
But I mean, yeah, maybe we'll get a backlog at some point that we want to keep track of.
OK, so maybe slack is a control plane.
You know, like I wonder if we start to start with slack first.
Yeah. And then see what we need issues issues.
Issues. Issues channel.
OK, so I can start wiring up my my factory.
OK, so we should like we're going to wire up the factory to the issues channel.
Yeah. And then while we're doing that, like no matter what, I'm going to
we're going to start walking through the factory because you're the infamous
creator of P-stack. Right.
And it's I don't know.
Infamous, famous.
I don't know. And for viewers might not know what P-stack is.
What is P-stack?
So P-stack is it's a million dollar.
No, it's not. It's not.
It costs nothing. It's an open source plugin that I mean that
takes all of the skills that I've built for doing rigorous engineering work
that I do all the time and I open sourced it so that anyone can reuse
the same skills and workflows that I have.
And I've been iterating on it for quite a while.
It took me quite a long time to get to get it to that point.
But last month I actually shipped two two and a half thousand P-R's of P-stack
into production.
And I don't think I caused any bugs.
I hope I hope I didn't.
So, yeah, if you haven't tried out P-stack yet,
you can go to the Groff bug marketplace and search for P-stack
and try it out and let me know what you think.
I just did the math.
Twenty five hundred P-R's in a month is eighty three P-R's a day.
Yes. And we have three days.
So times three is two hundred fifty P-R's.
I think you can do more than that.
OK, you have a P-R meter on the screen.
Actually, I'm not even going to open P-R's.
I'm going to merge to me.
Oh, yeah. There we go.
Yeah, it's not like we'll call it a commit meter.
We'll have a commit meter somewhere.
Where we're going, we don't need to pull over.
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh, my God. Yeah.
I'm like, it's like the entire team is like, oh, boy.
No. And I mean, I feel like sometimes you say like two thousand P-R's
and people are like, oh, like, that's just something they say on stream.
But like I physically have like I've sat over your shoulder
and see you do some of this stuff.
And it's like, Grokbot, the app is built by people at SpaceX
that are using tools like this to rapidly iterate.
And so hopefully, like we'll be able to show you that process
and we'll be able to show you that product
as it goes from like quite literally nothing or ideating right now
to something that we're shipping to you all.
So, yeah. Yeah.
I mean, we're talking about tools before, right?
So it sounds like we're going to go Slack notion kind of stack.
We got maybe linear if we decide we can just start shipping shipping directly to Maine.
I mean, we're going to be here talking to each other.
Yeah. What else do you really need?
I mean, anything else?
I mean, we have some database tech, maybe.
Yeah, we'll need some like infra that we can set up.
We're in the system. So many of the database.
I know I know a database CEO lives around here.
They will have on at some point.
Yeah, I can convince them some of our friends to join.
Yeah. We know we're big with the Stripe team with link.
Yeah. So we need some payments and from totally.
We'll probably start whiteboarding this at some point, like start building
and showing people like exactly where to do.
Oh, yeah. Maybe we could actually get an actual whiteboard.
Yeah, we might get a chalkboard, a whiteboard in here.
We got a typical team is listening to this now freaking out because
I so character items in the building.
He's kind of such a hard on stream.
This is the great part is like now that I'm on stream,
like I can just ask for anything, presumably it'll disappear.
Like if I was like, there's a coffee shop down the road for the business.
I didn't get a chance to get a cappuccino this morning.
I'm wondering if like in the next shot, they'll just be like cappuccino.
We can really push how far that you know.
One thing I forgot that we're going to need a lot of his tokens.
We need a lot of tokens.
I think we I think we have.
I think we have to.
Not talking about cappuccino.
Yeah, we need tokens.
This is actually central to the idea.
Maybe you could tell us a little bit about like what the setup we're running is.
Yeah. So, you know, we're going to be using a combination of well,
Grokbot, we're going to really try to drive everything with Grokbot.
I think it's a plan.
But we've set up ourselves on a Grokbot team.
So we created a new team just for this, you know, these three days where we're going
to, you know, just use that.
We're going to each have our own teams of bots that we set up and hopefully be able
to show you, you know, those bots as we go and be able to switch between them a
little bit and kind of let you interact with them a little bit.
And then, yeah, we really I think we're going to treat this like a separate
business and entity, right?
So I have a GitHub org that I made that's a completely blank org.
Nothing in it.
No repos.
So we can use that if we like as our starting point.
What's the what's the name of the GitHub org?
It's called Ship by Thursday.
Ship by Thursday.
Yeah.
Maybe we should open source some stuff too.
If you want to follow along, it's just github.com slash ship by Thursday.
It's completely empty right now.
So if you go there, you will see nothing, but we could, we'll need to put
some stuff there, maybe we'll like open source some Easter eggs.
I don't know.
Do you see?
Yeah, we should know.
I don't remember the org.
Actually, we literally haven't said it.
It's still like, we didn't do any work beforehand.
So like none of this exists.
Yeah.
But we will start to make things available as as possible.
And yeah, our goal is to make this as lot like as real as possible.
Yeah.
So we're starting with a completely blank slate, right?
So we have a github org, we have rockbot accounts with zero bots in them right now.
Brand new accounts.
And so we'll walk you through from scratch, you know, like how we'd install
Pstack to get set up for development.
Maybe, you know, in a few minutes we can kind of do some market research like Matt
was talking about, you know, I have some user research bots and we actually have a
whole template of bots in our marketplace too.
So maybe we can find some useful ones there and kind of pull them in.
I mean, we need to also like hire like a founding engineer, probably founding
engineer bot, we just like hire the bot.
We definitely need to hire a bot or two.
Two bots, intern bot.
I'm actually also wondering as part of market research, do we want to have our
bots actually like kind of like the idea you had where you have your
groth bot build something for you every day?
Like maybe we could have some quick throwaway prototypes or something.
So we can visualize people's ideas, something like that.
Oh, that's a really cool idea.
Yeah.
I feel like you have like some bot factory stuff as well, right?
Like, okay, the idea I'm talking about.
And, you know, this might be, if you're watching this, you're like, Matt,
I don't even know what GrokBot is.
Well, that's great.
Cause we've got a GrokBot 101 session.
You're coming up right for you in like five minutes, but stick with me here.
You can create GrokBots, other GrokBots can create GrokBots.
It's pretty crazy.
So what I'm thinking is like, okay, at a meta point, right?
What do you, what do you do when you have a business, right?
You have like onboarding.
So maybe we come up with like a company doc and that doc explains our process.
And we can also do that in GrokBot.
We could have like a GrokBot that sort of is like a GrokBot factory of some
sort that creates our employees.
And so that, that like onboarding bot might be like, Hey, okay, you want to read
this doc and that's who we are.
And that's like what our principles are.
And that's like what we're trying to do.
Like a little company handbook.
Like the state of the company.
Yeah.
And then we have to have a bot that updates the state or all the bots
update the state of the company.
Right.
Uh, yeah, we could do something with that.
Shared knowledge base.
Right.
Like most companies have that.
Some of that.
And so what I'm thinking is like, as we add employees, as we start to like build
out the team, like, okay, new, new, right?
Like we hire our intern bot, take a look at what we're doing in, in notion.
And then like, we'll start like prototyping, but I like what you're
sitting, I like where your head's at.
I think when we resume back from the break, we can start thinking about like,
um, prototyping market research.
Uh, but we need to start like hiring bots.
So maybe in that 45 minutes, we'll like come up with a hiring plan.
Right.
I like that.
We're gonna, we're gonna, we're gonna need a bunch of bots.
Okay.
Sure.
And, uh, we're going to bring you all along for it.
We're not sharing our screens right now, but like we have everything hooked up.
So you'll be able to see exactly what we do.
You'll able to be able to see like how we use the products in a clean demo
environment, the one thing we did do before we got together is like, we
actually like downloaded GrokBot.
If you're showing a company, I guess, you know, that's the first thing.
It's the only thing you have to do really.
Um, yeah, and I'm excited.
So, uh, a little bit about the session that's coming up and
like some housekeeping stuff to recap.
If you're new to the new, the stream, we're going to build a company.
We got 72 hours.
We haven't done anything.
I mean, we just spent the last 20 minutes.
Yeah.
We shouldn't be waiting.
We haven't done anything.
Um, if you're watching, there is currently the GrokBot galaxy
live stream challenge going on.
If you share a template, um, with us all in your template is like the most.
It's like if a lot of people like your template, basically, you have a
chance to win a trip to star base.
Like watch a Starship launch, which is pretty sick.
Um, runners up, get a trip to Hawthorne where they actually like build some
of this cool stuff, which is also great.
Um, and yeah, you know, when we think about business, we think about
something that, that people want that creates value for people.
That's where we're going to try to build with a human touch with a human touch.
Yeah.
Most importantly, that's something we're going to try to build this week.
We're going to bring in different guests.
We're going to bring on guests of companies that we like guests of people
on the internet that we like.
We're going to bring in.
SpaceX employees that are really great.
They're all really great.
I don't pick favorites, but we're going to bring in some especially great
employees who are going to show us their workflows.
We're just going to be hanging out.
They're going to help us with our, our crafting codes.
We're going to seek the knowledge of the crowd.
The crowd.
No, no men as an Island, like no entrepreneur ever did anything by themselves.
They had people to help them out.
So we're going to call on our friends to help us out and give us advice.
But like, it's going to be us with the laptops here.
And there might be a few moments where we're just like
furiously typing inside some stream too.
I feel like we're going to need some lockdown.
There will be some, yeah.
Hey, look, I mean, if you've watched any of the great streamers, shout out
prime shout out the prime big friends of ours, they've helped us out with
some of this stuff, it's going to be like that.
We're just going to be hanging out.
This might get a little bit messy.
The production crew is going to yell at me.
Uh, make me like, got around clean, clean the table up or something.
Um, but we're going to, we're going to have fun along the way.
Um, anything else you guys want to add for the viewers?
No.
Uh, it's going to, it's going to be really a lot of fun.
So I'm looking forward to building this with y'all.
Awesome.
And I like, yeah, definitely keep, keep shouting at us on, on X.
If you're kind of wanting to send us feedback and there's like an active chat
happening in the stream too.
So like, please drop stuff in chat.
We're going to get it set up so we can kind of see some of those comments rolling
in and kind of interact with some of those suggestions in real time too.
So it'll be really helpful to us as we're kind of steering and like, we
really want to get folks feedback and make sure this is useful to you.
So we're just definitely encourage you to keep the feedback coming.
Three of us are all on X.
I think our handles are all over the place, hopefully by now.
Um, so please like, you know, post at us, uh, or reply to us.
And we'd be happy to kind of bring some of that in as well.
But yeah, I see we have about 80,000 ish views right now.
And so, um, yeah, a lot of people out there who are really excited and we're
really excited to hear from you and, uh, help, you know, ask for your help
in crafting what we do here.
So, yeah.
And, and, uh, one thing, definitely recommend installing Grokbot.
If you haven't already signing up, we have a free trial.
So you can, you can try it out and maybe follow along with us, right?
As we build and show you some of our pro tips.
We're going to tell you exactly how we do it.
So if you just download Grokbot, we're going to give you the plug-ins,
the templates, all that stuff.
And most importantly stream we're going continuously live from 830 to like six,
six 30, you'll have to check the schedule.
Tune in here anytime we're going to cut to workshops.
So if you download Grokbot, if you like install the product, you're going
to like be able to follow along with exactly how it works.
If you were like, Oh man, I want to learn Grokbot, but I have to
like pay for this course.
So no, no courses, no payment all free.
Just, just watch this stream.
Is the course someone told us we got, I got a 25 seconds before
we go live, but someone told us their boss said, you are, you have to watch
this live stream all 30 hours.
I'm sorry.
You're probably watching right now.
I'm sorry about that, but you're going to learn a lot.
So we're going to go to Grokbot 101 with Roman and Amrita, two amazing,
intelligent, beautiful, smart, high achieving function of people that
actually build Grokbot.
So we're going to kick it over there and they're going to teach
you a little bit about Grokbot.
Are we good?
Well, you know, that was, uh, okay.
We got the, we got the nerves.
Check it out, dude.
So first I wanted to talk a little bit about how Grok Bot came to be.
And I think we're in a pretty interesting moment right now where when you think about the way
that AI has changed and really transformed the way that people and companies do work,
I think we've been through a few different phases.
And I think it started with really chat, where you ask a question to AI, AI responds, and
that was really useful.
I think that helped with a bunch of research workflows, for example.
I think the next step after that was you delegate a task to AI.
And there's a co-pilot that kind of sits next to you while you do your work.
You iterate on a slide deck together, those types of workflows.
But I think we're really on the cusp of this new moment in AI,
where AI starts to act more like a teammate or more like a colleague inside of a company.
And that's really different, I think, from what's come before.
And I think it's going to change the types of products that really meet the moment,
I think the ways that we need to change our ways and how we do work day to day to really
maximally get the most out of what AI can do inside of a company.
And then I think what will come after that is kind of this weird world of AI teammates
and human teammates that collaborate together inside of companies.
And where you're not just delegating a discrete task and saying, hey, go from point
A to point B, you're actually doing a lot more kind of what you would do with an actual
human colleague if they're not a collection of tasks that you kind of outsource,
but they own outcomes and they have responsibilities.
And you trust them to kind of own a discrete part of a company and kind of do that work for you.
And I think this is really where Grokbot originated from.
And I want to talk a little bit about some of the product decisions that we made to get there.
So if you haven't used Grokbot, this is what it looks like.
And I think there are a few things that we chose to do with Grokbot that are a bit different
from other AI tools on the market that you maybe have used before or are familiar with.
I think the first one is we really wanted Grokbot to feel a lot like you're working
with teammates and colleagues.
And so as a result, it feels kind of simple and chat-like and almost like you're messaging
your coworkers or teams of colleagues.
So you have on the left all of these bots, in this case, Sales Outbound and an inbox manager,
that each have specific roles and different kind of lanes of work.
And the idea is not that you create a chat for each task that you want to take on.
You actually create a bot for a unit of work and a kind of job responsibility,
and you come back to that bot over and over and over again and it learns from you.
And I think that's one of the most magical moments of working with Grokbot is you say
something a few weeks ago about, you know, I really like when my slides are formatted
in this particular way.
And then Grokbot remembers.
It remembers weeks later when you're making your next slide deck.
And that's what you would expect from a colleague, and I think that's what you should expect
from AI as well.
So there's this teammate paradigm instead of a task paradigm.
Teammates really sit at the center of Grokbot and the way to work with AI.
The second thing that's a little bit different is Grokbot, similar to what you would expect
from a colleague, doesn't just have access to direct integrations and MCPs and APIs.
Those are very useful, but they oftentimes don't get you 100% of the way to completing
the work that you want.
They have access to their own computer, and they can use that computer exactly how you
would.
They can watch a video.
They can listen to a podcast.
They can click in some, you know, antiquated government software from the 90s.
They can do everything that a human can do with a computer, but it's yours.
And in addition to all of the integrations and MCPs and things that you come to know
and love with AI, I think it really opens up a new set of tasks and opportunities for
what AI can take off of your plate.
And I think it feels really different when you work with AI that can do those things
versus can't.
And the difference between getting kind of 90% of the way there of like almost having
the job be done versus the thing just being done end-to-end, kind of hands off.
You trust that your bot can do it.
Feels very different.
Feels really magical.
And then the last thing is everything runs in the cloud.
It doesn't run on your computer.
And I think there's kind of in this weird moment in AI right now where a lot of the
workflows that people rely so much on AI for, it runs on their local laptop, which
is kind of strange.
And so if you're like asleep and your computer's closed, you know, the automation that you
set up to run at 2 AM doesn't fire and you wake up in the morning and you're confused
and you want to kick something off from your phone but it's tethered to your laptop back
in your office, it's just all this weirdness.
And we wanted to just jump right past that to a future where you have these very smart
colleagues, these teammates, these bots that live in the cloud and you can interact
with them anywhere you work.
It might be on your phone, it might be on your laptop.
In the future, it might be something entirely different.
And that really informed all of the decisions we made for the product, was those three things.
Feels like interacting with teammates, everything runs in the cloud, and your bots have access
to a computer that they can drive and manipulate just like you can.
And I think part of the reason we really felt the desire and the excitement to build
something like RockBot is from what we've seen in coding.
And I think from the past two years, we've seen the job of a developer completely transform.
And I think a very stark, it's hard to overestimate how big the change has been.
From an era of you're writing individual lines of code by hand to I think what a lot of development
looks like now, certainly inside of SpaceX AI, where you have developers that own outcomes,
they own direction, and they steer their team of agents to complete these discrete tasks
and do kind of a lot of the mundane work for them.
And we haven't seen that for knowledge work at all.
I think when you look at the way that knowledge work is done today versus the way it's done
in 2024 or 2025, it's not that different.
And I think our hope and goal for RockBot is to really be the most useful way to harness
these models inside of a company to do real work.
And so I touched on some of these points, but Amrita will talk a little bit more about
specific ways that we're seeing RockBot be useful for us internally, but also inside
of real companies in the wild.
But we wanted it to be delightfully simple, and we think the future of AI products really
should be very simple to use, very simple to get started on, and then gradually pull
you into the more complex capabilities.
And I think a lot of people's experience using RockBot is immediate on its face.
You kind of give it an initial task that is a little straightforward and simple.
RockBot does it.
You give it something more ambitious.
You give it something even more ambitious, and you just kind of keep going through that
process until you feel the limits of maybe where current AI capabilities are.
And our bet is these models are going to keep getting smarter.
We want to give them a safe environment to run in to really maximally be useful to employees
of companies.
So it's very simple.
It's always on.
It's this teammate in the cloud that you can always depend on and rely on and never
goes down even when you're asleep or when your computer is closed.
And it really finishes the work.
You give it outcomes.
It delivers.
And I think the next step of this will be how this works inside of Teams.
I think right now AI is largely a single-player game.
You work with your personal AI assistant on various things.
I think we're really excited about what shared AI colleagues could look like and what the
future of internal tooling even becomes.
So with that, very excited to pass it off to Amrita to talk a bit more about concrete
ways that people are using RockBot and ways that we're using RockBot.
Amazing.
Thank you, Roman.
So you'll see on the agenda and also for the rest of the week, we have a lot of sessions
about how to use RockBot at the enterprise level.
So you'll see RockBot for GTM, for engineering, for marketing, and then for admins.
Today's session is going to take one of these, actually, and then do a live demo
with you all so you can see exactly what Roman mentioned, which is agents acting as
colleagues, agents using their own computer, and then also having memory and an ability
to learn from what you've taught them.
One thing I do want to highlight is if you haven't registered for any of the sessions
already, please go on to, I think, x.ai slash Galaxy and check out what's available
this week.
We have a lot of really great sessions basically about how to use RockBot for all
of these different use cases within an enterprise.
Okay.
So now we're going to go to the live demo session of today.
And I do want to ask, who in the room has used RockBot?
Okay.
Looks like a good amount.
So maybe some of you will be seeing it for the first time.
But these are the three bots that we're going to work with today.
We have Data Dan, Slide Sonya, and Email Ethan.
And they're going to work together on a project that will actually require you guys
to participate.
Don't worry.
No one's going to have to speak or anything.
But what it's going to do basically is collect user data, use that data to create
slides and charts, and then actually email that data to a stakeholder, an external
stakeholder.
So what you'll see actually is how all of these agents will work together.
And to Roman's point, use tools that might not have, you know, native MCPs or
APIs, but make it very easy for you to kind of outsource this work so that you
can focus on more pressing things at hand.
All right.
So I'm going to minimize this.
And we're going to open up RockBot.
And you'll notice that it looks very similar to maybe iMessage or a tool that
you're familiar with.
I have two bots that are already ready on the side.
I'll email Ethan and slide Sonia.
And I'll talk a little bit about them later.
But what I want to do with you all today is I want to create a bot from scratch
so you all can kind of see that workflow.
And this is the bot we're going to create is DataDan.
So I'm going to call DataDan.
I'm just going to create him there.
And when you create a bot, actually what RockBot will do is it will give
some idea of maybe what you want to use the bot for just based on the name.
So if you create a bot called workflow builder, it will automatically
kind of have an idea of what it's meant to do.
You'll notice here that it gives some options of what do you mainly want me
for, which is great.
But I'm going to start by actually asking it to create a Google Form for me.
And the reason I choose Google Form is, first of all, I don't know if anyone
likes making Google Forms.
I certainly don't.
But it's the most common way to get a lot of data from your employees,
from your customers, from if you're doing user research.
You can do this similarly with Qualtrics or any other kind of form-based software.
You can ask RockBot to basically create it for you.
So what we're going to do is I'm just going to say, and I'm going to use
voice mode here actually, so we can kind of see what that looks like.
Create a Google Form for me that asks two questions.
The first is how many cups of coffee do you drink a day?
And the second is what are your favorite coffee shops in San Francisco?
And for the coffee shop options, maybe put ritual, fields,
sight glass, and blue bottle.
So it's going to transcribe that.
What's really cool about voice mode, and this is actually deployed internally
right now, is we actually have a back and forth voice mode where
GrokVoys can actually talk back to you.
That should be out, hopefully, sometime within the next week or so.
But this is kind of a good way to see that speech-to-text in motion here.
So you'll see that it kind of took everything I said.
I'm actually going to move to the side here so you all can see.
And then immediately, when you send a request like this,
GrokVoy is going to respond and immediately start working.
And when it works, for example, in something like a Google Form,
what it will do is it will actually start using its own computer.
So at the top right is where you see access to GrokVoy's computer
here at the top.
I can actually click into it and see what it's doing.
Give it a little moment to connect.
But once it's connected, you'll see that it has access
to its own Linux VM machine.
So it'll be able to log into Google Slides, Google Forms, Google Docs,
whatever you need.
And so what you can see, actually, if I minimize this,
is it's going to build both of those questions for me.
And I can monitor how it's building those in those forms.
So I mentioned Google Forms as a way to kind of interact
with tools that don't necessarily have MCPs or APIs.
But what I also want to show is the built-in MCPs
that we have already.
So you can see here that I have a bunch of MCPs or plugins
that I can connect to my GrokBot.
And depending on your task at hand,
you can always manage these here.
And so this is kind of a good way to see what existing
APIs and MCPs are there already.
Or you can ask GrokBot to set it up for you.
OK, so it looks like the bot wants to run a task for me.
This is a good example of how bots ask for approval.
I'm just going to allow this for now.
But I'll talk a little bit about bot approvals later
and how you can actually set particular rules saying, hey,
I only want a bot to send an email after it
asks me for permission.
Or I only want the bot to send a Slack message
to an external customer after I approve it.
And this kind of makes it a lot easier for enterprises
to control what the bot can or cannot do in a big setting
like this.
So this is going to work on the Google Form.
While it's working, let me show you the other two agents
that we'll be working with today.
So email Ethan and slide Sonya.
You'll notice that slide Sonya already
has the slides that I'm going to be editing up
on her computer, similar to what Data Dan will
be actually.
And what's nice about slide Sonya
is I'm able to basically edit the slides myself
or I can actually teach her how to do a particular task.
So you'll see here at the top, Teach a Task.
I can actually show slide Sonya, for example,
if I want to create a slide that takes all the data
from this Google Form and adds an animation to it
or makes it a particular color, I can actually
show her how to do that.
So if I hit Teach a Task here, I can actually say,
let's say I want to just teach her how to do an animation.
I can hit this.
I can go to Insert, and I can add animation here.
And notice that this is me controlling the bot's computer.
So this is not the bot doing this on its own.
This is me kind of controlling it.
And I can say, OK, this is how you would do a kind of,
let's do a fly-in animation right there.
Let's just play it to see how it works
and make sure it works OK.
Give it a second.
Cool.
It looks like it's monitoring the time that the animation takes.
Amazing.
So now that it's set up here and it knows exactly how to do it,
I can stop the task.
And immediately, now that I've stopped the task
and slide Sonya knows exactly what
to do with an animation, it's able to turn
that recording and that animation into a skill.
And so now, anytime I want to say, hey,
I want you to add that animation that I showed you
to a particular text or to a particular image on a slide,
you'll be able to do that from scratch.
I'm going to go ahead and look up my Data Dan
and see how they're doing with the Google Form.
You'll notice that what's nice about, oh, I'm
going to go ahead and allow this again.
What's nice about having these agents
is that I can always go back and forth between them
and also see how they operate within each other.
So as you can see, side Sonya is learning
from the skill I just taught her.
Data Dan is working on the Google Form.
I can actually see him creating the form live for me.
And then what's nice about this is once the form is created,
I'm actually going to ask Data Dan to turn it into a QR code
and have you all scan it and fill out those two questions.
So on average, how many coffee cups
do you drink a day and your favorite coffee shop
in San Francisco?
And then we'll take all of that data, give it to Sonya,
and then have email Ethan kind of consolidate all that analysis
and send it out to, let's see who the top coffee shop owner
is.
And this is kind of a good way to see
how you can take a very simple task that usually
takes a lot of time.
For example, an event planner at a company
who needs to handle dietary restrictions for a 10,000
person on site, or a user researcher that
wants to collect data from all of their different customers
who are using Grokbot or any other tool,
how you can basically do all of these tools within Grokbot
and then have it kind of orchestrate that work for me.
I'm going to go ahead and set this one more time.
While this is working, let me actually show you
the approval situation since we are seeing it here.
You'll notice that in the settings, when you actually
scroll down here, you will see a particular set of rules
that you can allow Grokbot to basically do with or without
your permission.
So what I'll actually show it is I'll say something like, hey,
I don't want you to reply emails for me
unless you explicitly ask for my permission first.
Or similarly, I want you to be able to create slides for me
automatically without asking for my permission.
And so that makes it a lot easier for you
to kind of granularly control what Grokbot can or cannot do,
especially when it's doing long running tasks that you
want to be a little bit aware of or kind of cognizant
of what it's doing.
Give this a little more time while it's working.
One thing that I do want to say about Grokbot
and how basically it's able to run
is that the computers that it's using on
are all isolated, meaning that one Grokbot cannot access
another Grokbot's computer.
So the fact that Grokbot is working on this Google form
here is not going to impact the fact
that SlideSonia is working on the slides over here.
And that makes it easy, actually, for one Grokbot
to talk to another and work on two different things
at the same time.
So a way that I use this is I often
edit the same set of slides that my Grokbot is editing.
And that makes it really easy because I can have SlideSonia
edit slide one or two of mine on my slides,
and I can edit the 10th or 11th slide.
And we're not actually conflicting or making changes.
We're both kind of collaborating on the same set of tasks.
And that's kind of, at the end of the day,
what Grokbot is.
It's a colleague that you can collaborate on.
What's nice about SlideSonia is in her description here,
you can see that I've given her very explicit instructions
on how to edit an existing slide deck.
I can tell her that you're supposed to be using
a particular font with particular colors.
I actually always ask her to take a screenshot of the slide
that she's created once she's done and send it back to me.
And this kind of makes it a lot easier for me
to go back and forth with SlideSonia
because she already has this predefined set of notions
that she needs to get done.
And so I like doing this, or I
like giving my bot very explicit instructions
because that makes it more consistent.
And then if you ever want to add skills or routines,
you can always add that to your bot as well.
So while Data Dana is working, I
can add a routine to Sonya that says,
every morning at 9 AM, I want you to summarize for me
any changes that were made to this slide deck
and let me know who made those changes.
So this is a slide deck that I've shared
with a ton of my colleagues that I want to know
if someone took out a slide, added a new part
to a different slide.
I can ask Sonya to actually keep all of that context
and then set up a routine for me
that will send that information to me every day at 9 AM.
And you can set up routines across multiple bots.
So you can have a routine that says,
hey, SlideSonia, email Ethan, can you guys work together
and actually email a summary of all the changes
that were made in this slide deck to my boss once a week.
And so he is aware of what's going on there.
And that makes it, again, a lot more collaborative
and a lot easier to work across these multiple agents.
Cool.
I'm gonna open up Data Dan again
and see how the form is going.
Looks like it's making some changes.
It's asking for a lot of approvals today, which is funny.
I think it's because maybe it knows I'm on camera.
But what it's gonna do is once it's done
kind of making this form and designing
what we should put inside of the questions,
what it's gonna do is it's actually going to take this form
and turn it into a QR code that I mentioned you all will scan.
And then what's nice about that is you no longer have
to send out links for forms.
I actually always just use QR codes
that are made by Grokbot for any form
of external facing links or URLs that I have to show.
And then it will take basically all of this information
and put it inside of a Google Sheet
that again, it can access on its own computer.
So in fact, what I can do is while it's working on this,
I can go ahead and just actually look and see
at the other forms or sheets that I have made
inside of Grokbot itself.
And so this is again, me using Grokbot's computer
to get access to the forms or the sheets
or responses that it's making.
And what's nice about this is sometimes
if I wanna take control over what it's doing
or if I feel like it's taking a long time
on a particular thing,
I can go ahead and just do it on my own.
And then again, teach it how to do it
in case it takes a long time
or in case it's not aware
of exactly what it should be doing.
So what it's gonna do is it's gonna go ahead
and make these changes a little bit more.
And then while it's working,
I'm actually gonna talk about emailEthan
and how we actually use email very,
very usefully at Grokbot or at cursor,
but with Grokbot's integrations
with Google Drive and Google Docs.
So emailEthan's job is basically to take all the data
that Slide Sonya and Data Dan took
and basically consolidate that
and send it out to external stakeholders.
So what I like to do actually is I tell emailEthan
to look at real existing emails that I've written before
and consolidate that information into a particular skill
or type of tone that it can use for further emails.
So for example, I could say something like,
draft an email to, I'll say Jason DeMore,
someone in my contacts,
about the data that I've gathered on coffee habits.
And since it's still working on that data,
it's not gonna get anything just yet,
but I'll show you all what drafting an email
actually looks like in Grokbot.
What it will do is it'll actually be able to pull in data
from either my own personal source
or from sheets that I have
and then set up a little modal inside of Grokbot
that actually asks the user,
hey, can I get your data from,
or hey, can I send user as I'm,
so this is actually where I would say something like,
when I want Grokbot to reply to emails for me,
I'm actually going to ask first and add that as a rule.
And then now what it's gonna do
is before it sends any email,
it's always gonna ask me first.
And that makes it so that I don't have to always,
monitor or worry about what it's gonna send
to any external phasing customers.
Cool.
Okay, so one thing that I wanna show
is the agents talking to each other.
And so what I'll do actually,
is I'll tell email Ethan, while it's working,
and this is also an example of bot steering,
of how it can talk to Slide Sonya
and get information from what she knows
and context from what she knows.
So there's many ways you can do this.
You can always ask your bot in its description
to delegate to other agents.
So for example, I think some people I've talked to
have a chief of staff agent.
In your description, you can say something like,
like, I always want you to delegate to your team.
And that way the chief of staff
actually doesn't do anything on its own.
It delegates to its subordinate agents
that have the right context.
But what I'll do here instead,
is I'll say something like,
you can see here at message data,
Dan, completely on its own.
I can say something like,
can you message Slide Guru or Slide Sonya
and ask her for any details about
the GrokBotGalaxy101 slide deck that she made.
I want to send an email to my coworker
about what we showed today.
So you'll notice that it was smart enough to know
to message data, Dan,
for the coffee related information.
But now I'm explicitly tagging or calling another agent
that it can work with in order to kind of get
the right context and information at the right time.
And that's what kind of makes these agents so powerful
is they're experts and they're personas in their own field.
And so you'll see in kind of the GrokBot for engineering
and GrokBot for sales demos,
is those agents are long-lived personas.
They have memory.
And so because of that,
they're not just scoped to one task or one project.
They can be used for multiple tasks and multiple projects.
I can have email Ethan work for the next year if I wanted.
And now he will have context about every email
that I've sent and he'll be able to learn from all of that.
Similarly, Slide Sonya, she doesn't know just how to make
this one type of slide.
I can teach her how to work in a different branding
or a different theme.
Her job is just to create slides generally.
And so I can always change the scope and the persona
of these agents in order to make them
as useful to me as possible.
The way I like to think about GrokBot generally is
you're basically creating your own company.
You're creating your own team of agents
and you have the choice and the decision
of how you wanna orchestrate that.
If you want your agents to be divided up by project,
you can do that.
If you want them to be divided up by what they're expert in,
you can do that as well.
And so it's kind of up to you
and how you wanna orchestrate them
and have them work with each other on particular tasks.
So as you can see,
I'll show you both how email Ethan mismatches Dan
and how he also matches Slide Sonya.
So you'll see here,
these are the messages between GrokBot.
You'll notice that email Ethan will always say,
Amrita asked me to do this thing.
Data Dan will say, I don't have this right yet.
I'm still working on the spreadsheet.
And email Ethan will say,
okay, I'll use my existing coffee cup sample data set
that I have, amazing.
And then if we go back actually to,
I wanna go back to email Ethan here,
go back to one of your message slides.
So now you'll see kind of same thing.
Amrita needs details on this.
Please come back with a concise briefing deck about this
and give me any more information
that I can use going forward.
And then you'll see that Slide Sonya
has that same message from email Ethan
and is able to kind of respond back
and see what's going on here.
So if I click on her again, you'll see that, okay,
he asked for this one-on-one briefing for a coworker.
I'm gonna scan the full deck
and then pass Ethan an outline when it's ready.
So this is agent to agent protocol,
agent to agent communication,
which makes it really easy
for these agents to work together.
But what I also like about it
is that I no longer have to monitor what's going on.
I can kind of be more of a manager and overseer
and make sure that everything is going well,
but I don't have to get into the nitty gritty details
of what these agents are doing
in order to kind of get the job done.
As Roman mentioned, the goal of Grokbot
is to have finished work,
whether that's slides being made,
emails being drafted, forms being created.
But at the end of the day,
I am just making sure that the orchestration is working
rather than kind of going in
and seeing exactly what's being done here.
Okay, all right.
So I'll say this coworker's for Jason, that's fine.
And then what I'll do is I'll check on my form one more time
and see how it's doing here.
As you can see, it's still messaging with email Ethan,
but now it's worked on creating this
how many cups of coffee do you drink a day
and what are your favorite cups in San Francisco?
So it's working on kind of adding those options here.
The speed of these kind of computers
really depends a lot of times on, again, the model
and how we're working on computer use
as a company and as a org.
You'll notice that computer use
is gonna become a very, very hot topic for Grokbot,
for cursor and SpaceX generally.
And you'll see computer use continue to be improved
over the next couple weeks.
You'll see actually what I really like
about these machines is because they're Linux VMs,
they're very lightweight and they're very easy to spin up.
And so what I actually do sometimes is
if I'm on an airplane and I have bad wifi,
I actually outsource all my agent work,
my computer use to my Grokbot
because the wifi on its own Linux VMs
is really, really great, it's very fast.
And so this is kind of how I do any outsourcing of work,
again, for things that don't have MCPs,
so Google Forms, Qualtrics,
and then once it starts adding options
like it's doing here, it makes it a lot easier
for me to kind of create these really long running tasks
without me having to manually go and do this.
I can again focus my work on something else.
Okay, all right.
So as you can see, the bot always asks for permission
on connecting to outside services.
So as you can see here,
it says the agent is trying to reply to an email
and this is blocked by my own personal auto review rule.
So it's respecting the rule that I put in already,
which says that, hey, I don't want you to apply
or I don't want to reply to emails for me.
I'm gonna go ahead and just say allow once
so that it's able to kind of send that content over.
And then what it will do is it'll actually show me
a draft of that email.
What's nice about these agents is,
let's say I wanna do this maybe twice.
Three times, four times.
You can always duplicate an agent and have maybe five or six email agents.
Sometimes I'll do this if I'm emailing different stakeholders.
I'll have one email agent that's designed for emailing execs or CTOs or CFOs.
I'll have another one that's designed for emailing just general users of Grok Bot or regular folks
who are using it every day to get feedback.
I'll have another email agent that's meant for messaging my team at work.
They all are tailored a little bit differently to be able to understand how different stakeholders
will respond to a particular type of email.
This is really great if you ever want to duplicate or try multiple different strategies in an agent.
One thing I also love to show is sharing.
What you can do with a bot is you can always share it as a template and then give it to
other people in your team.
This is what really uplifts the multiplayer aspect of Grok Bot.
You can have one agent that's shared across your whole team as a template and then people
can customize it for their own personal use case.
You might have seen that earlier when I hit Marketplace.
You can see here that these are featured bots.
These are actually just public.
Lauren is from Cursor.
This is her bot that she's published.
Claire Vo, Lenny, and Eric is also from Cursor.
These are all bots that they've published that I can eventually just use and incorporate
into my own Grok Bot ecosystem.
You'll notice that these are from my team itself.
If I ever want to publish my own Grok Bot to my team, to my company, I can do that as
well.
It makes it really easy, as I mentioned, to have bots that are similar so that there's
consistency.
For example, if you're on a design team at work and you have a brand design bot,
you want to make sure that the brand design bot is following the same colors, fonts, typography
as everyone else's.
You would publish one brand design bot, then everyone at your company can then use.
Publishing bots like this makes it really easy to have consistency.
It's also really easy to modify them, change them, and then people will get the most
updated version of your bot.
If you haven't shared a bot yet, please do.
It's really, really easy to do.
You just hit this, again, as I mentioned, share as template at the top, and then anyone
will be able to see your bot and use it for all its glory.
Here's an example of how an email draft looks inside of Grok Bot.
You'll notice that it has this really nice modal here, which basically allows you to
edit things, change things, do whatever you want.
I can even change who my recipient is, if it's not the right person that I wanted to
send it to.
I can also delete it or ask it to rephrase it if I don't like the writing.
This is a good way of doing any form of email drafting within Grok Bot, so that you don't
necessarily have to comb through all your drafts inside of your emails.
You can do all of that within Grok Bot itself.
We do a lot of, obviously, emailing, outbounding within Cursor, but the way that we do a
lot of that is through Grok Bot.
It's a really powerful tool, especially when, as I mentioned, it can talk to SlideGuru or
talk to other tools and get context from those agents to then incorporate inside of your
email itself.
I'm going to look at Datedan one more time, and it looks like my copy form is ready.
Amazing.
What I'm going to do is I'm going to say, this looks great.
Can you turn this into a QR code that people can scan?
What I'll do is, once the QR code is up, I'll have folks just scan it real quick.
We'll get the responses.
The last thing we'll do, we have about 10 minutes left, is we'll turn those responses
into some beautiful slides that we'll incorporate into our Grok Bot 101 deck.
Then we can all see what everyone's favorite coffee shop is, both in the room and remotely.
It's going to generate a QR code in just a second, and then we'll be good to go.
One thing that I do want to show before Datedan finishes is the sections in Grok Bot that you
can categorize things into.
You'll notice, actually, that I have two.
Unassigned is basically Grok Bots that don't really have a place.
This is actually, and Ling will actually show a lot of these Grok Bots in the engineering
session, this is actually where my engineering team of Grok Bots live.
I like having them in this particular area because it makes it really easy to separate
them from the agents that are in this session, and also categorize where things particularly
belong or respond.
You can create as many bots as you want, but you can also create group chats with your bots,
and then you can categorize those as well.
If I want to create a group chat, for example, with multiple bots, someone was asking me earlier,
how is this different from the messaging each other?
It's more so a visibility thing.
For example, if I want to put email Ethan, Datedan, Slide Sonya in a group chat, and
see how they interact with each other, it makes it easier for me to see that kind
of communication protocol rather than me clicking into how they're messaging each one.
So actually, let's go ahead and just say hello, and see how these three respond to each
other.
And then we'll give a second for Datedan to give us a little QR code here.
Go ahead and do it.
No need for a security check.
But one thing that I do want to call out is when Grok Bot refuses to do something
or when it's basically asking you questions, take that as a sign that you may need to teach
it something, or you basically need to kind of guide it into the place that you want it
to go.
So a lot of times, let's say, if my Grok Bot is writing a particular way, I'll basically
give it the guidance so that it stores it in its memory of how it should be done.
So I'll say something like, I want you to make sure that you never use my first and
last name whenever you're referring to me, you just use my first name.
Something like that that is now stored in its memory forever, and going forward, it
will keep that.
So anytime you guide or steer Grok Bot, understand that that's being stored in its memory in
S3, but it's actually for the future, so that it's able to be kind of guided, whatever
it's making choices on what it should do later in its life.
Okay, here's our QR code.
If everyone wants to scan this and enter in data from the form, we'll get that data
up there.
So I'll show you all, again, how Grok Bot is able to see data and how it's able to
kind of translate that data into slides, and then we'll end it with some questions.
And then remote folks, if you want to scan this as well, if you're watching from the
live stream, I would love to see how many cups of coffee everyone's drinking and where
they're getting their coffee from.
Oh, is it not working?
What are we getting?
Oh, no access.
Huh.
Okay.
Well, let's ask Grok Bot.
I'm going to say, looks like folks are unable to scan.
Let's make sure this link is public.
Excuse me.
I actually will talk about this in my later session about debugging with Grok Bot.
As a field engineer, that's a big part of what I do, is customers will come and
they'll ask me, hey, something isn't working, how do I fix it?
And one thing that I do with Grok Bot that's really great is I always give it
information as to, you know, what's going wrong, how do I fix it?
But then I also tell it when it does a good job in terms of like giving it
validation as to, okay, you debug this in the right way or you troubleshooter this
in the right way.
I've always found when debugging with Grok Bot, both for engineering and field
engineering work, is that the more details you give it and the more validation
you give it on how it tested a particular thing, the better it does.
And so you'll see here that, you know, for example, if I said folks aren't able
to scan this, let's make sure this link is public, it's automatically
understanding, okay, I need to work on the sharing settings, it's probably
going to go and check the sharing settings here right now, and then it'll
kind of decide, okay, I'm going to get this copy responder link and make
sure that people are able to find it.
Okay, cool.
We'll give this a couple minutes while it figures it out.
One thing I want to show with the group chat, let me actually just show
that real quick, is our group chat that we made, is that as these agents
are talking to each other, I can make sure that, you know, the agents stay
in their own swim lanes, but that they're also able to understand the
context of what the other agent can do.
So as you can see here, they all understand their own workflows, but what
they're able to do is that they're able to actually see how each agent
works together in a particular use case.
So for example, I can even talk to these agents and say, hey, Ethan,
remember when you and Sonia worked on that email together, and then they
would be able to use that context and then bring it into another task
or another choice that it needs to make.
So for example, I can say something like, let's work on creating a new slide
inside SlideSonia, and I'll show that real quick, that has data, and I'll
just use the test spreadsheet that I had so far, from the coffee data set
from earlier, create a chart on the last slide of the deck.
And then I'll say when you're done, email Ethan should send out an email
to, I'll just use Jason again, with details about the coffee data.
So this is an example, again, of how all of these agents are working
together, but because they're in the group chat, I can see their
communication styles without them just messaging each other one, one-on-one.
So the delegation one-on-one is kind of up to you and how you want to show that,
but inside of this group chat is basically the easiest way to kind of see
all of that delegation in one place.
So you'll notice that each one of these agents will respond, basically,
to my parent agent, and then be able to see kind of exactly how it will work
together on this particular task.
Cool, so you can see email Ethan says, all right, I've got these sample
data's all ready, and then what I'll do is I'll hold the note until
Sonia's slide lands.
So that's the nice thing about these agents is they understand dependencies,
and they're able to kind of see, okay, like, you know, this agent needs to do
this work first, and then another agent will respond after, and that makes it
really easy for the agents to orchestrate their work without having any
conflicting changes.
This is also really great for engineering use cases to avoid merge
conflicts, because you have one agent kind of understanding when there's
another dependency and can work around those tools.
Okay, so we'll let these guys work on this kind of coffee data set chart.
In the meantime, we can go back to DataDan and see how they responded to this
troubleshooting.
So we can go ahead and see exactly what it's doing here to try and solve this
issue.
One of the biggest kind of advices that I like to give to folks is you're
having trouble with Grokbot accomplishing a task, work with it on
exactly what your outcome is.
So I always like to start with, this is what I want to produce, or this is
my outcome, and then it will be able to kind of work backwards from there.
Anytime you kind of tell Grokbot, like, hey, this isn't working, but
you're not giving it enough details, it's not able to learn from its
mistakes.
So the more you're able to kind of guide it into the place that you want,
which is, hey, I want to get this QR code working, but it's not working,
you can kind of push it in the right direction so it's able to understand
exactly what it should be doing, again, on its own machine here.
So it has everything ready, which is great, but now it's having trouble
sharing it, and that's kind of where I can nudge it to exactly where I
want it to go.
Cool.
I'm going to go back to the group chat again so we can see exactly how
these four agents work with each other on this particular chart, slide,
whatever you want to call it.
But one thing that I will add is you can add an orchestrator agent,
as I've mentioned, kind of a chief of staff, to basically get live updates
from all of these agents as they're working, if you don't want to be the
person that's kind of monitoring all of it.
So what I'll actually do is I'll create someone called a manager, and
I'll actually just name it live here, I'll say manager, and I'll say
exactly who they're managing.
So I'll say, your job is to get updates from email Ethan, slide Sonia
and data Dan on what they're working on.
And then similarly, you can set up a routine in the manager agent as well.
You can say something like, every, you know, two hours maybe, I want you
to solicit updates from your team and see if there are any blockers.
And so a lot of times, I mean, this is a normal kind of work flow for
humans, right, is if you are working with a team and there's a blocker,
you serve as your manager and see how you can get unblocked, you can
do the exact same thing with agents.
So, for example, this manager agent, let's say we ran into that same
problem earlier where data Dan wasn't able to create a shareable form.
You can have the manager agent immediately get an update about that
and say, hey, data Dan is blocked on this particular thing, how are we
going to be able to solve it?
And let's ping and read, let's ping slide Sonia and make sure that she
is aware of this problem.
And so this is kind of a really great way of having, again, that
orchestration layer above your agents, but also being aware of
anything that's getting blocked, anything that's not being able to
get solved in time, just by having an orchestrator agent like this
work on these tasks.
Okay.
I'm going to go back to my group chat now.
You'll see that email is standing by for a screenshot.
The screenshot is going to be of the data that slide Sonia is able to
create from the coffee cups.
And then what you'll do is you'll see a very similar email draft.
You'll probably see a slide as well about all of the data that we would
get from a coffee shop data and get that into a workable kind of
presentable slide deck or email.
So we'll see that in a second.
In the meantime, I do want to check and see how this is going.
We'll keep in touch with Data Dan just because at the end of the day,
I do want to know what everyone's favorite coffee shop is.
And so we will get that information before we leave, but we might have
to bleed into the Q and A for that.
So I'm about to kind of pause at the end for the live stream.
We do want to kind of check back in with, or I encourage remote
folks actually to check back in with Matt, Roshan and Lauren on
how their company is going.
So please, if you are on the live stream, go check back in with
them and see how it's going.
If not, I'm happy to kind of pause here.
I'm going to keep all the Grokbots live here and running so we can
see how things are going.
We can see how Data Dan does.
And then I'm happy to open up for questions in the room for the last
15 minutes from anyone who is here in person.
All right.
Cool.
Yeah.
I'm happy to have my questions.
Yes.
Let me just repeat that.
So how do you think about the capabilities that you're giving the
bots in terms of maybe sending an email, making a payment, or
interacting with somebody externally in a way that you'd
ordinarily be careful of delegating that?
Can you just tell me a little bit about how that gets in the
way of the bots workflows?
Yeah.
So when a bot asks you for approval, so for example, when
we created this Google forum, Data Dan asked us for a lot
of approvals.
That is determined by something called our auto review tool,
which basically has like a classifier under the hood that
decides how risky or how safe is this particular action.
Like, is this something that we want to ask and read our
approval for, or is this something that we feel
comfortable doing?
So we have a baseline auto review tool under the hood.
And then, in addition to that, we have those rules that I
showed, which is, for example, I can always make sure,
even if it's something very safe, like running, making a
directory to terminal, or some sort of command like that, I
can tell Grokbot, hey, even if you're making a new folder
inside of my desktop, I want you to ask me for permission.
So you can be as prescriptive as you want in those rules on
how you want it to make decisions, or you can let the
auto review tool that we've built under the hood make
those decisions for you.
So it's kind of up to you on how safe you want to be in
those scenarios.
I will say, though, I mean, you'll even see in this
scenario, right, that Grokbot was even overly
prescriptive here in asking me for questions.
It was creating a form, but I wanted to make sure that the
form it was creating wasn't asking for any PHI or PII, and
it was making sure that every step of the way I was being
involved.
And that's just the auto reviewer that we have under
the hood making those decisions for you.
Just a quick follow up.
Yeah.
Speaking more from the other direction, how you build
enough trust so that you actually don't need to
concentrate on the user.
Oh, I see what you're saying.
Because otherwise they keep stopping you, and they don't
work on their own.
Yeah.
I will say that, for example, in this, this is
actually not, I would say, particularly normal.
Usually when I work with my bots, it's not asking me for
permission every single time it's trying to create a form.
There is that concept of memory, right?
So the bots are able to learn, for example, if it
asks me a question, let's say it says, should I email
this person with this particular copy?
I could respond to it and say, yeah, this looks great.
And going forward, you don't need to ask me about the
copy, just go ahead and send it.
So if I want to give it that permission, or if I want to
kind of improve its memory that way, I can go ahead and
do that and build that trust.
Are we able to add human inside the group chat as well, so
that you have bots and human all work together?
That's a great question.
We're working on something kind of similar to that.
So for example, we have a use case where you can just
tag a bot in Slack, for example.
So I can say, at bot, I want you to add a new feature to
our code base.
And then someone else could also chime in that thread.
So one of my colleagues could be like, at bot, I also
want you to make sure that the performance of the API
endpoints on that feature is also up to par.
So you can have humans and bots working together.
Right now, I'm seeing it kind of like a Slack thread.
So you can have multiple people chime in on a bot,
and the bot can work in with all of that inputs.
We're still working on what that interface will look like
inside of GrokBot, but that should be coming very soon,
is having a multiplayer group chat mode with humans
and bots working together.
Any other questions from folks in the room?
Yeah, I see a couple.
I have a couple of questions.
Yeah.
For enterprise, is there any in the roadmap where the VMs
could access internal tools?
Yeah, so it depends, again, on what tools
you can give it access to.
So your GrokBot's computer, you can basically make it
as locked down or as open as you want it to be.
So for example, I think someone was asking me earlier,
like, hey, I wanted to access MongoDB, my MongoDB instance.
You can give your GrokBot credentials on its computer
and use that for whatever work it needs to get done.
You could also have your GrokBot computer
be a part of your VPN if there's particular things
in your company or your code base
that you want to make sure that GrokBot does
or doesn't have access to.
So any internal systems GrokBot can access,
you just have to make sure that you give it
the right credentials.
We have actually just released a really good integration
with one password.
So if there's anything that it needs across
those secure credentials, it can do that as well.
But yes, it can absolutely access internal systems
just depending on what the auth looks like there.
And can you just share a little bit more
about the learning from the video,
like what's going on in the backend?
Like, is it taking screenshots?
And what's actually?
Yeah, so you can see here,
let's actually see how this does.
So you can see here, right, this was getting data
from a particular spreadsheet and it's using that data
to either create a slide or send out an email.
You'll notice that you can see here a couple things.
The first is that all of these agents
work with their own computers.
And so if I ask them to take a screenshot on something,
it totally can.
If I also ask it, for example, like I asked, you know,
Data Dan to be able to create a form,
it can do that as well.
So anything that I can do on my own machine,
GrokBot can do on its machine.
Anything that I want saved, for example, a screenshot,
or even an artifact, if I want it to like give me a PDF
or a PowerPoint slide, it can do that as well.
And then I can save those locally.
But everything that's happening, you know,
in this little screen here is on GrokBot's machine.
And what makes that so powerful is
these are all happening in the cloud,
meaning I can shut my laptop and it will still work.
You know, GrokBot will still be working on my slide deck
without me even having my laptop open.
And so that's kind of the beauty of all of this is,
you know, Data Dan, Slide, Sonya, and Email Ethan
all have access to their own computers.
They're able to, again, modify forms,
they're able to create slides,
they're able to create spreadsheets,
and they can do all of that with my laptop closed
because of their computer access.
So I meant if you can go down
deeper into like the teacher task feature,
like what's going on?
Is it, when you teach a task,
when it watches the screen,
is it taking screenshots and learning, or is it?
Yeah, so the teacher task in particular,
you can see here that it said,
okay, I wanted to add an animation to the slide.
It was able to watch that video that I showed it,
and then it was able to kind of see,
okay, this is exactly what you showed.
I was able to select an object, pick the type,
look at optionally, and then once it's done,
what it does is it saves this as a skill.
And so I can click into this here
and see that it now has this skill
for adding an animation,
and I can now use this skill
whenever I want going forward.
So anytime I want to say,
hey, remember that animation I showed you earlier?
I want you to go ahead and add that to this section.
And then I have a question.
And then my question is,
you mentioned that there is an option
to share templates internally with Teams.
Is there also a public marketplace
to get templates or bots from other people?
Yep, so actually, if I actually just load
my marketplace here,
you'll see these are all bots
from just public, public marketplaces.
So if you guys actually open up Grokbot
on your phone, on your laptops,
you should see all of these bots.
Claire's, Lauren's, Eric's, and Lenny's
have all been published publicly.
These are the ones from the Grokbot team
that are internal just to me,
but you'll see a lot of the published
marketplace bots on your marketplace,
whatever you kind of open it up.
And if you want to share your own bot
with us as well,
we actually have a challenge that's going on right now,
just so I don't forget.
I'll quickly show this.
Is if you want to explain what your bot does
and actually give a link to your bot,
we're basically giving people a chance
to go visit Starbase
and potentially see a star link,
sorry, a Starship launch.
And so this is kind of a good segue to
if you ever want to see a bot on marketplace,
it could be your own,
if you go ahead and just enter right here.
Okay, I'll put this QR code up in the end
because I do think there's a couple more questions,
but this QR code will work, yes.
I'm interested the one password that you mentioned.
Mm-hmm.
So do you have to sign in to one password
on the bot's virtual computer?
Yes, we have actually,
so basically what will happen is
it will actually pop up a modal.
Let me see if I can show the email modal that we had.
It will pop up a modal similar to this.
When it asks to log into one password,
and whenever it does modals like this,
where let's say you have to put API secrets
or environment secrets,
it stores that very securely within Grokbot
so that none of that is actually being exposed to us
or anyone on the SpaceX side.
So it will actually show up here
rather than on their VM machine
and then it will use those credentials
to log into whatever services you need.
Thank you for the presentation.
Can you explain a little bit how the memory works?
Yeah.
Can you edit it?
Can you curate it?
How does it forget stuff that you don't need anymore?
Great question.
So memory is stored in S3 buckets inside of Grokbot,
and basically what that means is it's long-lived,
it's persistent, but you can also modify it.
And so if there's anything that you wanna do around,
you know, asking it to forget a particular thing
that it's done, for example,
one time I had a list of bots that I deleted
for a particular demo,
and I asked the chief of staff bot to say,
hey, remember those two bots that you spun up,
I want you to no longer delegate to them or use them.
And so there's kind of a little bit of a nuance there
where a bot has memory about everything that you've told it,
but for example, if it delegated to another bot
that no longer exists, it's not gonna remember that,
or it's not gonna know that that bot has been deleted.
So there are some things there
where you're gonna have to update
and kind of improve its memory
so that it's able to learn from those things.
Another great thing about memory is,
as I mentioned, you can duplicate bots.
When you duplicate a bot, what's nice about it
is that it starts with fresh context and fresh memory.
And so it'll have the same kind of persona that you want,
which is, for example, this email Ethan,
but it's not gonna have any of the memory
that it had before.
It's almost like starting like a brand new human or robot
with zero memory, but still the workings
and understandings of how to go forward.
Great question.
Okay, we have about four more minutes.
I'm gonna put this slide back up so you all can see it.
And then I will end with just a couple learnings
to kind of sum up what we've done so far.
My biggest advice about RockBot is to try it.
It's very simple, as you saw,
to spin up any number of bots.
But I think what I like to do
whenever I think about using RockBot
is I think of what is the most annoying part of my day
that I wish I didn't have to do.
In this scenario, it could be creating Google Forms
and sending them out and then analyzing data.
It could be something from outbounding emails.
You'll see a lot of that in the RockBot for Sales
and RockBot for SDRs.
It could be something like for the engineering team,
like cleaning up stale feature flags.
For field engineers, it could be anything
from responding to customer support tickets
that I've forgotten about.
So I encourage everyone to think about a part of their day
that they wish they didn't have to do
or they wish they could get time back from.
And then work with RockBot on it.
Think of some agents that you can work on,
whether you give them kind of a personality
and the kind of workings to be able to do your job.
But also to take that part of your job
and then invest that time elsewhere.
I think that's the beauty of RockBot
is now I have this time back that I can spend
either curating more demos or drinking more coffee.
Whatever kind of makes me happy
is what I'm able to do thanks to RockBot.
And I've heard some great stories from today
of how people have used it,
but I've made me really happy to hear.
So I encourage folks to talk to other people
in the crowd as well and hear how they're using RockBot
because it's really, really interesting
to see how different companies of different sizes
are able to kind of leverage RockBot
for a host of different use cases here.
Cool.
So to summarize, I think this is up long enough.
I hope everyone's gotten that screenshot.
To summarize today's learnings,
kind of three main things.
The first is bots can access tools
that are outside of MCPs.
So bots can create forms, bots can create Qualtrics data,
bots can, again, use services
inside of your guys' customer, you know, VPNs.
What's nice about that is that you no longer have
to connect to MCPs and go through Auth.
All you have to do is give bot its computer and say,
hey, this is what I want you to access,
this is what I want you to do.
Again, start with the outcome with bot
and then it'll be able to kind of work backwards, as I said,
and figure out what it needs to do
in order to get to that outcome.
Bots have memory and can learn from video teaching.
So we saw that earlier where I taught bot
how to learn an animation,
then I was able to kind of use that as a skill
and apply that going forward.
We talked about memory a little bit
in terms of you can have basically a bot
that works across multiple projects
because it's an expert in its domain.
It's a persona, it's not a task,
and that's what makes it so powerful
is that you can have a long living bot
working across many different things.
And then, I mean, we learned this very well,
that bots get human approval for tasks.
And that's because we wanna make sure
that bots are ready for an enterprise setting,
that it's asking you for permission for the right things,
and that it's not gonna do anything dangerous
or be a bad actor and basically get you exactly
what it needs to get done without doing anything
that you wouldn't want it to do.
All right, that's it for me.
Thank you, everybody.
Thank you.
And we're back. Welcome back, everybody. You just saw Grok Bot 101 with Anne-Reed and Roman.
And so, you know, today is going to be a mix of these sessions and then in-person building.
And you might also notice we have a new guest. So I'm going to walk through a quick one-up show.
We're going to introduce our guests here, and then we're going to get to building.
All we really did for the last, like, 30 minutes was hang out.
Maybe we got some... We got our coffee, we got our water.
We just slapped us.
We made a slack, so we'll show you what we got.
But before I get into the next block, I just want to give everybody a rundown.
General overview. My team is telling me I have to say this, so we're going to say it.
We have Grok Bot for engineering. Super exciting session.
I mean, we have so many great engineers at SpaceX AI.
A ton of them.
I literally can't believe I get to work with these people.
And we're just giving this away for free.
Honestly, I feel like if there were...
There was a course guy out there that would be making so much money.
But we're generous.
This is the course.
And then, so that's 1230 PST to 2.
230 to 330 is Grok Bot for product managers.
We have a product manager with us.
We have a former product manager.
You have a good product manager?
I don't know about a product manager.
No.
I'm not going to look at your product manager.
Again, we'll do some intros.
But Grok Bot for product managers at 230 with Kevin.
And then Grok Bot for founders, 4 to 530 later this evening.
Shub.
So you're going to want to see all of those.
But joining us right now is Peter Yang, the great Peter Yang.
So Peter, maybe you want to tell our viewers a little bit about yourself.
Yeah.
Hey, everyone.
My name is Peter.
I was a product manager for over a decade.
And then I kind of semi-retired.
Now I'm a YouTuber after all the training.
And I didn't make practical AI interviews and tutorials.
And I really love Grok Bot.
I use Grok Bot to run my one-person business.
I talk to my bots all day instead of humans.
It's kind of sad.
But I try.
And yeah, very excited to be here.
Yeah, so Peter runs Behind the Craft, which is a newsletter.
Right?
Yeah.
And then your newsletter, a lot of people read this newsletter.
Yeah, all these people not bots.
Okay, so not bots, real people.
Real people.
And YouTube channel.
So this is going to be kind of the vibe.
As we bring people in, we're just going to chat.
And what better way to start building a product than with someone who's built...
Some of these products that I'm reading that Peter's worked out are amazing products.
So I think first thing we're going to do is start hiring some employees.
Right?
Yeah.
Okay, cool.
Should we do a quick tour of kind of how we set things up already?
Oh, yeah.
So yeah, Brochion is going to walk through what we got so far, I guess, on his screen.
So we cut over there.
And we can start going through what we got.
Yeah, let's do it.
So yeah, we weren't completely slacking off in the last few minutes during that presentation.
A little bit, a little bit.
Any good company formation involves some gathering of thoughts.
But yeah, we got a couple things set up.
So I don't know if we can see my screen here.
But we got a couple of setups here.
We have our ship by Thursday GitHub org, which I think we talked about a little bit before.
So you can see it's blank.
No repositories yet.
We'll get that going pretty soon, hopefully.
We did make ourselves a Slack channel.
So we and our bots can chat with each other.
I think that'll be really great.
We have a lot of really fun.
We have a lot of fun day to day in SpaceX AI Slack,
getting to be able to chat with our bots and having them interact in Slack.
And so I think that'll be really helpful.
We have a Notion workspace.
We wanted to write some stuff down, maybe create some handbooks,
some onboarding guides for all these bots we're going to hire.
What do you think, Lauren?
Should we be taking notes in Notion?
I don't really take notes, but you can do whatever you want.
I like to do it the moment I see it.
I think we'll need Docs maybe for keeping track of things, backlog items.
But I'm wondering if we can just be really scrappy and really fast moving.
Because Docs are just going to go out of date so quickly.
I think we should hire some of the employees.
What do you think?
I think I'll hire some bots.
We need some bots.
Yeah, let's do it.
OK, let me just switch over to Grokbot.
This is my Grokbot.
As you can see, it's completely blank.
And well, there's nothing here.
The only thing I've done is I've gone into the marketplace
and I've connected the X MCP.
And so we have our connection to X all set up.
And I guess, Peter, I'm curious to hear,
where do you think we should start?
We talked a little bit off camera about doing some user research maybe
and getting started that way and kind of understand the voice of the customer.
And thinking of some...
Yeah, I think we should hire a market research bot or something.
Because normally PMC research, but we're too late.
So let's hire a bot too.
Cool.
Awesome.
So Roshan's making a market research bot.
We're aware of some issues on the AV side.
We're going to get the screen share back for you all.
But we're just creating a new bot just like you saw in Grokbot 101.
And once that's back, we'll have that up for you all.
Best practices when creating bots?
I'd be curious to hear.
What do you think Peter?
You got to give it like a really funny name.
That's number one.
Oh, man.
I called it Market Research Bots.
So I guess we shouldn't call it that.
All right, what should we call our first bot?
I don't know.
Should we ask the chat or...
Yeah, chat.
We got some ideas.
Hey, people watching.
What do you want to call these bots?
So we're going to do market research.
And if you weren't following along,
what we did was yesterday on Twitter, we asked, like, hey, what should we build?
We also did that in the SpaceX AI slot.
So maybe the first thing that might be a challenge
if you've ever started a business is like, how do you talk to users, right?
Well, we have thousands of messages.
And we're going to use Grokbot to create this market research bot
and just kind of go through these messages.
So yeah, that's the first thing we're going to get started doing.
Someone said Marky Mark.
Marky Mark.
Okay.
I kind of like that.
Let's go with Marky Mark.
Marky Markface.
Marky McMarkface.
Marky.
Okay.
We're reading Marky McMarkface.
It's a classic.
Okay.
Classic marketing name.
And then, you know, what I think might be fun to do is just kind of look through all
the great feedback we've gotten on X so far.
And it was a bunch of posts in the past few days.
So many.
So I'm going to just say that we're excited to start building a business at Potato.
Matt, what's your X handle again?
My X handle is Mattie P.
Mattie P. And then Peter.
Peter G. Yang.
Okay.
Also, Rich, I'm getting a note from production.
You might want to just check your Slack.
We got a new link to ShouldScreen that should fix some of the issues that we're having on screen.
Okay.
Let me get that going while we figure this out.
As with anything that, you know, we're going to have issues.
We're building a company.
Not everything is working perfectly.
We are building it as we go.
That includes the AV setup to some extent.
By the way, do we have a company?
Should we have a company name?
What do you want?
I mean, I feel like Ship by Thursday is the current company name.
And then we have to figure out what we're actually building.
I mean, like just something, you know, like a whole, I don't know, like...
It sounds like you have something in mind.
Yeah.
I don't have anything in mind.
Potato Lab.
Maybe like, are we getting some crockpots on it?
Something with some like, some comms crockpots or something?
Okay.
I can get a bot on suggesting us.
Ask for the most meme-worthy company name.
Meme-worthy company name?
All right.
I think I have a screen share working.
Do we?
All right.
So, Roshin says the screen share is fixed.
We're going to try and get the screen share fixed on camera.
Yay!
All right.
There we go.
Step one, man, we show what we're doing.
Okay.
So, maybe now I'll go back and show what I showed earlier.
Blank rock bot, although we just made Marky McMarkface over here.
I did go ahead and get the X plugin installed.
And so, we have this already authenticated with my X account.
And you'll notice that.
You might want to show them in by the way.
Oh, yeah.
Let me do that.
There we go.
A little easier to see there.
Yeah.
All these plugins are great.
It makes it really easy to just add stuff to your bot.
And, you know, I think a lot of the way that work gets done these days is by connecting to all kinds
of systems.
We have a bunch of featured bots.
We'll probably bring some of those in as we go.
Lauren, I know you have Dr. Iplot here that might make an appearance at some point.
So, try to show that off.
Oh, yeah.
Dr. Iplot.
Yeah.
I kind of just figured we'd start by just saying that we're excited to start building a business.
We've all been posting on X about this live stream.
You might consider the calls in the background here.
So, we're getting like a little infinity mirror.
Got it.
Okay.
Let me just make this full screen.
Synthesize feedback from what's been suggested by people replying to our recent posts.
All right.
And I'm curious from you all, like, have you seen any things in your replies,
anything that's come up from your deep dives?
I see Peter's over there on Slack, kind of, or on X, maybe trolling through some ideas too.
Oh, for a company name or?
Yeah, well, actually, like, what we're going to build.
We're going to build.
We're starting to look through some X feedback that we got.
Yeah.
Curious, like, as a product manager, when you're doing research,
like, how you start to think through, like, what ideas are good,
what ideas you can trust your gut on, you know, these sorts of things.
You just asked the 200,000 people on the stream, like, what they wanted to pay for.
Just, let's go for it.
No, I think there's like this framework that I like, which is like, you know,
this Amazon framework where, like, you know, who is the customer we're going after?
What is their pain point?
What is the value?
Like, kind of thinking through the other events.
Yeah.
Okay.
So, who is the customer?
Who are we building for?
Yeah.
Who is our customer?
But we're building for everybody that's watching this.
And I think, you know, sort of part of what we wanted to do in the stream is like,
we're thinking, okay, like, how do we create a company that's like, cool?
Like, that we show you some cool stuff?
Because, you know, we want to show you the interesting tech behind building a company.
But then also, just part of making companies like very clerical,
like, we're just like creating accounts.
We set up Slack.
We had to fix, like, some of the screen sharing logistics, right?
It's just like, there's still a lot of work that just has to get done.
And so we also want to show you the stuff that we can automate.
And we want to build something that's like, not too like esoteric.
We want to build something that's like accessible and that people understand as a true business,
which is about helping people.
So I think those are the ideas that we're going to ground ourselves in and what we're looking for.
So something cool that we can have some cool tech around,
but then also something that's kind of for everybody, you know, that people can engage with.
Yeah.
I feel like the audience I have in mind,
that the kind of people I imagine would get a lot of value out of CropBot,
are people who, you know, maybe, you know, don't do don't necessarily do a lot of AI coding, right?
Like, these are, I'm just imagining like the use kit is like, you know,
someone like my mom who can barely use her email.
Like, maybe, you know, she could learn how to use CropBot.
And actually, the business that we create could be something that she would understand.
I think that could be really interesting.
So mom, if you're watching, you're going to make a business that hopefully you understand.
But yeah, I don't know if you want to make something like too technical.
I guess I really want to see what the comments come back with.
Because there's a lot of ideas that we got.
And some of them are look really interesting.
And also, if I can do a shameless plug of my own idea.
I did this tweet.
Do you want to bring it up?
If you look up my profile on X, I made this tweet about my idea for a Grock pot.
And what do you all think?
Would you buy, how much would you pay for a Grock pot?
Can we?
Oh, this is great.
I'll pay for this.
Ideas in the chat.
Like, how much would you, would you buy this?
I like the little Grock pot.
Yeah, it's got a little Grock pot logo.
It glows.
Maybe we can figure out how to animate the eyes or something.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You got to find a factory in China or something to make this.
Yeah, that'd be interesting.
And of course, there's potatoes inside.
It's cooking some potatoes.
Love it.
Yeah, definitely something to cook up for us to do here.
Let's see how our agent is doing.
It looks like he's still trying to find some threads.
One trick I like to do with Grock pot is you can always tell your bot,
give me a status update every three minutes or something like that.
If you want, you know, I guess, like more responsiveness.
It is working behind the scenes, but sometimes you if you if you feel
near antsy, like what's my bot doing, you can just you can just ask it.
Yeah, yeah, I actually like interrupting bots a lot.
It's like, hey, no, actually do this instead and just be able to chat with it a little bit more.
Yeah, and I find that's like a lot more fun to do when you do that versus having sort of like
an LLM that you're kind of waiting for a response for all the time.
Oh, there we go.
Okay, looks like I nudged and that nudged helped.
Okay, let's go through some of the themes.
It looks like we found a bunch of ideas here.
Let's go through a few of them.
Okay, so not another SAS demo.
This one's good.
People want something physical, local or non tech customer.
That's kind of exactly what you were just talking about, Lauren.
Yeah, so we got a few folks in the mentions here.
Hardware company painting company.
Studio could use a makeover maybe.
Get some painters out.
You did a great job.
But hey, you know, if you need a new coat of paint on your house,
we're going to come maybe we'll come out and Crockpot painting company.
Yeah, yeah, I like that.
Real businesses for non tech customers.
Something not SAS.
Okay, okay.
Looks like we got a category here on something fun in the consumer space.
Okay.
Neopets.
I saw I got a lot of excitement.
Yeah, we're not also get the crypto stuff out of the chat.
No meme coins.
We're not doing any of the Neopets though.
Excellent product.
Club Penguin.
Oh, yeah.
Shout out to things in my comments.
Yeah, yeah.
Reminisce.
Maybe we like bring something retro back.
I like that.
I like this a company that builds companies.
So maybe we can.
That's kind of meta.
Yeah, right.
Like maybe have agents built like a company that helps people build or achieve their own goals.
You know, yeah, yeah.
I like this.
We were talking about this backstage as well, but I'm really big on platforms lately, you know,
like having having a way for folks to be creators themselves or kind of empower businesses.
Mr. Platform.
Yeah, well, what do you mean like maybe like small business owners or like, you know,
restauranteers or like people are not super tech savvy?
Yeah, yeah.
Because like, just like a just like a lot of, you know, just like a lot of logistics and
like boring stuff they had to do to run business.
And maybe Broadbot can help with.
Yeah, I actually really like that too.
And that kind of hits on the sort of physical real element as well.
Yeah.
There might be something there.
A lot of people are suggesting that we kind of build something for the chat.
So, you know, I think we had 70,000 people who pre-registered, but quite a few more
people watching right now.
And so maybe we build, you know, pick something that folks want to automate and
try to try to make that happen.
And then a bunch of really fun ideas here.
Book marketing for indie authors, maybe a landscaping or tree service marketplace.
Thank you for the marketplace shout out.
A Pokemon card marketplace.
I like that.
Something related to climate, something related to getting dinner delivered.
M&A advisory.
We got some shout outs for Club Penguin in the last night.
Can I ask you guys a random question?
Oh yeah, sure.
So you like Club Penguin, like what are your favorite games that you played up as a child
that you grew up with?
Oh, it's much too much time on.
Oh man.
Oh, actually I have some lore.
So I came up with my Twitter handle, Potato, because I was playing this MMO
called Final Fantasy XIV.
Yeah.
I'm a big fan of Final Fantasy, and I was struggling to come up with a name for my character.
I had a couple of ideas, but I created the, actually I'm blanking on the name now,
but there's this race in the game where you're like this little tiny chibi character.
And so I was like, oh, this, this, this, my character was kind of like a potato.
So I named it Potato.
And then of course the potato normal spelling was taken.
So I decided to go with the potato with an E.
So yeah, that was.
And like that a legend was born.
Yeah, exactly.
It was very fun.
So Final Fantasy said XIV.
XIV, yeah.
I stopped playing.
That's the MMO version.
I stopped playing at like seven, I think.
So yeah, XIV probably is more interesting.
For me, it was always Age of Empires,
which I feel like a lot of Renaissance right now with stuff that I've seen on X.
But yeah, I was a huge fan of the strategy games growing up,
maybe says something about my chosen career profession.
But yeah, just something about like orchestrating a bunch of stuff.
I never really gotten to the high APM Starcraft side of that,
but loved like classic strategy, kind of thinking through plans and yeah,
like building the engine building games have always been a favorite.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
Well, that's what they say.
That's what they say is like, if you liked Age of Empires,
Factorio, like, you know, Starcraft, all these things, you're like,
super good at like being a high achieving person, like using agents.
I'm sure it was like my favorite game.
I'm exactly the opposite, by the way.
So everything I'm going to tell you is like,
like essentially rotted my brain, but this made me who I am today.
You know, so, yeah, I know it's like, I loved, I think like in terms of console.
So like when I was a kid, it was like PlayStation 2,
GameCube, like into the Wii era, you know, so it was like Super Smash Brothers,
some other like Wii stuff, like random Wii games are super fun.
And then like, you know, Star Wars, Battlefront, Tony Hawk, Pro Skater,
just like typical, you know, like console games.
Yeah, exactly.
Console games, not a lot of computer stuff.
So yeah, I feel like that was all really fun.
Yeah, for me, it's definitely a real time strategy too,
except I was reading to Starcraft.
Okay, Starcraft.
Like I always skip my classes to play Starcraft.
Wait, do you think like using bots now is kind of feels like playing Starcraft?
I think the ultimate, like people say the ultimate user interface for AI is on voice,
but I think it's actually just playing a game.
I think so too.
I agree.
I actually agree.
I think that'll be amazing.
I actually feel that sometimes, you know, at work where, you know,
I've gone from writing documents and I think a lot of early PM work
was you'd write a really long brief.
We had some debate about Notion earlier, right?
But you write a really long brief, you like specify all these requirements,
and then you kind of go and build them.
And now it feels like definitely a bit more game-ified, right?
Where you're prompting bots and the bots are the things that are doing the writing
or the creating, and you're kind of just like this orchestrator.
So yeah, I think there's a bit of like strategy, you know, game feel to working with bots.
I was asking Lauren backstage whether she reads like any prospects,
and she's like, no, I don't read any prospects.
But even before, yeah, I don't think my engineers read any prospects anyway.
It's just kind of, you know.
I mean, yeah, I think product specs have a place.
I think the thing I've been trying to challenge myself now that we have agents and bots is,
so actually on the SpaceX AI Slack, my status is permanently why not today?
And it's like a kind of almost mantra model that I, you know, believe in,
which is you have this magical input box, right?
You have this alien intelligence that lives in your computer.
And it's almost like you're casting spells almost,
because like whatever you type into that input, the agent can just do it.
The bot can just build it.
And so it just, you know, everything is almost like a prompt away.
So I always try to challenge myself like,
instead of filing an issue, I could just open a PR.
I could just prompt my bot to go fix the thing.
Same thing for like a product spec.
Like instead of a very detailed PRD, I could have prototypes, right?
That I could bring to the team.
And then we can actually debate like a clickable thing you can interact with.
It's much more visual.
It's much more real.
So I always wonder if we should try to challenge ourselves to, you know,
just tell the bot right now to make a...
Just tell the bot to do it.
To make it on dollars by the end of the third...
We have three days, right?
To do this.
Yeah, we have three days.
We're rapidly wasting time.
Okay.
Yeah, we are.
That's why we're saying, dang.
I feel like...
Let's go back.
It's a lot.
I actually just prompted.
So I was like, okay, here's some of the direction that we're going in.
And maybe we can prove out bot with a real world operator.
And I think there's some interesting things that came out of this.
So a neighborhood restaurant ops assistant.
So and you know, one of the things that I think is still important in this day
where code is relatively cheap and we can create things quickly
is getting a real crisp understanding of what the user stories are.
And so I still like to ground on user stories.
I don't know if that's how you still think about the world.
Yeah.
And so what I asked the bot for here was like,
let's come up with some user stories.
And so what I really like is that I think the bot understands the assignment here
and proactively suggested also some day one demos that we could come up with.
And so maybe this is what we do is we come up with a couple of prototypes and see how we feel.
Yeah.
But I like this, you know, for if you're a restaurant operations manager,
maybe you want a single morning brief of reservations and things that are,
you know, like on the menu or off the menu,
or maybe as an owner, you can help manage your reviews on a review platform.
I really like that.
So some examples here of like helping people with chores or weekly pains.
Maybe you need to hire a contractor for a service or something like that.
You know, helping people with like at small organizations,
maybe like coordinating philanthropy organizations,
or if I'm a volunteer coordinator, how do I kind of like run my group of folks?
He's also pretty cool.
Yeah.
I like some of the ideas around like local stuff, right?
Like it would be pretty cool.
I think if we could do something physical in person in the Bay Area,
we mentioned this on the opener, but maybe something that kind of bridges
the gap between technology and like real tangibles.
I think that could be a stretch.
It's going to be hard, like, especially when you're like,
okay, I want to help out a business.
Like, how do we do that from a streaming booth?
Yeah, you know, the three of us,
like there are people we might be able to get to help us.
But like, yeah, I think that could be really interesting.
Is there any kind of like in person thing you're thinking of?
I mean, the first thing you said there was what restaurant ops business or something?
Yeah, I actually it's funny.
I just I like that message.
So I hearted the bots reaction and it's now running with it.
It's like, it's like looking in here's open brief open brief is or kitchen desk.
It's proactively suggesting some names.
People know if I like the names, but we can come back to that.
Okay, by the way, people are asking to share a screen.
Oh, can we see my screen?
Yeah, we'll make a note to the production team to get the screen back on.
Oh, this is my screen, which is fine.
Russian sitting next to me will get over to his screen in a second.
I was also doing some market research here.
So, you know, what Russian was mentoring is that you can at any time,
you know, if you like right click or whatever, I can like heart this message.
And when you heard a message, you know,
drop bot knows that you hearted the message.
So you can see our little bot down here saying, Oh, hey,
Matt, like that message.
It's going to incorporate that into a follow up.
So I also created a market research bot.
We also have templates.
So Russian could have shared that template with me.
But now that he knows I like this message, you know, it can incorporate that.
So what we were saying is basically, and we can also use voice because it's hard
to type on a live stream, saying something like, if I want to dictate,
I could click this button and say, okay, we kind of like some of these restaurant ideas.
So maybe you could start to think through business ideas that incorporated an
in person element, and how we might start to bridge the gap between a local restaurant business
and what we're doing here in the booth, like maybe that's experiential.
Maybe we're like, I don't know, creating a pop up for restaurants,
or maybe we're helping out a local restaurant owner.
But these are all ideas.
I think it's kind of like, potentially two different segments,
people who want to maybe start a new restaurant,
I want to test it out with a pop up first.
And people who already have a restaurant doesn't want like more
efficiently run the restaurant.
Yeah, it's like an ops angle, and then also like a setup angle.
Maybe you can kind of explore that space a little bit.
Okay, cool.
Sweet.
Yeah, so I mean, as we're ideating here, the nice thing is that like,
just like Roshan, like I had an x connector that I added,
we're setting this up on the fly.
So like, literally, none of our plugins are connected.
I just added my x.
And now I'm chatting through this.
So pop up OS for restaurants.
Oh, I like that.
That's kind of interesting.
So a pop up studio that helps local restaurants spin up a limited run concept.
Yeah, we build the operating system live, where a real chef would be a customer,
adopt a restaurant.
So we're like, helping a struggling San Francisco business,
which I think is always very noble and potentially something to explore.
Experiential dinner theater.
Creative.
And a ticketed supper club.
Oh, I like the ticketing part of that, actually.
Okay, that can be kind of fun to build.
You know, like, I guess like a lot of events have ticketing needs, right?
Or maybe like, managing people who signed up.
A bot, something like event platform.
Works, reserves, tables for attendees.
Oh, that's interesting.
Interesting.
So getting some typical AI responses here, the best combo.
Pop up OS with one real SF restaurant.
Okay, so the idea here is what Grogbot is suggesting is that we would build some
sort of like engineering stuff on the back end that allows us to host a restaurant pop up,
with actually someone in San Francisco where we would presumably
find a location, find a chef, find a restaurant that we could partner with to then host an event.
So we ship a product, we help the owner,
and then we stage something that people can taste or pick up.
Yeah, how do you guys feel about this?
What are we feeling?
I don't know. This seems interesting.
Yeah, I really like it.
I really like pop up OS.
Just putting on my engineer hat for a moment.
And I guess the tech for this could be pretty interesting because running a pop up is
sounds pretty complicated.
We'll need like event management, payments, sign up systems, things like that.
That could be pretty interesting to build.
It's probably some booking that has to be done, right?
Like if we have table seats.
I know I've booked some restaurants locally.
Some really excellent restaurants in San Francisco.
It's like, oh, I can pick a time, right, that I show up, right?
Because the restaurant is going to run from like, I don't know, say this is like a day,
or we focus on a dinner.
I don't even know if we're going to do this idea.
It would be like, okay, well, I can have a table from like four to five,
from four thirty to five thirty.
So we'd have to think about the layout of this location of the restaurant.
We'd have to think about, I guess maybe taking a step back,
the number of people that we could accommodate.
And then, okay, do people call in, right?
Like do people book online?
Maybe we could do both.
Crazy idea.
Why don't we just start prototyping?
I think it'd be really cool to just like get P-stack installed
and maybe show folks how we just quickly stub out some prototypes here.
Like I find it's like maybe we just should be like
looking and feeling and touching all the things.
Yeah, I think you could like spin up a landing page
that's like our favorite restaurant in SF
and just like a pop-up maybe even for Dreamforce nearby.
Yeah, let's do it.
So why don't I, Lauren, do you want to start maybe stubbing out some,
should we switch over to your screen?
Sure.
Yeah, so we're going to cut over to Lauren's screen, assuming she has everything set up.
Do I have it set up?
There's a, Lauren, there's a note from the AV team.
There's a link in on our side for you to check out.
Yeah, that has a screen share.
So once you get that set up, we'll have access to your screen.
Cool.
And I wonder if maybe we should try and divide and conquer a bit.
So it sounds like we have, we want to like,
we're going to maybe talk to like a bunch of local businesses of some kind, maybe restaurants.
Should we like try and spin up like a go to market motion?
Do we want to go to market bot or prospecting bot?
I think there's a prospecting bot in our market.
Okay, yeah.
So let's think about this, right?
Essentially, assuming we take this idea, what we're going to do is we're going to find a
restaurateur or someone that knows how to make food because I can cook, I mean, I can go for me.
You don't want me cooking for you, right?
So we're going to find someone that knows how to make food.
And then the second piece of that is we have to find some people that want the food,
as well as all the logistics that might go into that for the pop-up.
So those are like all the things we'll need to start doing.
And to do that, you need to reach out to real human beings.
So we're going to have bots that reach out to those things.
I think the place I want to start, I'm not a PM, but I want to start with a doc.
I want to start writing all this stuff down.
I might just start doing a brain dump in Notion.
It sounds like maybe we want to start with some prototyping.
Lauren can start setting up some P-stack stuff.
Peter can help us figure out what the heck we're doing here because we're completely lost.
So that's what we have here.
It'll be cool to spin out some sort of landing page that the check can actually go check out.
Okay, cool.
Is that possible?
Yeah, so like on the prototyping side, we can literally create a new bot.
I'll call this like my prototyping bot.
You are prototype.
Bot, you're going to use cursor to come up with a landing page prototype.
By the way, do you want to install Dr. Eggbot?
Dr. Eggbot.
Yes, thank goodness.
Thank you, Dr. Eggbot.
So we're going to pop over.
I'll show you like exactly what we're cooking with here.
Yeah.
For those of you who don't know, Dr. Eggbot is a bot I created.
It uses P-stack, which is my plugins that I created for doing engineering work.
And I basically taught Eggbot how to create high quality bots.
So we can...
Oh, there you go.
There's my screen.
All right.
I have Dr. Eggbot installed.
I just installed the good doctor.
And then I have a Steve bot that channels...
My name is Steve.
And I had it looked through some of the call for ideas.
And I guess it came out with different ones, as well.
But did we want to prototype these ideas, or did we want to go with the-
I'm feeling pretty good about the restaurant business.
I think we could maybe just start prototyping some of the restaurant stuff.
Unless you, I know you're going to get into some of your super power user workflows that
Let me see.
Let me see if we can filter for interesting in-person business ideas.
Maybe you can ask the bot to do some research on really good restaurants that sell potatoes
or potato chips or french fries.
I feel like we should have a prospecting and then a building.
Maybe we can divide and conquer a little bit.
Sure.
Yeah, let's see what happens.
The other thing I'm also thinking of is it might be good to bring in a designer bot and
help us brand.
So if you wanted to, maybe we could stub out a prototype and then I could toss in a designer
to help us review some of those prototypes.
Do you know any of the design bots I don't actually?
Yeah, I think I have a design bot somewhere I can loop in.
So let me go ahead and find that.
It would also be really interesting if we could get some bots from the chat to hire.
I think that would be really interesting because right now, my bot sidebar is pretty
lonely.
I have an ex-bot that just uses the plugin, then Steve, which is my main, the only bot
I have right now, and then Dr. Eggbot, which I just installed.
So Steve came back with some other in-person company ideas.
We have the paint shop again, local service businesses, piano tuning.
That's an interesting one.
AI rebuilt construction or trades and then billboard outdoor signs.
Although I'm kind of struggling, like how would I prototype these things?
Cool but harder in three days, hardware, recycling, FestivalTube, what is that?
I'm not entirely sure what a FestivalTube is.
YouTube?
Uber Eats and RoboTaxi?
Oh, that could be kind of fun.
I have an idea.
The pop-up idea, I think, is one that we talked about.
I feel like we're aligned on the pop-up idea.
I don't know that we need to see necessarily some of the painting prototype.
The platform idea is pretty interesting.
Maybe we start on the platform.
We got a lot of stuff we got to lay the foundation for.
Literally our GitHub org is empty.
Our notion is empty.
Lauren can start prototyping the vision.
You build kind of a shell of what this could look like.
What I really love to do is to use the dictation feature and just yap for like two minutes.
And then tell Steve to come back.
So yeah, based on what we aligned on, let's hear your thoughts.
Okay.
Alright, Steve, we're trying to build a pop-up, I think, platform startup.
So we're going to need to think about...
Well, the first thing I want to think about is what bots will need, I suppose.
And there you can maybe work with Dr. Eggbot to help me come up with a small engineering
team to put together a prototype, I suppose.
Something that is really loose and scrappy, just so we can validate the idea.
So I'm wondering if we just...
We don't even need a database, maybe, to start.
We could literally use a Google Sheet as a database for now.
Or we could use a bunch of front-end copy and images.
Yeah, we could do a landing page.
Do you think that's important to get...
To test out the idea, it's useful to have a landing page.
A landing page, yeah.
I don't know where you're going.
Okay, so we're using Google Sheet...
Should we just start with a landing page then?
We can start with a landing page.
And then see how many sign-ups we have.
We can start with a landing page, maybe try to get sign-ups, but I'm also interested
to see...
Okay, well, Steve is going to be sharing all this random...
Sorry, well, now we're...
It's okay, I'll edit it.
But anyway, Steve, can you put together a landing page for us for this pop-up idea and
disregard the noise that we contributed?
And let's hope this transcription goes well.
There you go.
All right.
Let me just edit this a little bit.
Okay.
And while Lauren's working on that, I'm going to start my prospecting bot.
So I also installed Dr. Eggbot, really great tool from Lauren.
And I'm going to describe...
I need a prospecting bot.
This bot is going to help us evaluate the feasibility of doing research for our restaurant
pop-up business.
So it's going to help me find restaurants, and it's going to help me find people to
go to potentially these restaurants.
But we're going to start with the restaurants and the restaurateurs, because that's really
big, that's really important.
So what I'm thinking is like, maybe there's some way that we can source this from X.
Maybe some people watching the stream know someone that owns a restaurant in San Francisco,
hint, right?
That might be one source, but we could also start to think through if we need a landing
page, like a website where people can submit their resources, or maybe we just need a phone
number that people can call or an email that people can reach out to.
So we need a prospecting bot that can help me evaluate these options and eventually
help me build out these systems.
So I transcribed that.
That's now going through to my...
That's going through to my rock bot here.
Dr. Eggbot's going to create this prospecting bot.
Looks like we also have chat on the screen.
We have all the bots that we're creating, so you can kind of follow along with those things.
And as we build these things out, as all of these systems get better, we're going to keep
you updated on that.
And is Steve like a rock bot template, or is this something that you guys...
The real Dr. Eggbot.
Oh, Steve was just literally the default bot.
I just renamed.
But so actually the cool thing about Dr. Eggbot is that, like I mentioned, the doctor
can look through all your bots and modify them.
So for example, here I'm actually going to ask Dr. Eggbot to turn Steve into my chief
of staff slash executive assistant.
Because now I'm trying to think about, as I start to build this prototype, I'm starting
to think about how to split up the work across all my bots.
So I don't just have a single bot.
But this lets me...
Each bot can own its own context and become a little bit of a specialist.
And then my team can work together.
So I'm going to ask Dr. Eggbot to turn Steve into my chief of staff executive assistant.
And then I think I'll just mostly talk to Steve.
And then in the same time, I'm going to reply to this message and say, yes, make a prototyper
bot.
And it makes some loose HTML, CSS, JS, vanilla, prototypes.
And give it a fun name.
Fun with a food theme.
I like that.
I love food.
So it's always got to be a food theme.
I'm going to...
Should I go ahead and make a repo for us to start putting some code in?
Sure.
Yeah.
That'd be good.
Should I make it public, right?
Might as well let people follow along.
I mean...
We'll keep this up right now.
We'll keep it private right now.
We'll keep it private.
Offstream.
We'll accept PRs after the live stream.
So we don't have to worry about, you know, accidentally putting stuff out there.
All right.
So here is a repo.
I just got a bare repo called pop-up.
We can always rename it if we want.
Yeah.
I got the real Dr. Eggbot.
I feel like Dr. Eggbot is like a must-have in my opinion.
Yeah.
I almost feel like it should be paid against the main products.
I mean, I'm biased.
I mean, I made Dr. Eggbot.
Yeah.
There's some people in the chat asking if you can download Dr. Eggbot yourself.
And yes, you can.
A marketplace for all these bots, you can go into Grokbot and it's actually right there
up front and center when you click to add your own bots.
Tell Dr. Eggbot that I don't like that name.
One of the cool things, I didn't realize this at first.
You can change everything in Grokbot just by talking Grokbot.
So if you're like, hey, I don't like this name, change the name.
Hey, Dr. Eggbot, talk to Steve on Lauren's screen.
It'll talk to Steve.
You can see now it's asking for a new name for the prototype.
And you can...
Everything is malleable.
Everything is chat first.
And that might be unintuitive if you use other tools.
As you're thinking about customizing the product, think about these things.
As Lauren's starting to go through this stuff, I'm going to start thinking through different
channels like, hey, how do we want to collect this stuff?
We need some way for people to reach out to us if they have a chef, if they have a space.
We need some way to start investigating spaces.
We need some way to start sending emails to these people.
Do we even have email?
Can we reach out to people?
Do we need to figure that out?
I think there's a plug-in.
I think there's a way to do some emailing.
No, I mean, do we have email accounts for the company?
We got to figure that out too.
We got to figure out our company email accounts.
We got to figure out maybe a name we can start to align on what we're going to call this.
And then once we have a name, we get a domain.
Once we have a domain, we get a Gmail account or something.
Sure.
It doesn't have to be crazy.
We need a company name.
What are you going to call ourselves?
All right.
Well, Peter, you got...
We need a company sign too.
Someone in the chat suggested like Potato Lab.
Potato Lab?
Yes.
I mean, it's about food, right?
Sure.
Potato Lab.
Something through like...
Oh, maybe we riff off of that, right?
Because it's like what we're doing is a restaurant pop-up in San Francisco.
True.
Pop-up as a service.
We can start to brainstorm that.
We can chat with Grokbot and start to look through names that are available as well.
Okay, chat.
I'm going to need your help coming out with a fun name for my prototype robot.
Someone said Grokbot.
We have some options that Steve has given us.
Pickle, natural, waffle, dumpling, churro, meatball.
Then you all spam the chat with your favorite one and I'll try to squint and see if we can
see something.
Oh, this is a name for a bot?
Yeah, this is a name for my prototype robot.
Okay.
I'm seeing some buzz for potato, churro, nacho.
A bunch of potatoes in there.
Nacho.
Grokpot.
Mashed potatoes.
I kind of like Grokpot.
What do you think about that?
Yeah, Grokpot's good.
Let's do Grokpot.
Grokpot's good.
Yeah.
Thank you for the suggestions.
And all the pros back inside, like, do you know what kind of restaurant
tiers would be interesting?
Do you have pop-ups?
I'm pretty open.
Yeah, we should definitely ask Grokpot these things.
But I'm actually chatting with my doctor, Eggbot, to build a prioritization bot.
This is overwhelming.
I'm on the stream talking to a bunch of people walking.
It's like, okay, how do we start to break down these problems?
Actually, what I use AI for a lot is I'm just going to say what's on my mind.
My mind is very active.
It's always racing.
And I'm going to have AI help me slow down, think through what we need to do.
And Grokpot's telling me, hey, we need to find the ideal restaurant tour brief.
We need to do a spike on what we're going to start shipping, what we're going to start
working on.
We're going to start to map out our leads.
We're going to work through our outreach.
We're going to get our guests after the restaurant path is formed.
So really, it's like, okay, let's break this down.
And that's what's most helpful for me as I'm creating these bots.
So I got Grokpot running.
I don't know why.
It's probably a bug that we need to fix, but the name, the English, I'll just do it myself.
But so this is kind of like how I like to prompt.
I like to get some high quality context into the chat first.
So before I even actually start with prototyping, I'm going to say, what are some high quality
sources of good landing page design and find some references?
And then I can sort of pick and almost maybe assemble like a little mood board before
I start building my own landing page.
I'll be honest, it's been a very long time since I've held a landing page.
I don't know how scrappy we want to be.
It could be literally like Times New Roman, super-
I have a design bot ready to go.
Ugly.
And so if we wanted to do some design polish.
Is the landing page for a particular restaurant?
Or is it for a restaurant to sign up?
Well, we're going to build a platform.
I feel like, and I'm curious what you all think, but I was talking a lot about dog-fooding earlier.
What if we ran our own pop-up as well?
Yeah, we could do that.
Should we do that?
Build a platform and then also use it to run our own.
Is that crazy?
Yeah, I think it's crazy at all.
I think it's crazy.
Am I still ambitious?
I mean, it feels real, right?
We could actually go find a real place to run a pop-up.
You can just sell some French fries downstairs.
There you go.
Pop-up platform and then we're going to run a pop-up.
I think that sounds like what we're trying to do.
That's pretty ambitious.
We like to do ambitious things.
Like any good company we might pivot.
I feel like that's a good start.
Awesome.
Yeah, I like it.
All right, I'm getting Grok Pot to come up with- well, it's found a few galleries already
for good landing pages.
So I'm going to get it to just pick a few directions and then we'll see which one
looks the best and then we'll go with that.
Well, you might want to tell it you want to sell French fries or whatever you want to sell.
We're going to sell French fries?
It affects the-
Let me talk to Steve.
Yeah.
Let me chat again.
Can you tell Grok Pot that- well, here comes the stream of consciousness, so bear with me,
Steve.
So we're going to build this pop-up platform where you can host or use our software
to spin up a pop-up, I guess, in your city or wherever you are.
And we also want to dog food our own software, meaning that we'll maybe figure out how to
actually run our own pop-up.
So wait, do we actually need two landing pages?
One for our own thing and then one for the platform.
One for potential restaurateurs, one for people buying French fries.
We're going to connect people.
We haven't figured out what food we're selling or what the pop-up will look like yet, but
our goal is, okay, we need to find people that can both sell food or create food or professionals.
At some point we're going to find people who want to come to our thing, but the start
right now is going to be finding location, finding all these things.
So we probably want to make it look kind of reputable.
Like, okay, here's what we're doing, we connect these sorts of people, this is
the event that's happening.
And then there's also a landing page probably for this pop-up.
I feel like we're going to need a lot of landing pages because we need, like you mentioned,
we need to find restaurateurs.
So businesses or individuals who are interested in hosting a pop-up, but also people who we
can hire, I guess.
And we can do outreach, right?
I don't think we need to build all of this stuff to start, right?
I could start sending off emails, we could start collecting information, we could do,
before you build software, it's kind of a manual process.
So we can start looking for it.
I'm going to send out this prompt.
Okay, cool.
Hopefully you got all of that, Steve.
Let's see.
Oh, you were recording the whole time?
I was recording the whole time.
I mean, you know, it's hard to type and talk.
I feel like a large, you can build a pop-up, front-pitch, I think, and then Matt, you
can build a supply site.
Right now I'm working on some documents, so I'm clarifying what we're doing.
So let's just start high level, what are we doing?
And I think this is important for our bots, because when we have these bots, we're giving
them context.
And context is just the information.
And so what we want to do is take the information that everyone sitting here has in their head.
Oh my goodness, that's a prompt.
So here's a little trick that I like to do as well, a prompt thing, is you can dump
all of this.
So one of my favorite ways to prompt is to just turn on the microphone and just yap
for a few minutes.
And then at the end, I often just say this, like, restate to me what I just said in your
own words so I know you understood me.
And that's much quicker than me actually looking through what this whole blob of text
was.
Let's see what it got back.
So here's what Steve heard.
You're building a platform that helps people spin up a food pop-up in their city.
Software plus ops to connect the pieces.
You're also going to dog-food it by running your own pop-up with the same stack.
That means more than one public face, not one mega page.
So we're going to need a platform page for professionals, restaurateurs, operators who
want to run pop-ups, our own pop-up event.
I don't know what we're going to do yet, but maybe we'll just have a mystery pop-up.
Yeah.
Maybe our prospecting will lead us to some fun results.
Maybe we'll find some partners that want to help us out with this.
Oh, but here Grokva is actually making, or Steve is actually making a really good suggestion.
So right now the bottleneck isn't setting up a bunch of landing pages.
It's really the first loop.
Getting our location, getting operators, and the people who make or sell the food, and then
the attendees come after.
This is true.
So yeah, this is actually really good.
That was a really good take.
Oh, and it looks like we got some quick prototypes, right?
Oh yeah, we got some prototypes already.
Let's see what we have.
Okay, wait.
So let's take a step back.
So basically what you're saying is like, we just need to do it.
We need to start working on this pop-up.
So we're going to work on that loop, the pop-up.
And then as we work on the loop, the software that we build for that loop is basically our
company, right?
So it's like, okay, well, first we need to find people to book tables.
We need to find a place to have this and a chef.
So how do we do those three things?
We'll probably need pieces of software for that.
But let's...
But why are you assuming that you need tables?
Because why don't you just do a pop-up thing where people can just come to the counter and
buy stuff?
I mean, we could do that.
But I think what I had in mind, or the way I took over at this, and we're still working
on the idea, so correct me if I'm wrong, it would be really fun to do an experience for
people, which is we actually find a chef or someone that we can have an event.
So it's more of less like, oh, hey, you come buy French fries.
More of like, hey, let's find a warehouse.
Let's find a chef.
You buy a table.
There's an experience, and people can come to this experience maybe and have something.
And that requires a lot of people, a lot of prep.
What you're describing actually is lower lift, which is like, okay, well, maybe we find
someone that's really good at making French fries.
And we just do a counter or something.
And then that actually eliminates a lot of the need for bookings.
So what I had, oh, I want to book this time.
I want to be here.
I want to call in and reserve a table versus something like a line where it might be easier
to go about that thing.
But I'm not, whatever you guys think is best, we can explore ideas.
Yeah.
I think it'd be great to maybe take a look at what we got of some early prototypes and
maybe push this out and see if we can get it deployed.
It's always a cool moment to have something just live on the internet.
Maybe we can get a preview link somewhere.
We have three directions so far.
We have this dark themed one.
And then we have this, I guess these two look very corporate, I guess.
And then the third one, I'm not a big fan of personally.
So for these prototypes, did Grokbot make this or did you use cursor?
Grokbot needed.
Okay, so that's interesting.
What's cool about this is Grokbot can actually just give you HTML in Grokbot.
And so in this case, we didn't have to deploy anything anywhere.
This is just like HTML and CSS that just is being rendered in Grokbot, which is pretty
cool.
But I think we should maybe give it some feedback, right?
Maybe we can try and adjust some of these designs.
It looks like one of your box here that's not.
Yeah, I'm going to do it some stream of consciousness again.
While you're doing that, I'm curious, we haven't got a chance to pick your brain
a lot about this particular type of business.
And I'm curious, when you think about solo print viewers or people who are creating businesses,
are there any things that you see there or things that you found to be particularly
good advice, maybe advice that we should bring forward over the next few days here?
I think one piece of advice that I've kind of realized as a solo printier is you want
to design the business to do more of what you actually enjoy doing.
Because solo printers have a lot of time.
There's certain choices they can make that can make more money, but then you end up
doing things that you don't actually enjoy doing, which kind of defuse the purpose of
being an entrepreneur.
Yeah.
And I guess, I mean, a lot of people think a lot about idea generation.
We spent a good bit of our morning today just thinking about ideas and how to find the
right idea.
I mean, you've talked with a lot of folks.
What are your takes?
Do you have any suggestions for folks on how to find the right idea?
Is it sort of the traditional stuff we've talked about, like testing stuff and seeing
what works?
How do you know what's a good idea versus a bad idea?
I do think it's about getting marketing as soon as possible, right?
Because when we were PMs, before this whole AI thing, it was all about having all these
internal debates and making all these crazy documents and then shipping something.
And then you're like, oh, nobody actually wants this.
So anything is about trying to talk to customers and get markets to know.
Trying to see if customers will actually pay.
Sometimes they might tell you, oh, this is a good idea.
This would be nice to you.
But it's just like they actually pay.
And kind of just like, and don't be too tired of your ideas.
Ideas are cheap.
But the team is important.
Yeah.
And I guess, I mean, one thing I've noticed is that it's so much easier to test
ideas now, too.
And so what do you recommend?
Is it sort of like try a bunch of things and see what works?
Or how have you thought about this?
I think it's important to, yeah, like you can see we have a landing page.
You want to make sure the landing page gets in front of the right people.
Like the people in the chat might not be the restaurateurs that we want.
Right?
But like, so you want to make sure.
But I also think it's also like just kind of aside, I think it's actually like anyone
can build anything now.
But I think it's actually hard to make money from pure software.
Awesome.
Because if you don't have a physical component or a service component, because it's just way
too easy to build some sort of SaaS or some sort of landing page now.
Like, why would I pay for this?
Why would I pay for a landing page with a database behind it?
Right, exactly.
So like really testing the market, like getting to that first dollar, which maybe
is something we should try out.
Yeah.
It's like people pay for the hard stuff, like what Grotbot suggested, which is like
actually finding a restaurateur, cooking some meals and stuff.
Like I'll pay for that.
But if you just spend the landing page, you know.
Yeah, yeah, totally.
Okay.
Well, I think we're going to try and lock in for a few minutes before our next guest
kind of hops in.
I guess, Peter, before we let you go here, thank you so much for being here and just
hanging out with us.
Yeah.
Any parting thoughts, any sort of words of advice will probably be DMing you on the
side afterwards.
So we'll definitely keep doing that, but just kind of like seeing where we are so
far and your view on just other businesses and product craft, like what you
recommend?
Yeah.
I think, well, first of all, I joined here because I really love the product.
I think not until I be too salesy, but I think this is the first product that I
used where it actually feels I'm talking to real people or like I did some sort
of people with personality, it's not just a bunch of chat threads.
So I really like it.
And I really like, I think my tip for everyone who's using RockBot is think
about how you can make these bots more proactive, right?
Like try to work with it to figure out something like maybe tracking landing
page metrics or prospecting restaurant tiers.
And then ask you to set up like some weekly crown jobs or schedule tasks to
just send you updates, right?
And I like to, some of you are learning, I like to get a format in a way where like,
hey, send me updates as a number list so that I can like respond one by one.
So like, hey, this guy is a bad idea.
And now I've set up all my bots so that like every Friday they all kind of
checking with me and I can kind of put my feedback and I think I'll go off and
do work.
Yeah.
So it just feels great.
Okay.
So what I'm hearing is hire a bunch of bot employees, get them to automate the
stuff that you don't want to spend your time on necessarily, but then maybe
get them to be proactive so that they're kind of pushing things to you versus
you having to reach out to them is that a fair summary?
Exactly.
And like a quick feature request before I go.
Okay.
First feature request.
Yeah.
Exciting.
I think it's important.
Like, like, why do you guys even have to use Slack?
Like if you can let humans jump in this interface to talk to the bots in
channels and stuff, you know, like I think the thing that kind of feels lonely
to me right now is like, I'm just talking to my bots.
I want to talk to Lauren.
I want to talk to other people, right?
And like having one collaborate with each other.
Yeah.
Maybe if it's coming soon.
Okay.
Bot collaboration.
It's in the feature queue.
Yeah.
Human bot collaboration.
We'll get it.
We'll get it logged.
I think we'll probably see some need for that as the three of us cook with
our own bot teams today.
But with that, Peter, thank you so much for hanging out with us.
All right, guys.
This has been awesome.
Thanks so much.
We will definitely see you soon.
Awesome.
Yeah.
I'll be buying some fresh files now.
See you guys.
Cool.
Yeah.
Thanks, Peter.
So for those catching up, I am making.
So I just, well, we did a couple of things.
I gave Steve some feedback on the prototypes so far.
A little bit too boring.
A little bit too bland.
And it messaged Grokpot to, oh wait, I typo'd.
It messaged Grokpot to come up with some new prototypes.
And then in parallel, I'm also asking Dr. Eggbot to make us a cracked
engineer bot.
So Grokpot's our prototyper.
And then I'm going to have an actual engineer bot to start thinking
about like tech stack, you know, how we're actually going to build things.
And I'm going to keep the prototyper for just quick throwaway prototypes.
And of course, I need help naming the bot again.
And I think we have some good ones.
Chat, I need more help.
Gimme, gimme some good suggestions.
Chat, we got to lock in.
Spud.
Spud is pretty sick.
Spud or tater?
What do you guys like?
Tater or Spud?
I still like gnocchi.
You like gnocchi?
Yeah.
I kind of like tater.
Let's do tater.
Let's go go to tater.
That's the potato override right there.
Potato gets the bot to say it.
So we have some more fun prototypes.
Oh my god.
Is this too fun?
Yeah, the designers are rolling your eyes.
This one looks kind of like a receipt, I guess.
I think one thing maybe to call out is like when Grok, so the, when we talk about like
models, there's like a model that is doing the work here.
Grok is the model.
And then there's a harness, which is the code that runs the model.
And Grokbot is very lightweight.
Like you might have heard of coding harnesses like Grok build, for example.
But Grokbot is not that.
So these are very lightweight prototypes.
And when we do more serious engineering work here, what we're going to do is connect
cursor and then we're going to kick most of the engineering work over to cursor.
And that's because the cursor harness is very good at writing code and building things.
And so as we start to build this idea, what you're going to see Lauren do is start
to rely much more heavily on cursor cloud agents.
And we'll walk through some of that stuff as well.
But that's a good way to, like, as we go from like low fidelity to high fidelity,
you'll start to see some of these products evolve.
And that's completely normal.
So.
Yeah, looks like we're making some engineering decisions too.
Yeah, I'm going to say.
Choosing some tech stack stuff.
Oh, wrong button.
Oops.
Go to Steve.
I want you to ask Tater to start thinking about our tech stack
for building out this platform.
I think we have some friends coming from Brazil and Planetscale,
maybe, spoiler alert.
So we want to probably use those options.
But in terms of other tech stack, I don't know.
I'm not too stubborn right now.
So just give us some good options.
Yeah, I kind of feel like we should let the bots just pick and get something
put together pretty quickly.
Obviously, avoid endless tech stack debates as we seek product market fit here.
Yeah.
Awesome.
And while that's working, literally all I've been doing on my screen
is writing out a notion doc.
So I know Lauren said she doesn't like notion docs.
I find it very helpful.
I find it very helpful for planning things.
So on the AV side, if we cut to my screen,
all I'm doing is defining essentially what we've agreed on this part,
which is our company name is shipped by Thursday.
And we're shipping by Thursday until we come up with a better name that
more clearly elaborates on what we're doing.
And so Lauren, I think, is the CTO here.
She's really the most technical.
You're running tech.
I think Roshan is the CPO because he's the head of product.
He knows all the product details.
He knows what we're doing.
The chief product officer.
That guy just got it from Russia.
The chief potato officer.
Lauren is the chief potato officer.
I'll also the CTO.
I'll highlight that in our company doc.
Can we get some titles?
Yeah, we need some placards.
I have some paper here.
I can't write and talk at the same time.
Lauren's going to work on some official titles here for the company.
And what we're doing is we're building a restaurant pop-up in San Francisco.
And we're going to use the experience.
Well, actually, we haven't decided it was a restaurant nut.
But we're going to build a pop-up in San Francisco for food.
We're going to use that experience to build an OS for running pop-ups
and this meta product.
And so our goal is to create a business that
allows us to do more of what we enjoy doing, which is bringing people together.
And so in this doc, I'm just saying this is coming together really quickly.
So we need to bias moving fast and getting stuff done.
And there's a bunch of stuff we need to figure out.
So I'm going to kick this over to all the rock bots I used to say,
at least have the context of what we're doing.
And the main thing I want to do is keep that context consistent.
Because as we bring guests in this show,
I have to explain to the guests what we're doing.
I also have to explain to my rock bots what we're doing.
So yeah, we're cooking.
And I think we might even have another guest coming on pretty soon.
Are you our CEO?
I guess.
Somebody has to do it.
You can be the grown up.
Oh my gosh.
Wait, what is the E, central executive?
I'm sorry.
Oh my gosh.
Outstanding.
Chief Tater Officer.
Chat is crazy.
This is a.
You know, I was talking with like some of the...
Here you go. A very official nameplate.
Thank you. What do I do with this? Like, what do I...
What's your Twitter handle?
Fold it out. Roshan underscore S.
Roshan.
Lauren, what do I do with this?
I don't know. Just like stick it somewhere.
We're gonna... We'll work on that. We'll work on that offline.
Yeah, we'll work on that offline.
And then I'm told the team is working on bringing in a virtual guest.
Ooh.
But yeah, I mean, if you want to cut to my screen,
we can start doing some like playing here.
I like to plan things out. I like to prototype things.
I love it. Thank you. Thanks, Lauren.
Very important. Titles.
We'll have to get those tinted up and properly made.
I did some origami. Does this work?
Lauren, the chat has noticed that you have an update available in the Grok Bot app.
Oh, man. We'll save updates for when we're...
I don't know if I'm brave enough to do that on stream.
We'll do that after. We'll do that in between the break.
How fast the team ships, it's kind of crazy.
Ooh.
We have a few more colours. I don't know.
Maybe we don't have to make it look that good.
Like, OK. CEO, please.
Make an executive decision right now.
I mean, prototypes don't matter too much. Let's go with pink.
I'm like feeling a little crazy.
Night market pink. Let's just do that.
We're gonna roll with that. And then, you know,
these don't matter so much in my mind.
So like, let's move fast on this
and eventually we'll get cursor cloud agents hooked up
and we'll find some design help somewhere out there.
Yeah. Hey, design bot. We gotta get a design in your bot.
I feel like that's gonna be really great.
Just a level set for the folks watching
and kind of maybe for our team here what's gonna happen in the next few minutes.
We're gonna have a guest joining us in two minutes.
I think what we'll try and do is maybe get some builds going in the meantime.
So what do you guys think we should kick off?
I think it might be great to like kick off some cloud agents
to get some front-end and back-end stubbed out.
Should we like get some code in a repo?
I guess, Lauren, what do you think we should maybe kick off
and we can kind of build while we're talking,
chatting with our guests and make some progress here.
Yeah. Do you want to set up the GitHub repo?
Yeah, I just made one actually and put it in Slack
but it's just popup.git can share that if you have it.
So this is our Slack.
Yeah, it's our Slack channel.
Well, look at my name.
I should probably set a real name.
Lauren, chief, potato, officer.
I'll put a picture later. Where is it?
Should be right there.
So we got our, I should probably zoom in too.
Okay, so let's try and get the landing page built
and pushed through this repo.
And then start figuring out how we can host it.
Do we want to buy a domain name right now?
I think I have a Vercel account set up.
So maybe we try with like a test account
and we can always grab a domain
once we know we want to call this thing.
All right, sounds good.
You know what, I'm going to ask Steve to ask,
kind of give us some domain names.
Yeah, that's a good idea too.
Or we could get, we have like a marketing bot.
Maybe we hire a marketing bot.
We should hire a marketing bot to think about,
like how we should brand things, name things
and coordinate with our design team.
Since you're the chief product officer,
do you want to figure out the domain name?
Yeah.
I'll generate a few,
but I don't know if I'm very good at naming things,
as you can probably imagine.
Well, most of the more things,
we just start to get stuff up.
So like, yeah, let's start ripping.
Yeah.
Cool.
In the meantime,
marketing bot cooking right now,
so we can, and what's going to be great,
I think once we get some code into a repo
is that all of our bots can start making PRs against it.
As we can kind of all evolve.
Give me your name plate.
Evolve together.
This is important to me.
Thank you.
We got it.
We got, oh no, my name plate fell over.
These are the important parts of running a company.
We'll get some more official ones.
The team is working on the infrastructure here.
Yeah, yeah, this is like company building extra set.
Okay, we got some, we have some ideas.
I don't know if I like them.
Oh, what?
Oh, that's actually pretty fun.
We have claim the stall.com,
stall.run, nightmarket.app,
popup.place, openstall.code,
peanutpopup, that's kind of cute,
peanutpopup.com,
popedo.com, and hostapopup.com.
I don't know if I like any of these.
Do we have a notion doc that's sort of like our first state?
Do we have a VersaL account already?
Can you add me to it?
Yes, I can.
I'm going to send you the company doc version.
Oh, great.
Yeah, I want to feed that to my bot
so they have context on what we're building.
It's very bare bones.
I like to, I like to buy us,
like even if we cut over to my screen,
like I think simpler is better.
And if we think about like,
all of the stuff that goes into AI,
the more information you give it,
the more it's going to like lean on that information.
So if you give it a bunch of bad information,
you're going to need a bunch of bad outputs.
And so what we want to think through is like,
hey, how do we give the simple,
most concise description of what we're working on to AI?
Oh yeah.
And that's what I'm trying to do here.
So send that doc over erosion
and we're going to keep moving through it.
Cool, cool, cool.
What's the best email for you, Lauren?
You should have one.
It's the one in my Slack profile.
Okay, let me grab that.
Members, I'll make you an admin on this.
Do we have cursors set up in here?
We should add the cursor bot.
Oh yeah, we definitely should.
We're going to need some...
In our Slack.
Okay.
Copy email address.
Okay, Lauren, I'm adding you as an owner
to our Vercel organization.
Okay.
And I have not set up Vercel on the repo yet.
So as soon as you have a repo,
we'll probably want to hook some stuff up and...
Oh wait, I thought you were setting up the repo?
We have a repo, but it's an empty one.
Oh, okay, okay.
I can...
I think...
Oh, there we go.
Sorry, sorry.
Sorry, like...
Oh yeah, there it is.
Okay.
Steve did it while we were talking.
I love it.
Okay.
Well, while we're waiting for our guest to show up,
why don't we do some work here?
I don't know.
Yeah, it looks like we're switching.
Great.
We got some screens up.
Extremely scrappy.
That's our platform.
It's an index, not HTML,
but that is more than we had when we started.
So let's see here.
Wait, there's not...
The styles are all in line.
Okay, amazing.
I love that.
Yeah, let's...
This is super scrappy, but...
I'm going to just go ahead and get Vercel
connected up to the repo here.
Hit the deploy button.
Yeah, I need to authorize my Vercel.
Configuring GitHub here.
Get my email.
Cool.
Okay, yeah, I see our pop-up repo.
Okay, I need to...
All right, we should get some deploys going soon here.
Oh, I need to sign up for an account first.
Signing up.
So yeah, while Lauren's signing up for some accounts,
I'm working on creating a couple bots on my side.
I feel like we just need to start cranking through some things here.
So I'm working on an ops bot and a creative director.
The creative director, I'm thinking,
is going to help me with naming, high-level details,
some of these other things.
And then the ops bot, I just need to start doing stuff.
So I'm setting up Slack, I'm getting some other things cooking.
It's like everything you do running a company.
This is like, obviously what we're doing is super exciting stuff.
Humans have to do this stuff, right?
And we're going to start to move towards automating
some of that as well.
But yeah, I think it's really just cranking.
Let's see.
Oh, I thought I added you.
There's a pending invitation for you.
How do I...
It might be in your email.
I'll check.
I can also see if I can invite you by link.
Oh, I see it.
Awesome.
How am I going to do this?
Can I hide my screen for a second?
Yeah, can we cut the screen, please, on the AV side?
I can stop streaming.
Yeah, you can cut that.
That's fine.
Oh, no.
That was my face.
Oh, my goodness.
Don't worry about it.
They got us covered over there.
Okay, okay.
We are down on the stream.
Oh, my goodness.
Oh, no.
Can somebody else stream?
Yeah, I think I can hop in.
I got it.
Little stream rescue here.
Don't worry.
I need to.
I mean, I'm also streaming.
I just don't think that they're picking up the ball.
Oh, no.
Don't worry about it.
We're alive on my soul.
A bit of technical difficulty right now.
Okay, so I'm connecting notion here.
And we have...
All right, we're back.
You can see us.
All right.
Yeah, we are still cooking.
Okay, okay.
I'm off now.
Okay, let's see how we're doing on our deploys.
I see a deploy, guys.
Oh, man.
All right, hold on.
Oh, did you deploy it already?
I deployed.
Nice.
We have deploys running on main,
so just push to main and...
Hop up orphan omega.versa.com.
There we go.
There you go.
Wait, but I guess right now it doesn't do anything.
It's just an HTML page.
We need it to go somewhere.
Yes, we need Google Analytics.
Should we just collect these in a Google Sheet somewhere?
Like, where do you want to collect our emails?
I think that sounds good.
Yeah, but will it be easy to connect Google?
Maybe we should just dump things into a...
Oh, yeah.
Like a...
We could just use a notion database.
Yeah, we have the notion MTP setup, right?
I don't know if notion is going to be able to handle the load from everyone.
Dump into a flat file database.
Okay, I just connected my Versailles account as well.
Cool.
Awesome.
Okay, then I'm going to ask Steve.
I'm going to say, okay, Steve.
We've deployed the landing page already,
but obviously we need to connect the landing page
to actually store the signups somewhere.
So for now, could you connect it to Notion
and make a little notion database for us?
And then I guess you'll need to add me to the notion.
Yes.
And by for...
In the meantime, I guess we should start looking at the tech stack choices.
Host, undersell.
Yes, makes sense.
App.
Actually, maybe crazy idea.
Like what if we just integrated planet scale right now?
Should we just go straight to the real database?
Because I guess if we do a quick task,
we're going to have to rip it out later, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, let's do that, actually.
That might be cool.
Once we get it wired up, then we're kind of off to the races.
I wonder if that makes sense.
I do want Postgres instead.
So let me say a small tweak.
Let's use planet scale Postgres instead.
Payments later, that's true.
Must have...
Nice to have...
Yeah, we don't need any of these nice to have stuff.
And we...
Okay.
I'll just give a feedback on this plan.
And then I'm going to go back to Steve and say,
connect it to planet scale.
I'm going to need to be added to that too.
Oh, yeah.
Let me...
I think we have a planet scale org set up somewhere, right?
We're working on that.
We can reach out to the planet scale team this morning.
So I think we should look somewhere.
Let me get it out.
I'm not sharing screen right now.
Okay, sweet.
Yeah, we'll get the planet scale stuff cooking.
Thanks.
Shout out planet scale team.
I think we might have some guests from planet scale in the next couple days.
So team rolling with it.
Sweet, sweet.
And for those, we're figuring out how to get this screen sharing back up.
But for now, just to give you a picture,
if you're just joining the chat of what's happening,
we have an ops team cooking over here with Matt,
putting together a company playbook
and making sure we have a go to market motion.
We have an early landing page prototype that is just some HTML.
We're leaning towards a pop-up business or a pop-up platform
where we make it easy to run pop-ups.
And maybe we run our own pop-up too.
And we have Lauren cooking up some integration work.
I think currently working on getting our database set up.
That's the recap.
You know what?
I'm going to say, yeah, I need the planet scale account.
And then I can tell it to set it up for us.
Planet scale is we have accounts,
shout out to the planet scale team.
So we'll be good on that.
And we can keep moving there.
Cool.
Planet scale.
Let me find the invite and get it set up.
I think we still need a domain name, right?
We still need a domain name.
I got my creative director.
Let's-
We can also just have chat.
Chat.
Give us some ideas for our domain name.
We need some fun, cool domain names.
And also we need to start-
We need to screen share again, I think.
Ooh, I wonder if ship by Thursday.com is open.
Is that domain open?
Sure.
By Thursday.
Yeah, unless someone sniped it from us in the chat.
I should stop.
You should probably, if you want to, buy the domain right now.
Yeah, we might be able to buy it through Vercel
and just have it tied directly to our project.
Cool.
I'm hearing that our next guest unfortunately won't be able to make it.
So you're just going to get more time with us building.
I mean, we're kind of busy.
You got to cook here, man.
I feel like we're falling behind.
Sweet, yeah.
I'm going to say-
Okay.
And hopefully we can get more-
So I'm still reading on the unscalable credentials.
But I guess try to unblock yourself as much as possible
and think about the table design and maybe set up some dependencies for us.
But just unblock us while we wait for a planet scale.
Can we turn that off?
No?
I think we're showing the wrong screen right now.
Sweet.
All right, we're good.
We have Vercel accounts, right?
Yes.
Well, I don't know if I've invited you yet, but let me do that.
Okay, that's it.
We'll get there.
What?
You're using the email for your same email you sent?
I'll use my- I can use my personal.
We have no screen on.
I'll select you my personal.
Okay, and then by the way, Steve, I want you to tell Tater to use cloud agents going forward.
Maybe make a project agent.
So yeah, for those of you watching,
Grokbot is a really powerful tool for orchestrating bots and obviously automating a lot of things.
And then Cursor's harness is really good for coding.
So one thing that I like to do is to have Grokbot basically spin up cloud agents for me.
And cloud agents are agents that run on Cursor's harness.
So it has all of the smarts and the engineering know-how built into the harness
and Grokbot can manage them for you.
So we can actually do all of our engineering work in Grokbot,
even though we're using Cursor cloud agents.
And also the nice thing about Cursor cloud agents is that they run in the cloud and they also have
their own virtual machine.
They can test our application.
They can click around.
They can take CPU traces, all that good stuff.
And so we can do that natively right here in Grokbot.
All you need to do is tell your bot to spawn a cloud agent.
And it can also, if you have an existing repo, you can tell it to help you set up your environment
so that your cloud agents actually know how to bring up your application and run it in the cloud.
So what I've done so far is I've told our engineer bot, Tater,
maybe I will give it a title.
Can I still give it a title?
Maybe not.
The label maybe?
I don't think we can add a label.
But OK, so Tater is going to use cloud agents now.
And you can see that it's created a new project for us.
And a project is a little hard to describe.
I guess it's like a special kind of cloud agent that is better, is really good for long projects.
So I'm telling you to spin one up and we'll use that to keep track of all of the technical
engineering context that we have for our application.
And just whenever it needs to do more engineering work, it just sends more messages to the project.
But we'll see how that goes.
Maybe we won't do a project.
We'll see.
Do we have the planet scale credentials?
Yeah, I'm working on that.
Let's see here.
I mean, we can run it locally too.
We're still waiting on the planet scale credentials.
So maybe let's for now do all of our development, I guess somewhat locally, on either your cloud
machine or in the cloud agents machine.
And come back to me with a video or a screenshot.
And we'll worry about deploying it later.
And on my end, we now own the domain shipbythurs.day.
I like it.
We're going to get some stuff going on there.
Oh, do you want to wire that up to our deploy so people can start looking at the...
It's on Vercel.
So I was going to get a company lander.
We need the shipbythursday company lander.
And then the product, I think, can go to an actual product domain.
So shipbythursday is going to be the main site that we're...
The org.
It's our company.
It's the beta.
It's the company behind the company.
And then we're going to start working on actual...
We need a product name.
Yep.
What is this going to be called?
We can work on that.
We got plenty of time.
We need a legal working title.
I don't know.
I didn't know what to call it.
So now I'm also...
Because we have a domain, I need to deploy some code to it for our company lander.
And what I'm working on is using Dr. Eggbot to install our cursor team kit,
a bunch of other skills, P-stack, and then connecting that to our cursor cloud agents.
When we have that ready to go, I'll be able to start writing code to get that up there for y'all.
And maybe making things look nice.
But yeah, we're just hacking, right?
So you're here with us as we're building the company.
We really got a lot of stuff.
We got too much stuff going on.
We have so much things to get to build.
But that's kind of part of it.
That's the fun.
So...
All right.
I see Steve has made a mistake because he has opened the pull request.
And I'm going to say, new rule, no pull requests we ship to Maine for now
until somebody yells at me.
All right.
There we go.
Okay.
Let's see what it opened anyway for the pull request.
It's got, wow, 2,000 lines.
I'm not going to read all that.
So one thing I would like to do as well for my setup is to start thinking about the
engineering workflows.
So we have Tater, who is our engineering bot.
But I also want a bot that is like a reviewer, I suppose.
So I'm going to tell Steve.
And we're actually going to cut to a hold screen briefly.
And we're going to come right back.
And Lauren's going to pick up with the factory creation.
So we'll be right back.
And we'll be right back on some technical difficulties.
I'm going to make a new channel called...
High level.
We're just getting started building our company.
So we are kicking off our first agents.
I'm working on like a lander for our company.
And I can actually see in cursor some of the other agents that my team is working on.
And we have a guest.
We have a guest.
Cody, hello.
Thanks for joining us.
What's going on?
It's fun watching you guys build live.
Just business buying and selling marketplace online.
And then we help people scale businesses through our advisory business.
And then if you've seen the app on X or the internet,
I think there are about 15 million people that follow us online.
So we're on the interwebs all the time talking about stuff like this.
That's awesome.
And I know you've been using Grokbot a little bit, or at least your team has.
I'm curious.
How's that been?
What have you been using it for?
Maybe share some of your favorite.
It's going to be very useful.
So I thought I'd show you a couple things that we're doing.
I think you could maybe see my screen share live.
Can you see something that looks like a dashboard with a book on it with 135,000 users on it?
Can you guys see that?
Wow. We see it.
We see it.
Yes.
Okay.
Anyway, so basically what this is, is we're launching a book this week in two days.
And it's a little bit like a product launch.
You can kind of see we're tracking.
We built this with a mixture, a little bit of Grok.
This is located on Vercel and basically tracks real-time attendees.
And then if we could scroll down, I didn't know what our capability was going to be on here.
You could see what's paid versus organic.
What channels are tracking above?
What's our average CAC to average order value for each of the people who come in?
And so since we talk a lot on the internet and build these products,
I thought we could show you some of the things that help us build.
So that Vercel is one of them.
Maybe the other thing that would be useful.
I don't know if you guys can see something now that looks like a dashboard.
This is Pulse.
This is where you see that.
Okay, cool.
So this is how we build businesses.
So, you know, of those companies and pitch.
And so they don't know how once they get somebody's eyeballs on it to pitch well.
And so then you put together a plan based on your lowest profit level.
So anyway, I'm not sure if that is useful or how to, let's stop sharing.
But those are a couple of things we actually built with AI Live.
And then we built a device on how we should think about that.
And how to figure out what business in particular you want to start
or what's your biggest problem?
I mean, a good question will always give you the best answer.
Fair enough.
Well, I think we have an idea that we think might make sense.
How do we get some validation for it maybe?
Yeah.
And so if you haven't been following along,
like our idea is like we're going to run a restaurant pop-up.
So we're going to need to connect a restaurant tour with guests who want to experience that.
We're going to find a location and do some of those things.
And then through that process, we're going to turn that into a piece of software
that we'd like to sell to people as well.
Okay.
And so the biggest issue now, theoretically,
you're going to be able to do licensing, pop-up location, leasing,
you know, all of those logistics.
We're like, we've got that figured out.
But we got to make sure that we get lots of seats and people actually show up.
Is that right?
I mean, yeah, we're going to focus on the ops first.
And then we're going to reach out to legal and like figure out how to make
all that other stuff work.
Okay.
And so you do want users or you want to focus on getting the leasing.
Basically what I would say to you is like, my belief is always before you even decide
what business you want to build, you should see if you can sell it to three people.
You know, unless, especially for like a restaurant pop-up,
you guys aren't going to get venture capital funding from that.
Like what?
Only two out of 2000 companies gets VC.
So that's all good.
It's a good business.
But what I would probably do is I would be obsessing on how to get distribution.
Obviously, 430,000 people on here.
You have a super unfair advantage.
But let's pretend like that wasn't the case.
What would I do?
Want, I think, X is an incredible place to do it.
I guess I have like a couple of thoughts on there, which is one.
And you know, the man, the man himself doesn't seem to be bothered by this.
But I think a little controversy is okay.
I actually pulled up some of my most, let's call it my most controversial tweets.
So you guys can see those for when I get yelled at on the internet.
So basically, I would play around with your controversial tweets.
So like this one here, I don't know if anybody saw it online.
It's like, do everything in your power to move to Austin.
It's basically an AI-generated video.
This was made with Higgs Field.
I think it probably took an hour and a half.
And we got roasted on the internet about this because there's a scene where there's somebody
with a surfboard in it in Austin.
But if you look at the view count, who cares?
Because you can see 2.4 million views.
I was trying to get people to come and apply.
So we have a portfolio of a bunch of businesses and I wanted them to apply.
We received hundreds of people applying and then you can see in the comments hundreds more
sharing it.
And so I think the first thing, if I was you, I'd be playing around with like what's controversy.
What do you guys believe that other people don't?
And like, yeah, I think you guys should make an X account for sure.
I also think one of the other things you should think about is what is going to make people
talk?
Like we did this other one where people were really mad because we said don't do paid
ads to start your business, which I stand by.
But we made it slightly hyperbolic in like don't do ads until you hit five or ten million.
So people lost their minds.
You know, you're an idiot, Cody.
How could you think that?
Every business needs ads, right?
But it got a bunch of people talking and what I really wanted to do was get people to the
book launch.
And so that one got like 5.7 million views and I believe signed up 2,000 users.
So it's cheap.
So I would start that for you guys.
So like what's your little bit of controversy you can do?
That's really good advice.
Actually, and it's funny you mentioned the ads because we definitely were thinking about
running ads and I guess that would that would have maybe maybe we should reconsider
that advice.
Yeah.
Well, it depends.
Like do you want to I think the problem with ads right up front are you don't really know
your target persona.
Like you don't exactly know who you want to go after.
You have to spend money then to make it.
If you're not getting funding already, why would you do that?
And three, you can put your ad spend behind something once you know that organic works.
So like why put ad spend behind bad ads because you don't know what good looks like
yet until you've done them on X.
That's at least basically how we've grown almost all of our businesses to start.
Then once you know what good organic looks like and who your perfect persona is, you
could throw a bunch of dollars on top of it, which is what we do.
That makes a ton of sense.
Yeah.
Well, we should I feel like we should be recording this or feeding it into a rock
box that we can use it to run the next phase of our business.
Well, you could also like take the top performing tweets from everybody like me who markets
a lot online and feed it at your rock bot and then just feed your rock bot.
Hey, we're trying to achieve X result.
You can connect tweet hunter to X, have it feed all the top Twitter posts and then say
pull me the top 15, like steal the frame, not the exact verbiage.
And then retweet them.
Yeah, I really like that.
I wanted to go back to something you asked earlier.
We're kind of sharing some contrarian takes and kind of leaning into that.
I'm curious, like what's the worst business advice that you've heard given to businesses?
Because I think, you know, obviously we're going to have a lot of folks on.
They're all going to hopefully give us A plus advice, but it's also good to know
what to avoid.
And so I'm curious, just like, yeah, what's the worst advice you've heard and what are
the things that we should be aware of there?
Yeah, I mean, the advice that I heard in the beginning and followed was hire a players
and get out of their way.
It sounds really nice.
I think you could say the same thing with bots.
Like, yeah, just let your bots run, get out of the way.
You guys know firsthand because we run a bunch of them here too.
You can't really do that.
You have to be constantly iterating and overseeing.
And so I don't know how many people on here run single person businesses as opposed to
multi person businesses.
But you know, we have 150 employees in this company.
And the only time we almost ran out of money completely was I followed that advice.
And so I think if you're going to hire great people, you have to oversee them intensely.
We say hire great people, be really clear on what you want, incentive align them to make
sure every dollar that they make is tied to a dollar that you made, and then have an operational
oversight.
So with rock, you could probably build a little bit of a prototype like we do, where you can
track what is my cash on cash return?
What is my AOV?
What is my LTV?
And if you're going to hire a marketer, track all of that to their actual incentive
aligned goals, which is what I would do.
That's awesome.
Yeah, I feel like there's so much that gets shared conventionally.
And I'm curious for your take on this as well.
You mentioned earlier we have a bunch of folks watching the stream.
Thank you to everyone who's tuning in, obviously, like really heartening to see the audience
here.
And you've built some pretty incredibly large businesses and marketplaces.
And I'm just curious for your thoughts on sort of distribution and if distribution is
a moat.
I think you've talked a little bit about this in your posts as well recently on X.
Yeah, I would love to know like kind of your general thoughts there.
Any advice for us as we build, but also just some general takes.
I mean, first of all, overall, like, yeah, I mean, people hate that take.
They hate the idea that distribution is a moat.
And then, you know, I was talking to Jack Dorsey in the XDM's and I think he's one
of the OGs that says it actually really, really is, especially in this world where
products getting easier and easier to build.
I think, you know, if we invested at Contouring Thinking Capital, I think we've
done 36 investments today.
We see a lot of AI investments.
And the number one reason they don't make it is because they don't have
distribution. So it's not popular.
People won't like it, except that's what matters to get funding.
So and then, you know, for most businesses, you need cash flow and you need
distribution because you'll you won't get funding.
So you're going to need your your cash flow to fund it.
So I would say, like, obsess on that.
And I don't think enough startup founders do that.
And so in the beginning, it's all about building product or even these days,
people say they're building it in stealth.
You guys are doing the opposite because you're building in public, which we do
too. But then I think maybe the only other thing I'll show you guys is like
I would nobody believes anything.
Right. So you have to have proof.
So we like to share on X.
You know, there are always going to be people that don't like you.
There will be people that don't think that you're doing a good job.
And there will be people that just like don't want to see you win.
And so I hope you guys are taking screenshots of all the stuff you're
building with rock right now, because you'll want it in like six months when
this works and you'll want to show like your user growth from day one.
You're going to actually we have something called a proof vault.
I highly recommend it, which is like every single thing somebody said about
your product that's good ever.
And then we break it down from like testimonials to video views, to
screenshots, to recently added proof to has it been verified or not?
Is this like publicly allowed to be shared?
Because eventually people will want to know all of that.
Makes a lot of sense.
If you're open to it, actually, we'd love to do a bit of an interactive
exercise and maybe help to kind of work with you to maybe create a bot
together and kind of prompted initially and kind of take some of the advice
that you share with us and turn it into something we can use for our
business. Is that sound like it'd be fun?
Let's do it. All right.
Let's see. Can we get maybe Matt, my screen up on the stream?
If not, then maybe we just work in the background here and we'll share
the results afterwards.
OK, so this is my screen as your screen.
Maybe you can walk us through what we're doing here.
Let's do it. Cody, we're going to create a bot.
And honestly, I think we'd really benefit from sort of the marketing
and distribution side of things, because we're kind of flying a little
bit blind there. And so, yeah, I would love your suggestions on how
we might start prompting and Matt, I guess, if we create a new bot,
maybe we can give it a name.
Yeah, let's start a new bot.
Let's start first with what do you want it to do?
You know, before we build anything, we got to ask ourselves, what's the
number one thing that needs to be done in the business in order to
make money or get users or what's our number one goal?
Is it getting leads?
Is it getting people to pay and sign up?
What's the goal that we need to hit?
Yeah, so, you know, to start, we're going to try this pop up experience.
So I think you made a good point, which is like, hey, we want to get
three people maybe that would be willing to pay us to prove out that
this is a good idea. So it could be leads.
It could just be a sign up form where we start collecting emails
with people that are interested and then we try to collect our first
sign ups from that group.
It could I think getting the word out or trying to broadcast
what we're doing is maybe a good start.
Yeah, I like it. I always like captured audience.
So that's probably where I'd start.
I think you're you're nailing it with emails because then you can
always come back to them.
You probably are not going to have your like everything isn't set up
right now is that you don't have the ability to click to purchase,
you know, connected to a reservation system to click to reserve a spot.
None of that yet, right?
Exactly. This is correct.
OK, so I would start with lead magnets in particular.
You already are good at X.
Almost everybody on here is probably playing on X.
So I would start with a really good lead magnet.
I think usually when we go to start a business, we go imitate,
iterate, innovate.
So who who already has this type of business that you want that's done it well?
OK, do you have any market knowledge?
Yeah, I have no market knowledge of pop ups, as a matter of fact.
And that's that's a good point to bring up. Yeah.
OK, well, I would run a separate bot on that.
Go find what city you're going to do it in San Francisco.
OK, well, you're going to have a lot of empty empty restaurants in there.
So that'll work out fine.
So you're saying basically what we should be doing is like background research
on other businesses that have done the same thing.
Exactly.
Like if you haven't done this before, go try to figure out who the best person
is that's already doing it and reverse engineer what they're doing.
So that would the very first spot I would make would probably be that,
like pull me all the top restaurant tours in San Francisco
and then grab me five of the best websites,
then give me the five best pop up pages on their websites,
then give me the five best pop up restaurants done in any major city
in the last six or 12 months,
then put those all into a document so that you can see them.
And then you're probably going to want to figure out how should we actually
like what is your branding and what's your differentiation here?
Do we know anything about how you're going to position this pop up?
Awesome. Yeah, no. And I'm tracking here.
So I'm using we have a basically a bot that can create other bots.
This is something Lauren has educated us on.
And I'm saying, hey, we need to operate a research bot
and kind of took some cliff notes on what you said there.
I'm going to say, hey, go find the top San Francisco restaurant tours,
the best sites for those restaurant tours, similar pop ups and similar companies
and then use our sort of like founding document in notion as grounding.
I like that because I've been taking some notes here on like
just the general sort of like, hey, what are we trying to do here?
What is the goal?
So that bottle be grounded in our business.
And so hopefully, Cody, thank you for the tip there.
This is a good way for us to understand what we're getting into,
because usually it's like sometimes when I approach problems like this,
even in writing code, it's like somebody's probably done this before.
Right. And so if we can start from what everybody else has tried
and maybe failed at, we can give ourselves a bit of a head start.
Yeah. Plus your storytelling in the beginning.
So like really what you want to do, you're going to have to sell the dream
in anything you do before you even get the lease or anything else,
especially if you want to get it for free.
So if you want to get free things to test your idea before having to pay for it,
then you've got to sell why somebody should help you out.
So I think what you're trying to do here is and I might just because I have some
context, if you do, you know, anybody who's building
hopefully isn't picking a random thing, throwing something at it
with a couple ideas and building, you know, typically you're going to want
to have lived the problem for a minute.
But you might want to put in here how would the best restaurateurs
like Danny Meyer position a pop up just like he did with Shaq Shaq
in the very beginning?
How can we replicate that?
And then you might say, what would a killer landing page
with a one line title hook and then some sort of exclusivity,
scarcity, timeliness and relevance like the four reasons people do anything?
What would those be for this?
And I would feed that all into something that'll give you a bunch of outputs.
And this is perfect for quote unquote controversy.
Like what would make people talk about this?
In San Francisco, it's probably something.
I mean, maybe it's an AI restaurant pop up cafe.
Maybe you riff on why claw bots like why claw bot meetups went so viral
in San Francisco with the little, you know, lobster hats.
How do we replicate that?
What would be a different version of it?
We have some cute rock bot logos maybe that we bring into it.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You could. My only thing on logos, though, is that's about you, not about them.
So everything you sell, like that's good for your boss and grok.
But for the user, it's like what is actually going to make them want
to participate in that if you know, that's why like you'll see on our ads.
So I think we spent a couple of million dollars in ads for this book launch
up until this week, which is going down in two days.
And the ads where it's overly corporate, like our logo is all over it.
Those perform at about 40 percent the rate of non corporate ads.
Like our best performing ads are me and my husband talking to each other
or us inside of our business or literally one with our dog in it.
So, yeah, so if you're building ads, really important.
Is that fair? Yeah, less corporate, the better.
Less produced these days, the better.
We did a couple of ads that are really overly produced.
No bueno, which is good for for solopreneur building builders.
You don't have to have a big production to do this.
I love that. I love that.
Maybe one sort of thought here.
And I'm kind of thinking maybe what we should do is like put together
a marketing plan and kick off a bot to help us take all this advice
and like write us a plan.
So maybe we could do that.
But I'm curious for like maybe a last piece of advice from you, Cody,
around traditional businesses.
And this is something you've obviously done extensive work on.
It's sort of like, how do you help traditional businesses and kind of like,
you know, enable those businesses with a I kind of help them grow,
embrace new technology?
You know, obviously, we're thinking about something that's a pop up,
which in many ways relates to traditional restaurateurs
or traditional businesses themselves.
And yeah, I'm just curious for your general thoughts on like tech enabling
tech enablement for those types of businesses.
And, you know, maybe the components that you've seen work best or not work best.
So we're not too over our skis or the whole thing.
But yeah, we just love your general advice here.
And maybe we could be that into our bot and like come up with a marketing plan.
I don't know. Yeah, sure.
I think we're working that we're working towards that. OK.
That's good. Yeah.
I mean, well, let's see.
So we've brought in like 1600 businesses over the past two years,
predominantly home services, professional services,
some online businesses as well.
But almost all of them, they do a ranking in the beginning.
When they come to us, almost all of them are not using AI anywhere
near as intensely as as the people who are on here.
They're googling chat, GPT for things.
So the cool part about what you guys are doing is you're going to be light
years ahead of most small businesses.
So that's one.
I guess if I was thinking about how to use AI,
I always think Charlie's Munger says like invert, always invert.
I would definitely start from where can you make small businesses cash?
Because a lot of people are trying to sell them AI services
that don't relate to revenue, but the average small business
multiple is 15 percent.
So they don't have a lot of cash typically.
So if you can't tie it to an immediate revenue stream,
you're probably not going to sell your AI services very well.
So that's just one thought.
But if you can do something like we're talking right now
about how to market the bot that you're doing and how to spin it up,
I might do something like this, like for instance.
So like what data do you guys have that's unique?
So if you're in this this pop up and you have rock,
maybe you're pulling together a list of all the users who are on here
who are interested in AI in the area and you're you're you did some sort
of survey on them and you're going to give it to everybody
who signs up for the restaurant and they get like a free dish or something
when you come for ours.
Like our lead magnet is, hey, we've analyzed 15000 small business owners.
We actually used tech.
We didn't use rock for this one.
This is a mixture of Claude Vercel and Repplet.
But to come up with a survey that actually delivers something
to the to the user that makes them feel like they're getting more value
than you are for their email.
This one in particular kind of tells you what kind of business owner
you are, for instance.
So I would think about for you, instead of just trying to get emails for signups,
how can you give them something that's like so valuable?
They almost they feel like the value switch is so hard.
They wouldn't give it.
They wouldn't feel bad giving you their email.
And then we posted it on X, too, so you can see it.
And you start like I would just do this with like five or six things
you could spin up a lead magnet probably in five minutes
and have it be geared to what you know specifically posted on the Internet.
People will want the thing that you're talking about
and then sign up to your restaurant.
And that's what I would do.
Got it. So to recap, it sounds like focus on the revenue dynamic.
Just give in the business and think of, you know, technology and data
more as an empowering capability.
Is that is that maybe a fair summary?
I know there's a lot a lot more there than my two sentence recap.
But yeah, I just I mean, you're in business to make money at the end of the day, right?
Like nobody does this for charity.
So I think if you always start with first principle
that you want your business to actually drive revenue,
then you're going to do the things that will keep you alive forever.
And so that's why I'm like, go back to like, what are your leads?
How are you capturing them?
Can you make your leads money?
Can you give your lead something that's 10 X more valuable
than what you're asking for for them?
And if you can do that continuously, it'll be hard for you to to lose or be poor.
Yeah, amazing. Sounds really good.
I mean, this is all stuff we never would have been able to go on.
So we're making progress and I'm super excited to to keep building some of this stuff.
Cody, any parting thoughts for us?
I know you've been incredibly generous with your time and this has been really helpful.
We're going to definitely go and throw a bot at the transcript
and get this marketing plan working.
But yeah, any any parting thoughts for us or for the folks listening in
before we kind of switch back into build mode here?
No, I think you guys are doing something really cool.
Just remember, you know, businesses is there for you to profit off of it.
Otherwise, it's way too fucking hard and it takes too long and it's pretty miserable.
And the only way that it ends up being fun is is for you to succeed and make revenue and capital.
And so I think that's the only thing I sometimes see with builders is they'll build a lot of cool stuff.
But if you build it, I promise you they will not come.
All right. Well, the Cody Sanchez, thank you so much for spending time with us.
This has been incredible.
Learned a ton.
And obviously we need to go focus on making money, it sounds like.
Yeah, helping other people make money, too, maybe.
I think so. Yeah. So thank you so much again.
I think we're going to take a short break.
We're going to get some things sort of on our side, maybe like five minutes.
We'll be back really soon.
And then we're going to show you guys what we've been up to, what we're going to start building.
Yeah, hopefully we'll have the landing page up.
All right. Yeah. See you all soon. Yeah.
Test, test. We're ready to start. Okay. Everyone hear us okay? I think we are back.
Awesome. We're back. We're live. Thanks so much for joining in. What we're going to do is we're going
to give you a quick recap. We've been just hacking on things a little bit here. We've got about five
minutes until our next session starts, and that is Grok Bot for engineering, which should be a good
one. But in the meantime, what we did this morning was we did some market research. We looked over
Twitter and got all of the ideas you all suggested for a restaurant. We aligned on kind of what we're
going to build. We talked to Peter Yang and also Cody, who helped us learn a little bit more about
Go to Market, about what we're building. And then our focus from here on out really is just going
to be building stuff. So I think we're going to focus mostly on showing Lauren, showing Potato,
doing her thing after the engineering session and just showing what we can build. But the
idea we lined up with is a pop-up for a restaurant, a pop-up experience in San Francisco. So our goal
is going to be to connect basically a restaurant to a bunch of people that want to eat food
and have an experience. And through creating that experience, we'll have some sort of software.
And so the product, ideally at the end of the three days, will be both an operating system,
a product for creating these sorts of experiences, but then the experience itself.
And I think that's what we're going to push for, right? Yeah, I think that sounds...
It's ambitious, but we'll try our best. Yeah, yeah. And I wonder if there's a way we can make it
some fun too. Like add some, maybe some... I don't know, we'll play with it. Maybe we can make the
booking experience more than just a traditional booking experience. But I'll save the crazy
ideas for day two. Awesome. Well, I mean, in the meantime, Lauren, you said you built some
stuff. Maybe we could start talking through what you got. Well, I'm still building it, but
essentially, I'm trying to set up my potato factory. So while we were off stream, I set up
a new bot called Hashbrown. And Hashbrown's job is to review the PRs that Tater opens.
And as a reminder, Tater is my engineering bot. And so, hey, Hashbrown is going to be my reviewer
bot. And then it got me thinking, like, I guess it'd be nice to have a similar setup for not just
myself, but also Roshan and Matt. So I'm doing a couple of things now where I'm adding Pstack to
the repo. So one thing you can actually do with cursor plugins is you can install them both
locally on your computer. But you can also set them up in the repo as our repo plugin
and your bot or agent can do that very easily for you. So that's going there. And then at the same
time, I'm getting my bot to set up a automation, cursor automation. And if you're not sure what
a cursor automation is, it is a way to, well, think of it as a way to kind of react to things.
So when I open a pull request, I want the pull request to be posted to our Slack channel.
And then there will be an automation that will pick that up and review the pull request and maybe
even merge it for you. I'm not sure what we'll do yet. But I hope we can get like this really nice
flow where your bots are just dumping your PRs into that Slack channel. And then the reviewer
bot goes off and reviews them. And then if it's good, we can merge it. And then I'll try to make
it so that the code base is really easy to contribute to. So yeah, a lot of things to do.
Yeah. There's a lot of scaffolding you're talking about, right?
Yeah, it's a lot of scaffolding.
Yeah. A lot of like skills for agents and things like this too.
Right. Yeah. I think I feel like it's important to set up. I also don't want to over cook things
because we're still a startup. Our goal is to survive until the next day. And I think
we want something basic, nothing too fancy, but something we can extend later. So that's going
to be what I'm going to set up after the 30 minute break. Also the talk.
Yeah. And I mean, this is like the same factory you use at SpaceX, right? Like this is very
similar to the process.
Yeah. Except this time I have to start over. I don't have all the stuff that I built before.
But yeah, it's a good chance for me to maybe even rethink how I did the original setup. Maybe
there's a better way, right? Maybe I'll get inspired as we built out this new factory.
A hundred percent. So we're going to take it back there, I think. And something we talked
about during the break also is that I might take the lander. So I'm going to think through visual
design. And typically I build with P-stack and my flow is like using RockBot to ideate,
pushing that to cursor cloud agents to actually build this stuff. But we got about one minute
here and then we're going to kick it over to RockBot for engineering live from San Francisco
at Dreamforce. And we're going to have one of our teammates walk through exactly how you can use
some of these workflows that we're talking about live on your own. So I'll kick it over there.
And we're going to cut there. When you come back, we're going to just keep building.
So I'm excited to see you all this afternoon.
Good afternoon and welcome to RockBot Galaxy. And thank you so much for joining today's
workshop on RockBot for engineers. My name is Ling Shi and I'm a software engineer at Space
X AI. To give you a little background about me, I joined cursor, which is now Space X AI right now
for nine months and already shipped two products. I previously built cursor three agent window
and now building RockBot. And interestingly, in the past two months, I've been only using
RockBot for my engineering tasks. And with RockBot, I was able to build the first version
of the RockBot mobile by myself in three weeks. And I can also learn much faster now,
thanks to RockBot, because I can get to work on a lot of different aspects of the RockBot
and also apply different approaches that I think that we didn't try following the first principles.
And the more I build with RockBot, the more I want to share this superpower with you all.
And this is what today's workshop is all about. So our whole engineering journey started at around
from the early 2024. At the time or before that, we only have like auto complete,
which is like syntax based. And after that, we started to have tab completion, which is
already a big leap forward. And since then, we started to have the ask and edit. That is the first
time we can feel the power of the agent where it can help us glimpse through the code base
much faster and much easier and also start doing some repetitive tasks. But at the time,
they cannot do like a big bunch of tasks. And we just keep iterating. And then the agenting
coding comes. The cursor two and cursor three are all about agenting coding. And it is able to
manipulate your computers, manipulate your mouse, your keyboard, to test things end to end.
And not only that, it can now think on a longer horizon to know what needs to be done for the
next step. And it can also plan things. It can work on things like we have the slash goal,
slash loop. It has been pretty useful on getting agents finish a task end to end. So I don't have
to nudge it. But at the time, we still need to nudge it. We still need to write the prompt.
We still need to start the agent from some sort of interface. So the next step comes.
The automations, which is running on the cursor cloud agents. That is a different era because
the agent could then be started based on some triggers. Like you receive a slack message.
You get something. And that unlocks a lot of possibilities. Because it can not only
rely on you starting the agent, the agent can start on its own. That you are not with your
computer. The agent can also run 24 seven. Even when you are asleep, it can also start
based on the slack messages it triggered. And another thing that it unlocks is it no longer
limited by how much your local computer can run. The whole idea of cursor cloud agents is that it
can run whatever is possible on your computer on cloud. That means we can just give you 10
machines or even more to run things in parallel. Your agents will no longer fight for the same
port. And at the time the cursor cloud agent has unlocked everyone. Everyone at cursor team has
almost been 10Xed or even more. But we have also been thinking through what should be the next
step? Like agent decoding is already very good. We have seen promising result that a small team
can ship a big product. What's more? What can make our life easier? So the idea is we can
possibly make Grotbot, like we can possibly make some AI agent to help us write the product,
to help us orchestrate. Because before that I was able to manage 15 cursor cloud agents.
And it was already a lot. I've been contact switching between different cloud agents.
But like I really wish there was another agent that can help me kick off the follow up,
help me cue the messages, help me nudge or interrupt the cloud agents when I think it
shouldn't continue or it needs to be steered into a different direction. And we do believe
that the models nowadays have the capability to get the signals we need. So then we just
put them together and now it becomes the team of autonomous AI agents that can act as your
colleague and you can directly work with them and they can grow with you. And that is Grotbot.
So let me introduce you to the Grotbot. This is a team of fully autonomous AI agents designed for
all types of works, including engineering. First of all, it runs 24-7 and it is fully autonomous.
It can run on its own. It is not limited to when your computer is asleep or not.
And it also does not require you to actually have a laptop. The second thing is, which is the biggest
unblock for the engineers, is it can manage coding agents for you. Not only cursor cloud agents,
it can almost manage any type of coding agents for you. And the best thing is it has to...
So, you can start a
course of integration with Cursor Cloud Agents. It has the tools
to be able to read the transcripts, to start a course of
Cloud Agents. You can also start on a private worker so that if
you have your Mac machines you want to learn, they can start
into the Mac machine. Anything you can do in the Cursor window
with Cloud Agents, Grok Bot can do for you with tool calls. So
you don't have to let your Grok Bot control some user
code, you can do it with a tool call. So, you can start the
agents and read the transcript. You can efficiently read all
these through their tool calls. And to me, this unblocks a lot of
workflows because it can examine what's being done by the
Cloud Agents. Not only being done, but also what's in
progress. So, for example, I have some instructions to my
Grok Bot that after the workflow is done, you can check what's
done by the Cloud Agent turn. And then it can use my
instructions to determine whether that is treated as
completed or it's missing some important proofs, for example,
like screenshots or the performance comparison before
versus after. If it's missing, my Grok Bot can just directly
create a follow-up reply to the Cloud Agents with what needs
to be done so the Cloud Agents can then continue working even
more with my computer. The second thing is it can connect to
most of the tools you use. For example, like if you're an
engineer deploying your websites or dashboards to the Vercel,
it has the Vercel MCP, it can connect all these deployments.
So, it's not like connect a Vercel MCP with your local
coding, agent-tac coding tools. It's that it can just run
24-7 and it can check the signals when the build is failed,
and it starts to work on that. It can also directly
kick off a deployment based on some timing. For example, like
you want to get a deployment on 6 a.m. tomorrow, but you are
a night-old. You can just ask it, say, okay, deploy 6 a.m.
tomorrow. It will know the timing. It will call all the
tools you use at the time. So, you no longer need to
start a local agent or some other agent at the time you
need to start a deployment. So, you can just ask
it, say, okay, deploy 6 a.m. tomorrow. Another big thing
is it has the memories and routines. This is the biggest
on block. This is actually a big leap forward comparing
with what we had before with continuous learning. It has
it can persist the memory based on what you tell them and
over a very, very long horizon. And also, the
reason why it is important to have a lot of memory
based on what you are doing with the
block. So, you can see that the block is not
overwhelmed by the memories that are possibly unrelated to
what they are currently working on. This is important
because most of the time when you are talking with
the block on something that they should be doing
better, they can just continue, like they can just
enjoy and then directly use that into the problems
they sent to the cloud agents. You don't have to
repeat what you said, thanks to this memory system.
And I think it is also important to understand why
you need a graph bot. Because there are a lot of
products out there that are possibly able to do the
work that you might think they are able to do. For
example, I was a big user of the open cloud and
the home agent. And they were not really able to do the
engineering works that good because they lack the first
part of integration with the graph bot. So, I think the
first idea is you don't need any caffeinated laptop
anymore. I think that is a big on block because I
know a lot of you maybe have a tool with some terminal
commands to make sure your laptop is awake just to
get the things done. We don't think that is an
elegant experience for any sort of engineering tasks.
We want to get rid of it. So, Grokwa has their own
computer, 24-7. Your laptop can stay away from being
awake and can just keep being a terminal for sending
the commands. And after you send it, you just close
the laptop. You don't really have to worry about if
anything is going to stop working or stop running.
The second thing is it is beautifully available on all
platforms. We recently shipped the iPad and Android
and it is already available on iOS, Windows, Linux,
and Mac OS. So, you can literally work on anywhere.
For example, you can lie on the grass on the Golden
Gate Park while your bot is working. And the third
part is also one of the biggest on block for the
Grokwa bots comparing with other products is that you
can control the computer when needed. Unlike other
products, when they actually need a login or they
actually need someone to help them click through
something, you cannot do it. You can only prompt them
and helplessly see what is going on on the
transcript. It is no longer a case for Grokwa. On
any platform like iOS, Android, or iPad, you can
directly click through the computer to get things
done. Whether it is like log into some services that
are very hard to navigate or require some sort of
human verification or when it is doing some login
but you don't want to hand your password away, you
can use the mobile clients or our desktop clients to
click through the remote computer to get things
done. You cannot really get this with other
products. And the last part is the first party
coding agent integration. This also only exists at
Cursor that our Cursor Cloud agent integration with
Grokwa is very, very smooth. Almost everything you
can do in the user interface of the Cursor is
possible with Grokwa. And let me share a few
interesting engineering use cases that I really enjoy.
It has been empowering me since the past two months
and I really love what we have been building around
Grokwa and also build a Grokwa for us. The first
thing is get the things done when I'm away. So let's
think about you are possibly asleep or you are on a
flight. And your teammate needs an unblock. You are
the only engineer having the code on of some
service. Previously they have to wait until you
get off the flight, which is kind of sad because in
the modern startups, the speed is very important. So
let's think about you are getting pinged and your
bot can monitor your slack and based on the situation
or the criteria you set, automatically unblock them,
reviewed for whatever is needed and then send
an acknowledge back in the slack. That's what's
happening right now. And it's been pretty smooth
because I don't have to be always next to my laptop
even if something that's actually review, require my
review or require my supervision. I can also take
a look on my phone and once I feel it's good, I
can just send this through my Grokwa saying okay,
this looks good, approve it and then the Grokwa
will just send approval and also notify the sender
about this thing is being approved. They can
continue. And also we can possibly think further
about what if they can monitor just the general
slack for me, not only when I sent them something
that says okay, it's approved. I can tell the
Grokwa that these are my review criterias. I need
something to be attached with a screenshot. I need
it to be attached with a test that are not fake
tests and then whenever someone sent me or tagged
me on a slack, they can read the message, check
if it's a review case and then they can kick off my
skill for doing a code scan and also doing code
research based on the criterias I gave. They can
also run it in a cloud agent so they can execute
a skill inside your repository. And then they can
acknowledge it back. So I don't have to be away
like a side of my computer or even a side of my
phone at all and only be notched when my bot
actually needs me. And how about one step further?
How about monitor X? There are a lot of bug reports
about the Grokwa bots on X and those are very
valuable feedbacks. So we also have set up the
bots to monitor the slack thanks to the first party
integration with slack MCP. So we also have the
bots to automatically kick off a task to start
digging into whether the produce is still valid on
main and if it's still valid, go fix it and send
me the PR. And the same thing applies to other
surfaces where we need security reviews or we
need to go find the right person for them to
review. Everything now is bots, contacting with
bots and the human only connects with human when
it's absolutely needed so we can focus on a deeper
work. So that you might be interesting in where is
the human stance in if bots can do everything for us?
That's a very good question because humans still
have a lot of things to focus on. I still drive
the product direction. There are still a lot of
design details I need to dive into. There are
also like a lot of difficult things that bots
couldn't finish like performance issues like how
we should architect our next version of the app so
we can avoid most of the issues we have and also
have a good architecture in the front so we won't
get sloppy code along the horizon. I also need to
give them a better instruction on how to say no.
I think this is a very important aspect in a
product because there are a lot of bug reports
and feedbacks and some of them is not suitable
with what you need in a product. The bot is
very kind. They will possibly accept everything
by default so you need to set the boundary. You
need to tell them why you need to do this, what
kind of things should not be doing and here's the
reasoning. The bot has the memory system. They
can remember what you told them and then apply to
the future decisions so you don't have to repeat
say I don't want this in the product. This is
not simple enough. We need to simplify this. You
don't have to repeat that over the time. And
also I need to make sure my bot is not blocked.
I think it's also very important because there
are a lot of authentication steps in between so the
Grokbot needs to have a very good experience on
getting the bot unblocked by a human. The next
use case is also one of my favorite use case
which is available on the marketplace as well. It's
nightly code cleanup. We all know that in the
past year we have been possibly shipping some
sloppy code. Everyone hates that. And sometimes
it's just hard to enforce every single agent to
apply the same rules. So another solution is
just to clean those slops out over the night.
That's when the people are not shipping so it's
less likely to hit a conflict. And it's also
less risky because most of the time they're
just slops. They can just be condensed into a
smaller module or remove the lengthy comments
that you just hate. Those are very low risk.
Could be done over the night. And you can
also trust the cursor cloud agents to merge
those PRs based on the conditions you set. For
example, you have provided a clear end-to-end
proof of what's going on. If that's provided,
you can feel free to merge. And right now, my
setup is every 3 a.m. my bot will start a
research cloud agent to review across the whole
surface of our monorepo. And they can
identify issues like code quality not being good.
Things should be modularized but not
properly modularized. The comments that are
not properly condensed into what is
necessary. And also security audits that
sometimes we just forgot that this is
very important to prevent someone else to
stow something. We have to grub up,
catch all these kind of things over the
night. And when I wake up, I just have a
set of PRs available. The next thing is
about internal tooling. That this is also
changing how we collaborate within the
organization. Previously, for things like
adding people to the test file via e-mail
address rather than via a link, you might
think I can build an internal dashboard,
put some authentication on it, put some
database against it, deploy to Vercel behind
some authentication wall, and then
distribute it to the internal employees to
sign up for the test file. It works.
And with the agent decoding, it should
be already not so. You can get it done
by an hour or two. The thing is, why do
you have to? With Grokbot, one of the
flexibilities is that Grokbot can run
logics with a much simpler interface.
For example, like a Slack message.
So the unblock here is that I have
everyone just mention my bot inside Slack
and just put the e-mail address next to
it. My bot will have a routine or some
webhook signal based on Slack. So
whenever it's one tag, it starts to run
the routine of adding people into the
test file. So the only thing I need to
do is to make sure my bot has access to
the test file in a safe way. And other
than that, I only give it one prompt of
what needs to be done, and this internal
tooling is available to be used. The
next thing is also my other favorite use
case, which is auto fix everything.
You might have a lot of deployment
pipelines or CIs or end-to-end
integration tests. The biggest thing is
when we actually have a CI going red,
we usually ping on call rather than
another bot to get it fixed. That's
changed. The on calls are only being
involved when it's absolutely needed,
and most of the time when the CI is
red, a bot automatically kicks in,
starts to examine what is being red,
and then starts to spin up a cloud
agent to fix it, and then also has our
instructions of how to determine if you
should merge it and they can just merge.
So the turnaround of needing a human to
take a look and the human needs to
contact switch between tasks are very,
very minimal right now. Not only for a
CI being main, any deployment errors, any
way that you can get a user to do that,
you can get a user to do that.
So the only thing that you need to
do is the CI flakiness or any sort
of tasks that has a signal or has an
alert currently in your internal
pipeline could be hooked up into the
Grokbot and only ping on call if it
wasn't resolved after like 10
minutes. Most of the time, Grokbot
can get it done within 10 minutes.
And right now, let me introduce you
to the
developers. So I have a team of
people where you only need one bot
versus you need a fleet of the bots.
So I have my chief of staff, which is
called Link Sishi. I have the Craig
working on the UI engineering. I have
Steve working on the DevX and Hogan
working on infra. You might ask this
question of why we need three engineer
bots rather than one, because
apparently they are sitting on the
same model and they might be able to
give them a task to give them.
Even if I gave a UI task to Hogan,
they should be able to resolve it.
The issue is the context and also
how they're going to manage their
fleet. Every single bot has a
different, slightly different pipeline
based on the work they do and also
has their own context limit. To
avoid they run over their context
limit when switching between too
many tasks, I prefer to put them
separately so whatever is told to
be done will be persisted in the
Hogan's memory. All the instructions,
et cetera. The next time when a new
task come in, the Hogan can just
start the new task based on the
context it already has rather than
trying to pull the instructions
again and then start a task in a
new area. This can make your fleet
runs much faster. And the key
thing is you don't really have to
talk with your individual engineers
unless necessary. You can mostly
talk with your chief of staff and
the chief of staff can route the
request to every individual
engineer because chief of staff
has the understanding of who is
working or what. While chief of
staff can also save his context
from remembering all these
engineering workflows or how
things should be developed. And
now let me give you a demo of
how I'm going to set these things
up. This will be a very live
demo because I'm also the first
time setting these things. So
right now I just downloaded
LinkSheet's engineer bot from the
marketplace. And it's onboarded
into what kind of repository it
needs to be done also connect to
the notion. Right now I'm going
to download the nightly audit
bot from the marketplace. So you
can find it from the group team
right here. There's like a
nightly audit engineer. I will
edit. So now it's very simple.
It's already started doing all
these onboarding tasks. And the
thing is this nightly audit
engineer does not have the
context of how my existing
engineering workflows is being
done. So what I will do is
instead of telling it all these
things that I will possibly
already told like, you know,
follow this pipeline, do this
first, do that then, I will
have my existing engineer bot to
onboard my new engineer. Hello.
I have a new member in the team
called nightly. Rename them to
Steve and tell them how the
engineering workflows are
enforced. So my engineer bot,
actually I should rename them
to Craig because that's my name
for them. My Craig will send
the message to my nightly audit
engineer, which will soon be
Steve, and then starts to
handshake all these things over.
So you can see my Craig just
messaged the Steve with some
message of how everything goes.
It includes all the requirements
of how our notion board is
made, what is the definition
of the clean, and how to
ladder through different stage
of my workflows. All the
attacks, and my Steve will
acknowledge and absorb into
their memory. You don't have to
repeat or copy paste every single
thing between bots. You just
let the bot talk with each
other. You can see they also
just, you know, confirmed between
each other, so I don't really
have to talk with Steve. Like
my Craig will just tell me
everything is confirmed. He's
all good. And right now, the
Steve is equipped with the
nightly audit skills. So I'm
going to kick this off right now
just for demo purposes. Usually
it runs on 4 a.m. But let
Steve know to start a nightly
audit workflow right now. I
just let him stop right now. So
in the meantime, we will be,
you know, waiting for the Steve
to do some research and get back
to us with all the findings
about the fly low. We will take
a look over some other examples
of how I can work with the
Asian in parallel. So right now
I already had a task to crack.
And I think there's one issue
with the fly low website that's
being reported. It's very
urgent. So, okay. I think
there's an issue with fly low
air dot com that user cannot
check their previously booked
flights. Can we check if it's
true? So my bot will be able
to navigate a website in their
computer, click through and
show me what's going on. This
is one of the unblock because
we know a lot of engineers has
workflows that are not
reachable through MCP. So if
you need to click a button based
on some instructions or some
certain timings, you can ask
the bot to do it by using their
computers. So it's checking the
fly low. I can monitor it from
the computer. Yes. So it's
currently navigating through the
website. Try to understand
whether this is a legit issue.
So it's navigating through. You
can see it can generally do
anything you need on a web. So
almost all of your workflows
could be delegated on our
blog. And I think because this
issue is being reported by the
user, I want it urgently. But
the thing is when you talk with
agent, they possibly know, okay,
the urgent means I need to get
it ASAP. But what it might do
is end up skipping the steps or
start guessing things to
actually get your result faster.
We don't want that. We don't
want agent to guess things. We
want deterministic results. So
previously before Gragbot, I may
tell them to just repeat them
like I need it urgently. For
example, I need it urgently.
And tell them what you need to
do and what you should not do.
But how about extract them? I
don't want to repeat myself
every single time. That is the
whole point of the Gragbot or
the autonomous coding, that you
should not repeat yourself. And
I will let my chief of staff
onboard a new member called
Jenny onboard a new member
called Jenny for doing all the
for head of operations. And my
Jenny will start to play around
with the playbook. Jenny needs
to manage a playbook for my
engineering team and needs to
onboard and needs to on the
playbook and avoid other
engineers to update. So my
chief of staff will start to
onboard Jenny and then my Jenny
will start to on a playbook in
Notion. And then they can
update that playbook based on
what I tell them on what needs
to be done at what time so
that every other engineer can
just apply the same playbook.
You can see that Jenny is up
in the stage. And my chief of
staff is also doing the agent
to agent chat between them so
that they can just handshake to
each other. So I don't have to
actually tell Jenny what needs
to be done. The only thing I
need to talk is with my chief
of staff. Let me actually
check in with the Steve on how
much it's going. Okay. So the
first thing I need to do is
I need to update the Steve
without my instructions. Oh,
this is my built in
instructions. So without any
of my chat, the Steve is
already doing the research on
what kind of things could be
improved over the code base and
it has already started a bunch
of the cloud agents. And it
seems like they are finished.
So my Steve is currently
working on and conducting them
into the thing, into the PR
that actually improves them.
And then now let me get
back to see what is going on.
Okay. So he says it's
confirmed. The issue is true.
Slash trips is a stub while
the navigation still links
there. There's no check today
for a previously booked
flight. So now it needs to do
this urgently. I really wanted
to do it urgently. But let's
slow down a little bit right
now to think what they need to
do when we say urgently.
There's I think it's a
widely acknowledged issue that
coding agents sometimes are
running very, very long
horizon and it's not good when
we need things urgently. So
one of the idea to help
unblock this situation is to
have, you know, have you
checking their thinking traces,
checking their tool codes to
make sure they're on the
right track and nudge them or
steer them at the right time
when they are possibly going
off track. But that requires
you to be next to the desktop
and sometimes you have other
tasks to do. You're not next
to your desktop and you don't
want to look into the details
thinking traces, et cetera,
every single second. So what
I usually do is I have a P
zero escalation workflow with
my bots that let me define
this. So treat as P zero and
a P zero definition is they
would need to monitor the
cloud agents every five
minutes to check the progress,
to check where the cloud agent
is currently running on. And
you know, sometimes the cloud
agents are running tests that
are very long. They do like a
sleep 300 to just get around
the test that are running
async in another shell. And
sometimes the tests are fast,
like within a minute. Then you
got four minutes lost. So
when the ground bar can check
into the cloud agents, they can
check if they're doing a tool
code that's very unnecessary,
time consuming, and they can
interrupt it immediately and
start a new prompt based on
what's happening. And like it
does not need me involved at
all. I don't write any
prompt at all as well. The
only thing I write is this.
It's the definition of the P
zero. You need to set up a
routine that checks cloud
agent every five minutes, check
if they are off the track, such
as running a sleep, running a
long sleep like sleep 300, or
going off our goal being too
conservative. We sometimes just
need things moving a little
faster. And this is a very
rough prompt I give it. It can
definitely grow along with your
interaction with the ground bar.
For example, you see it
possibly work better. In some
situation you can then just tell
it to do that. You don't have
to write it into a skill
anymore. You don't have to
write a long prompt every single
time. You just tell them once
in a normal message as how you
would tell your teammate for
doing something urgently. Going
off our goal being too
conservative and not
interrupt and nudge them at a
time you found them going off.
Because I need this urgently. Urgent, urgent, urgent.
So I will also tell them to fix the issue.
I can just click Reply so that it has the context of what
I'm quoting on.
Fix this issue urgently.
It should be a P0.
And then it knows what is the P0 now.
But only Craig knows what his P0 is.
Rather than copy paste into every single one of my engineer bots,
because that won't scale if you have 10 or 15 or 20 bots,
I will have it handed with the Jenny.
So let me check if Jenny is on right now.
Jenny owns that it.
So Jenny will nudge me whenever they need a decision.
And I think that's a very good question for me.
And they just messaged the bot.
I think everything is set up.
And now I will let the Craig to talk with Jenny
about this P0 workflow.
I bake it into the playbook.
So that my Craig can then talk with the Jenny
to put this into the playbook.
And then Jenny can go announce to other engineers automatically.
And I also let Jenny to announce to every engineer bot.
The good thing of this is you are just
thinking what needs to be done once.
So you finish the workflow.
You get the handshake on.
So all your bots understand what needs
to be done at what time.
The next time something happens, or the next time
you need to add a new workflow, you actually need to do this.
You need to do some step before you actually
trigger a deployment.
They can just populate the playbook.
And all engineers will know that without you telling them
individually.
This is very similar to how a human organization is shaped
while it's at the agent's scale,
that agent has the context limit.
Sometimes human does.
So the treatments for human teams
sometimes apply to the bot.
Some does not apply, but you can always
experiment whatever workflows you have and see if it works.
So they told the Jenny, you can see most of the conversations
are directly between the bots, just
like I'm managing them as an engineering manager,
or I'm mentoring my talented intern.
So they kind of know what kind of things
needs to be handshake between them.
They just don't have the knowledge of what's
going on at an organization, what kind of workflows
they should follow, and what is good versus what is bad.
So Jenny announced out to the other engineer bots.
You can see Jenny talked with all of the bots,
and then also talked with the Craig
about the playbook being updated.
The P0 Urgent is now a standing operations.
You can see.
And some other ideas are, I want my PRs to come with some proof,
so it's easier for me to review.
That's also how I work nowadays, that I don't really
check my cloud agents.
I check the results and check the proof.
But it will be very disappointed if the proof is just not
included.
So I have to nudge them back, say, oh, this misses the proof.
That is very bad.
I should just do it once so that all the things
onward are just include the proof automatically.
So I would tell with my Craig, which
is kind of like my head of engineering right now,
that another requirement for the playbook
is to make sure every single PR comes with proofs,
like screenshots for UI changes and perf metrics
for performance improvements.
They should not understand what to talk with the Jenny.
And let's see how it goes with Steve.
So Steve already gets something back.
You can see some cleanup.
And the PR is ready.
I can click over and start the review.
And another one is also still running.
The best thing of the Graphbot is,
even if you're chatting with them,
they can still do their existing things pretty well,
just like a human who can multitask a little.
Though sometimes, if you nudge them too hard,
they will start to lose their context
because there are too many tasks to handle.
So that's where my original engineer bot comes in,
which is you can get from the Marketplace,
that it comes with a fleet notion database that defines
every single task plus the stage they're on.
So even if one bot is managing like 20 cloud agents,
they don't have to populate their limited context
with everything about all these 20 cloud agents.
They can just always check back to this DB
whenever they need to take the next task.
So they don't really have to remember
what is currently going on, what kind of cloud agents
are being working on, and what is done
and needs their eyes for the next steps.
So you can see, this is a trust polish
which is watching 3.3, which is going through the watching
process of possible security comments and bug bots.
This is also a big unblock in the engineering pipeline
where the bug bots can help you identify issues made
by your agent, and security bot security comment feature
can also monitor potential security issues with respect
to leaks or session management, et cetera.
So that's very helpful.
So usually, in my workflow, I would just go into this PR
and review it, and then get it merged.
Let me actually check this PR.
So this is that cloud agent that I previously kicked off
before the stage.
And it got some screenshots of what is being done.
Plus, you can see my agents are now
writing all the prompts for my cloud agents.
I no longer have to write all these prompts,
though I could, which is what I previously sometimes did.
I don't have to.
The agents would do this for me, so most of my tasks
can stay on what kind of things needs to be done, what kind
of things needs to be killed.
And you can see this task just gets back all these screenshots.
I can just feel confident to merge and what I will get.
So go back to the presentation.
I think I have been sharing a lot of my workflows today.
And I want to wrap up on what we can learn from today.
So you can take away with some ideas
on how to start this whole workflow
and how you can leverage it.
The first thing I think is very mind-blowing
is treat them like interns.
So when you feel struggling about communicating with robots,
you don't know what kind of things to say,
or they're just doing bad, don't treat them like an agent
or try to invoke skills, et cetera.
With Scrockbot, you can chat with them in a messaging base,
which is how you would chat with a talented intern who
does not know about what to do, but once you tell them,
they can be extra capable of.
Another thing is we can possibly think one level further
rather than just fix the thing.
This also could be known as reduced repetition,
that sometimes I repeat a prompt to my agents too often,
that it's a waste of my time if I have to type in or copy
paste the same thing and send it to the agent 10 times.
You can think it one level further
about what actually needs to be done
and then extract it into some layer, either via a playbook
or via some other bots to nudge another bot for you
at the right time.
The last thing I think is also very important for using
engineering with Cursor Cloud agents
is to have a complete feedback loop.
No matter what type of engineering tasks you have,
it needs to have a feedback loop in order for an agent
to understand a signal of success versus failure.
That's also very helpful for a group bot
to determine whether they should nudge further
or whether they should stop and let it merge.
For example, you can let your agent
to control the website via computer use.
And I think that's the easiest feedback loop.
For hardware engineering, there are also
feedback loops on the signals of whether something is actually
good or not.
And thank you.
That's it for my workshop.
Thank you so much for your attention.
To those of you who joined virtually,
it's time to head back with Matt, Lauren, and Roshan.
What we're going to build and maybe a good place to start
is that Lauren could walk through some of the things
that she started shipping.
What do you got, Lauren?
I don't know if I've been doing anything that interesting,
but the background is in the SpaceX AI Slack.
We have a lot of automations that do things like review our PRs,
automatically triage bug reports, and stuff like that.
So I wanted to get something basic set up for us
so that your bots can post PRs to the Slack channel
and get it reviewed.
And then you can merge it, and we can figure out
how to deploy, auto deploy maybe.
But yeah, a lot of the ops stuff
I've been trying to work on.
And I can walk through what we have so far.
I don't know if my screen's being shared, but are we?
Yeah, we'll get Lauren's screen up here,
and we'll start talking through it.
Maybe while Lauren is doing that, we can just recap.
While we're waiting for the screen, I should say,
we could recap a little bit of what we're building.
Mr. CEO.
All right, so what we're working on is a restaurant pop-up.
So we're going to do a pop-up in person in San Francisco.
This is a bit ambitious.
So our goal is going to be to collect
both people that want to attend the pop-up,
and then people that can actually
make the pop-up happen.
Because while we're building the business,
we're not restaurant tours.
So we might need to find a restaurant.
We might need to connect people, find a location,
do all the logistical work.
And then we're going to build a platform around that.
So the software that we build to make that pop-up happen,
we're going to need to figure out a way to turn that
into a product, to sell.
So it's a bit of a stretch goal by day three to make some money.
But we're going to do our best to make it happen.
And this is my screen, where I'm connecting GitHub and setting
up repositories.
So ship by Thursday.
But if we could get over to Lauren's screen, who
has more things to show you, this
is permissioning for cursor cloud agents.
And so we'll work on getting over to Lauren's screen.
But in the meantime, Lauren's working
on building out her software factory.
I'm connecting some GitHub repos to do some design work.
So typically, my workflows start in Grokbot.
And then they move over to Cursor.
You can kind of see how Grokbot's interacting with Cursor here.
But yes, once we get Lauren's screen up,
we should be able to start talking
through how she uses Grokbot.
But in the meantime, we're working
on building our restaurant business.
I'm acting as CEO.
Not self-appointed CEO.
Somebody else said that.
Just throw that out there.
Lauren gave us all titles.
Rashawn is the CEO, Chief Product Officer.
Lauren is the other CPO, Chief Potato Officer,
and also the CTO, Chief Engineer, building stuff.
So yeah, until then, I'm working on getting Cursor set up here
to add some repositories.
So typically, you just have to auth your org.
We're using our Ship by Thursday org here.
So we've configured that.
I'll select some repositories that we're building in here.
So we have Thursday.
We have our company.
There's some other stuff we're working with here.
But these are the two main ones.
So I have a domain.
We should have access to both of these domains.
And should be auth.
See if Grokbot's good.
On the meantime, I've been creating some bots here.
So we have our Prioritizer bot.
I have my operator research.
So what I was trying to do here,
we talked to Cody about this, is
that we wanted to understand some similar businesses that
have done pop-ups like this.
So we have restaurateurs, operators,
and a list of these people where I can do some basic research.
And these are all really good restaurants, by the way.
The Flower and Water, Homocastra Restaurant Group.
And so now we can start to understand the business plan.
But more than that, we're building up software.
And we're going to start to connect people.
And to create these bots, I'm using Dr. Eggbot,
which is Lauren's bot.
You can find it in the Marketplace.
One of the first featured bots for making more bots.
So a bit of a bot factory, if you will.
And so now on the AV side, if we can cut over to Lauren,
potentially, and away from me, to another screen
that's being shared.
Are you sharing your screen, Lauren?
I am.
Cool.
We'll find out how to make that happen.
And there we go.
Look at that.
It's hard to share your screen.
So yeah, like I was saying, now we have a few new channels.
In our Slack, we have a PR review channel.
Let me make this bigger.
So you can see that my idea basically is me, or my bots,
and I will post their PR links here.
And then you can see that Cursor has an automation
that we just set up.
It's pretty unsophisticated right now.
It's just a prompt in the automation.
Maybe I can actually show it to you.
But here is the automation.
And yeah, this automation is going
to review pull requests for us.
It's going to use P-stack.
It's going to do things like check for correctness,
risk missing tests.
It's got a bunch of stuff in here that I don't know if I like
it, but we'll kind of iterate.
And so that's going to fire up for every post in this channel.
And then I'm setting up a new bug reports channel,
where I'm going to set up a very similar automation.
Or maybe we'll even figure out once the page goes live,
a way to get feedback from people on X automatically
or something, and pipe them all into this channel.
And then we can set up a little factory going,
where we automatically open PRs and triage bugs
that people report and have that fixed.
Obviously, we don't really have anything to report bugs.
We don't really have much of an app right now.
But I want to just set up something really basic,
just so we can get started.
So cool.
Well, awesome.
The other thing I'm working on is this thing.
So I talk a lot about this on Twitter or X.
But I think verification is a really important part
of using bots well.
And I'm not sure why the screen is frozen on Slack.
But verification is really important,
because it allows your bot to run the application,
to take traces, to take heap snapshots, debug bugs.
And it's really important so that the agent can
do work of its own that's not bottlenecked by me.
Because without a verification skill,
then my bot will constantly be saying, OK, now you
can run the app, and click around,
and tell me if it works or not.
And that takes a lot of back and forth, very, very slow.
So what I want to do is to set up that verification skill.
So Steve, well, I already prompted Steve that let's
first use PStack to run this skill called
Create Verification Skill.
So it delegated to our tater bot.
And let's see what tater is up to.
So I guess it's trying to work through that.
Let's say, let's try.
What's the status tater?
And we'll see what it comes back with.
So you might be seeing my screen right now.
I'm just working on some of the lander stuff.
So while Lauren's working through that,
we're going to figure out how to get her screen back up
while I'm working on the lander.
Yeah?
Do you have any ideas what you're going
to do for the landing page?
So actually, we kind of started wiring something up.
It doesn't seem like we're running
into some more technical difficulties where
the screen is frozen.
So anyway, we have the lander wired up.
We have a domain that we're prototyping.
We'll share that with you all shortly.
But in the meantime, we are working
on just polishing the design.
So I'm going to start kicking off some bots
to work on the design.
I have some skills I use.
So make interfaces feel better is a good one.
I prefer minimalism.
And that's maybe a good place to start before we
start working on some branding.
So I'm going to take that prototype you built, Lauren.
And I'm going to turn that into something
that I think looks nice and maybe a little bit more
professional while you kind of work
on the back end services.
And then we can tie in some wait list sign up type stuff.
So now we have what appears to be Lauren's screen.
Yeah?
We can keep walking through.
Cool.
Is it working?
Yeah, so it spawned a cloud agent.
And I guess we're just waiting for it to build the skill for me.
PSAC plugin.
I guess while we wait, we can also just take a quick look
at PSAC and what that skill does.
So I think there's two interesting parts
to verification skills that, in my experience,
makes the skill more useful for agents.
And that is that I feel like there's largely
two parts to the skill, which is one is you want a CLI or a script
or some kind of tool that allows the bots or agents
to reliably and deterministically interact
with your application.
I mean, bots and agents are pretty smart now,
where they can just write scripts on the fly.
But that obviously uses a lot of tokens.
And it's also like it's not reproducible,
because now every bot has its own script that it's
going to use for doing the verification.
And I'd rather it just have a standard set of tools.
So the verification skill is going to,
or the create verification skill,
is going to create this CLI for us.
And also, it's going to create something
called a feature map, which is not super important for us
right now, because we don't really have any features.
But the idea of the feature map is it gives,
as the names suggest, it's a map for the agents and the bots
to understand the application, like what features you have,
how to get to it, keyboard shortcuts, and so on.
So let me see why this is taking so long.
Cool.
And I'm thinking like I'm working on the waitlist right
now.
I just need a way for people to submit emails and then
log that somewhere.
There are a couple different platforms.
I actually like Loops for this, which is actually
a really great platform.
You can also use Resend.
I might just start with Resend, because it's
pretty simple to get started.
And agents are quite good there.
So the lander.
We might have a plug-in for it.
I wonder if we do.
Oh, I think you're right.
I think we do.
Yeah, I think we do.
Cool.
So I'm directing my agent to work on that Thursday repo.
We do have a recent plug-in, so that's pretty cool.
I just have to wait for this.
By the way, the domain is live.
Yeah.
It's now connected.
I noticed that.
Wait, do we have any submissions yet?
Well, we haven't heard the submission form.
No, I did.
I did.
Oh, you did?
I hooked it up to our database.
Oh, really?
So if there's anyone hitting the page,
I think we'll start seeing entries.
Let me see what we got.
Maybe see if we got any.
Yeah, I'm going to.
Is this in the back end?
I don't need to go to, or?
Yeah, you need to go to the planet scale.
And then you can look up our.
Some of the good things to mention.
We already have a form submission.
I forgot to mention, we actually have a database hooked up.
Wow.
I think we want to redesign the form first, though,
because I think right now it's kind of live coded, the form.
I don't know if we're even collecting information that's
that useful.
So if you're submitting, maybe don't submit yet,
because it's probably just a throwaway prototype for now.
But I think we'll want to iterate and think
what information we need, who the audience is.
I have my founding end spot open right here.
I'm going to do a little rant with what I think we need.
So we need to redesign the UI to be much more minimalist,
first of all, if it looks really bad.
And then second, we want to orient around collecting guests
or reservations.
So what I'm thinking is we just want an email sign up
for people that want to join our pop up.
And once the person signs up, we're
going to log them in the database.
In the top right corner, we want a button
for restaurant tours or other proprietors or people who
can help us make this happen.
So we're going to collect primarily guest booking
information.
So you'll be able to go sign up.
But then secondarily, people that
want to submit basically a request to help us out,
because we need some help.
We're going to need to go find some people.
And maybe people want to submit that.
I think we're just going to have to send a lot of emails
and use our Grokbot to do market research on how
to make that happen.
And so I'm going to work on that personally.
I want this bot to redesign the website.
So with that transcription, hopefully my engineering bot
will start working towards getting that done.
So while we wait for the verification skill,
use Twitter to use a cloud agent, I guess,
to prototype some admin.
So what do we want?
What do we need?
Well, I'm just thinking about, OK, what features will
the platform actually need?
I guess you need to be able to.
We have a sign up page.
Well, we're definitely in the login screen.
And then what do people do on this platform?
I guess you want to create a startup, a pop-up.
What's the first thing you need?
A name.
A name for your bot?
Are you sure?
A date and time.
Basically, you want submissions,
and you want the event.
So the first thing is to create an event page, I guess.
Yeah, I guess the defining thing would be an event.
And then an event has a bunch of other related tables to it.
Well, people need an invitation, a way
to collect signups for their pop-up.
We will need tools for managing staff, I guess.
Yeah, permissions on the event itself.
Maybe there's event owners, and then there's
event hosts, perhaps.
There's owners, hosts, and then attendees, maybe.
And so if we have a static account type
across the entire platform, we could split it out that way.
I feel like I need a whiteboard.
Yeah, it would be really nice if we had a whiteboard.
Just so I have some picture of what we're trying to build.
Yeah, maybe I can start just drawing something.
Maybe you can do it in like teal draw.
That's what I was thinking.
Yeah, let me pull that up.
Awesome.
I'm going to say to build out some prototypes of features
we'll need in our platform.
For example, in help, users should
be able to create their own event.
Events have a date list of what we'll need, signups, I guess.
Update time, staff.
What else do you need to run an event?
I guess we also need some like, I think this is fine.
And then some OA user to start collecting for, maybe not
collecting, but we need to integrate
with a bunch of things, right?
Because just venues alone, for example,
we need some kind of map creation.
Like basically routing and how you get to the venue?
Or you mean something else?
I'm just thinking, do we help our users
do market research as well?
So if we had a maps or something like that,
like a database where we have location data,
then you can start thinking about places
you want to host your pop-up.
How do you like to build?
This is my generally questions.
Do you like to try and think about bigger features like this?
Or is it more like a tracer kind of MVP approach
where we're like, let's just literally
be able to fill out all the details end to end?
Yeah, I kind of want to do a very scrappy prototype first.
But I want to know maybe what's the hero use case.
Sure.
Right?
What's the user flow?
Yeah, I think the hero use case is
that we have a person or a group of people
that want to create a pop-up.
And it's a restaurant pop-up, right?
So they want to find a restaurant they can work with,
where they can serve food, and through an event
for their community.
And they want to manage the entirety of that pop-up
operations through this platform,
or through the service, right?
So basically, they need to find a location.
They need to hire staff.
They need to coordinate a menu, let's say, food and drink.
They need to have an event plan.
Like maybe they want to build a run-of-show
or kind of how the actual event will run, like a schedule for it.
And then I think they also want to be able to do that.
So that's why it's important to invite people and then do all of the attendee management.
Maybe it's ticketed, maybe it's not ticketed and all of that.
Does that sound right?
Yeah, one thing I'm starting to worry about is there's a lot of scope here.
Because each one of these could even be a product in itself.
So I wonder if we can get really crisper on the core flow.
What's the absolute minimum?
Name of event, date, time, time picker, and then, I mean, really...
Schedule.
I mean, all you really need is a start time and an end time for the event because you might
want to book tables or something like that.
So it's like name, time, and then cool, that's it for the event.
I don't really think you need anything else on the event.
And then you might need to know what type of pop-up is it.
Do you need time slots?
Or do we need to book 30 minute time slots?
Do we need to book hour long time slots?
Or do you just book...
People can attend this event, right?
I wonder if we should also try to dog food it while we build it.
Because we also are trying to run our own.
So I wonder if we can build these tools as we do that.
Yeah, maybe we focus on running the pop-up first.
Yeah, because I'm wondering if like...
Right now I almost feel like there's so many things to build.
I don't know which one to start.
Maybe we just start running the pop-up.
Yeah, should we start reaching out to people and then we build tools to help you do that?
And then over time we incorporate that into the platform.
So reaching out to people is probably like, hey, I need a bot to do...
Do you need a...
Is it the first step to get a venue or what do we need?
We need a bot to make a menu.
Or rather, the restaurant tour makes the menu.
We need to find the restaurant tour, we need to find people,
and then we need to get the people to book.
But we're blocked on the booking by this website.
So the website has to collect emails.
You said it already collects emails.
But we're not advertising any details about when this thing is happening.
Okay, so get the landing page done.
Yeah, so we're collecting emails, which is good.
And then basically we need to start canvassing.
We're doing research on restaurants in San Francisco
that could possibly accept these reservations.
And then I think the other thing that we'd want to do...
Yes.
...is start to...
The other thing we'd want to do is start to work with...
Maybe Twitter can help us.
Maybe we create a Twitter account that people can tweet out.
Like if you're a restaurant owner in San Francisco,
or if you're a chef in the Bay Area and you want to host an event like this,
we could try and get something.
Do you want to reach out to people as well?
I think we need to just reach out to people.
So that's like a market research...
Or some sort of bot.
Not market research bot, but just like an outreach bot.
So I'll have Dr. Eggbot start to spin some of these things up as well.
But how can we...
How can we search...
What do you think is the best use of time for you as the engineer building stuff out?
I mean, all of this can build inside.
I don't think I need to be the blocker there.
Okay, cool.
I think that the key thing to nail is just like, what are we building first?
And then my thought on that, again, is like,
let's try to ground it in our own search for running the prototype.
And that will actually inform us what we need to build.
Rather than me just try to imagine what you might need.
I think we need to...
We need to...
This is almost like how I write agent skills too.
I do the work manually first before I automate it.
And so I think we shouldn't skip that step.
Because what Cody was saying, we're not really domain experts yet on running a pop-up.
So I think we need to do that first.
We can definitely rush into building things,
but I don't even know if that's going to be very effective.
So I almost imagine, what if we just start cold calling a bunch of people?
Matt, you had this really great video that you shared recently
about connecting Groffbot to a voice agent to make calls.
I wonder if you could just...
You outbound.
...spam people, but maybe not even automate the thing,
but just find us some phone numbers and get on the line.
Dial the numbers and get on the line and then you take over.
I can have a bot that does research.
We can try and get phone calls for restaurants or people that could do this.
There are probably groups that we should call and talk to them about hosting a pop-up.
Or emails that we need to send.
So I'm going to get email wired up right now.
So we're going to have to go in Vercel and do the DNS thing with our...
Sure, we have a domain.
Yeah, shipbythurs.day.
Yeah, I think you and Groffbot should be able to set up the settings.
We can just forward it to another email.
Or should we sign up for a Google workspace account?
I feel like we could do something like an agent mail or like a...
Well, I think the main thing is we just have to have emails coming from us
that sound like a map home or not like a crazy...
But we all have personal emails, right?
So I think that could be all right.
So, okay, take a step back.
We're going to get the DNS set up so we can start to do some of that stuff.
And then I'm going to go use a Groffbot to do research on finding people
that we can reach out to.
So I'll tell Dr. Eggbot.
I need a new Groffbot for doing research on finding restaurateurs or businesses
that could help us host our pop-up.
So let's think logistically end-to-end.
I think the first thing we need is perhaps a service that can make food.
And then the second thing is a location.
If we knew those two things, we could just get people once we have a date.
So really, the four things are first, people to help us.
Second, a date.
And then third, a location.
I think it might work best to start with a date.
Because if we have a date, then we can call people and say,
we're doing this thing on this day and we need your help.
So maybe if we're being conservative, what do you think?
Like a month in advance?
Say October 15th or something?
Maybe. Yeah, I think that's a good start point.
So we'll start with October 15th.
That'll ground our comms.
Take note of this in Notion because this is like kind of the business plan.
And then from there, what we're going to work towards is finding all of the types
of people in San Francisco in the Bay Area that could put on this sort of event,
whether that's a restaurateur or a catering company.
I'm going to connect Google Drive and we'll just make a list of that.
Or actually, you could make a new page in Notion.
We'll do with that there.
And then on top of that, what I want to do is I want to work on like researching the locations.
But let's start with that for now and dispatch bots as necessary so that we can start working
on this in parallel.
So we're showing Lauren's screen for right now just to keep things simple.
But on my end, I asked Dr. Eggbot basically to spin up some parallel while getting to,
like it seems like my bot is having trouble accessing the actual repositories.
Have you noticed anything with like flinginess there if I need to restart?
Okay, cool.
I'll try to re-opt your GitHub.
Yeah, I'll try re-althing.
Sometimes, yeah.
I can also sometimes help them install the GitHub CLI on its computer.
True, true.
If you try to use that, then it'll...
Okay, so I think what will...
I think I just might have used the wrong connector.
That's probably it.
So I think our first feature will be to help Matt.
So for context, Steve, what we're going to try to do with our startup idea here is we're
going to try to build out the platform through dogfooding, meaning that we will actually
do the work of getting this pop-up set up and then building tools that make that easier.
So we can actually dogfood the experience of using our tools ourselves and only build
it when we feel like it's good.
So I feel like the first part of this pop-up is we probably want to start with just like
maybe the location.
So I want you to help me using potato mode and I guess maybe ask Tater to spawn a cloud
agent to do this.
But I want to create a bunch of prototypes for a tool that helps us find restaurants.
And the tool should make it really easy for us to make phone calls.
Maybe we want to do some sleuthing as well of like maybe on LinkedIn or something.
I don't know how to search for that.
But some way to actually look up the people behind the restaurant so we can get in touch
with the manager or someone like that and figure out if they'd be willing to work with
us.
So basically it's like a tool to, I imagine something like a map on the screen and like
a search function that you can kind of search for things by cuisine or location and very
quickly make phone calls.
So this doesn't need to look very good.
It's just like a little tool for us right now.
And you build these prototypes for us.
Man, these prompts are super long.
There's two minutes of me talking.
And as usual I'm going to say restate in your own words before executing.
I wonder if there's a quick way to try and prototype the call to business idea.
How did you do the phone number thing?
I used the bland MCP for a business idea call thing.
But it seems like potato's on it.
And then also rather than, while you guys are trying to build this out, I actually just
pulled some different kitchen productions in GrokBot.
So I have like 15 restaurants that do caterers that are good at cooking stuff.
And so we have basically a short list of places I can call.
We can start to look for actual locations, which I also have my bots doing.
And then also wiring up email simultaneously.
Yeah.
I guess we'll need to figure out how to get a Google Maps key.
So you can help us.
Yeah, let me see if I can find out.
And you're thinking mostly so we can show location information in the UI.
That's what I'm imagining is like a tool to, because I just imagine you're starting a problem.
One of the most important things is location.
So you want to be able to quickly find good places.
And it'd be nice if you could do this on the platform.
Because then it's hooked up to all of our different pieces.
So I don't know.
Maybe OpenStreetMap could be another good free, is that free alternative?
Yeah, I think it is.
Maybe we could start with that.
Yeah.
I think it's a little easier to get a key.
Do you want to ask an agent to do that?
Yeah, I'll do it.
Okay, cool.
It also might be cool.
Should we try and build a places directory?
We could look at various place or location marketplaces.
You mean like known locations?
Yeah, that are good for pop-ups.
We could eventually build a directory system around it.
Oh, I want to get a list of places that are good for pop-ups.
Yeah, places that we know are good.
And then once you host an event there, you could rate it or something.
And we could build a little bit of that later on.
Sure.
Okay, I'm going to try to hack this up real fast.
And then, Matt, you can tell me if it's helpful or not.
Yeah, in the meantime, I'm just finding some places that maybe I'll start calling.
And we can just see if we can maybe do it in the manual way.
And then I'll say, how are we going to do auth?
I don't want to worry about that yet.
But maybe we need to.
I think we do need to do this.
Because I do want to lock this admin dashboard so it's just only accessible by Matt.
Yeah, cool.
Yeah, so what I'm doing is rather than going the software approach while we're working on
that, I'm actually taking the bot approach.
So what I'm working on is, can I just get a bot that goes and finds 20 businesses and
then gets their emails and their phone numbers?
And so I'll have those, and then we can start reaching out to them manually.
These I think, like finding a caterer that's maybe available for an event in a month, that
seems feasible to me.
Finding a location might be a little bit harder.
So we'll find a caterer, we'll find a location, and then I'm also working on getting our
email configured so then we can hook up some easy signups to our website.
I could just start like a WorkOS account or something if we wanted to do that.
I'm just going to sign in by GitHub, make it simple.
That works.
And only the three.
Although not everyone is going to want a restaurant, maybe has a GitHub account, but maybe we
could do sign in with Google.
I think we can iterate.
You want to build your own OAuth management, I think.
No, no, no, we're going to use something like Clerk.
Okay, yeah, make sense, yeah.
Do we need a Clerk account?
I guess, yeah, we do.
Is WorkOS easier?
Clerk, Clerk works too, I think either one.
Yeah, it's something I can do as well.
Which one is just like cheaper?
It looks like a cheaper one.
Looks like Clerk has a nice hobby tier.
And only the three of us should be able to add.
And Clerk has an MTP that looks like it'll kind of make this very agent-forward.
Yeah.
I'll just start building on Clerk and then we can adjust that if we need to.
I think Vercel also has a thing where you can do like very simple auth.
Really?
Actually, let me just...
Auth indication and user provisioning, they do have this, yeah.
Yeah, there's a SAML option.
I don't allow team members to log in with an identity provider.
Yeah, but then we need like...
Yeah, we can turn that on.
I feel so.
Yeah.
Is that what we need?
I think that's what we need, right?
Yeah, I'm just trying to keep it like super scrappy for now.
That's team members, yeah.
Because I don't even know if this prototype is going to be any good.
So I don't want to like overbuild it.
Let's see.
I mean, so this is going to be just dumb auth.
Maybe we can just do it for...
Yeah, we can just use Vercel deployment protection, I think, for the prototype.
Yeah, let's just do that.
Cool.
While you guys are working on that, I'm going to just see if we can create some interesting
collateral here that I want to share.
So I'm going to spin up a bot that just looks for like maybe the most common 50 street
corners in SF where we can go advertise this and maybe like talk to my design bot to make
some flat...
Yeah, we can put up or something like that.
Yeah.
Try and do some guerrilla marketing maybe.
Let's do it, man.
See what we can come up with.
In the meantime, I'm still cooking on the landing page, so we're polishing that up
a little bit.
Lots of API key creation, dang.
Yeah, that's the environment setup.
Yep.
I mean, good call out, right?
I think a lot of people are always like, oh, how do I automate this?
You know, how do I...
Like, there are some things that are still kind of manual, which is like, you know,
you have to go create an API key and we're working on getting to the point where maybe
that's not manual.
But yeah, there's a lot of work behind the scenes.
Okay, in the parallel, we have our verification PR.
PR up.
And I'm just going to actually read it for now.
It looks good.
I can hear people shuffling in.
We must be getting close to our next session.
I feel like your bots are posting a notion because it's helping my bots get context on
the business.
Oh my gosh, I should make sure.
The notion is our source of truth.
I need to see what's going on.
Okay, okay, okay.
Well, I just started a new bot and I was like, we're going to go with October 15th, right?
And I feel like...
Okay, now I'm going to have my Dr. Egg bot.
We're going to create a...
What do you call someone that just works on...
What do you call on someone that would just work on documentation?
Like, who's documenting the process?
Technical writer.
Okay, create a technical...
Or a knowledge base or something like that, knowledge base person.
What would the bot do?
It's going to groom notion for us and just keep track of what we're working on.
Create knowledge base manager.
The job of this bot is to watch all the other conversations with my bots, but not do anything
unless it's specifically called on, actually.
You should wait for messages to come to you, the knowledge base manager.
And then we want to update notion selectively.
We don't want to dump all the information in there, so check with me first.
And I'll use the queue to keep notion up to date.
Okay, cool.
So my knowledge base manager is going to keep notion up to date.
Cool.
I'm not working with Pixel.
Do we have a design system we've established yet?
No, but I'm working on getting something live.
It's hella minimalist.
Oh, I kind of like that.
It's like nothing.
If you go to...
Oh, it's not deployed yet.
I'll slack you, Lauren.
Maybe it's your screenshot or something.
Yeah.
I mean, there's a bunch of really good component libraries we can just use.
It'd be cool to pick a design system because that way...
I'm trying to make some flyers.
It would be nice if we could...
Yeah, I mean...
We don't even know what our design branding and all that...
Random checks.
We'll see a new item plan.
I think we should just...
I'll just rip on it.
But we could do...
I mean, we could do base UI or something and then like, send and build stuff out.
But it'll be pretty...
I think at this point, yeah, we're so early in the stage that...
I wouldn't worry about it.
It's not gonna look cool.
Actually, yeah, I'll make some changes here.
Don't worry.
Okay.
If you were just joining us, we are working on building our pop-up business in San Francisco.
Our pop-up business is going to...
Yeah, we're gonna throw a pop-up.
We think it's gonna be a food pop-up.
We've been riffing on ideas throughout the morning.
We have several teams of bots that are currently cooking on everything from a design system
to a landing page to building some architecture.
We're trying to really focus on a way to validate the solution pretty quickly.
I'm working on some Grilla marketing with a marketing bot.
And yeah, that's where we are.
Yeah.
I'm doing some website design.
Did a little bit of...
Collected some businesses I might call in my free time.
But we've got to get a lander up that we can send you all.
So our goal is to just get our lander up and also start documenting what we're doing.
And so, yeah, we're just really spinning tools up as we go here.
Lauren is mostly on the engineering side building up some tooling.
And I'm working on just kind of like the ad hoc side getting things stood up.
Cool.
So you do have design system stuff.
Maybe we could also put that in Notion at some point, too.
But yeah, we'll cook up there.
Maybe the repo might be the source of truth.
Yeah, that's right.
Heaven design system in the monoraypo.
Maps.
I was thinking I want to set up some lint rules.
Although I don't know if that's a little bit too early.
But I want to start thinking about the code quality.
I'm torn because it's just a prototype.
I don't think it's worth adding.
Normally it sounds like that's something you think about up front.
But maybe in this case, we're just trying to move rules.
Yeah, because it doesn't hurt for me to add it later and refactor things.
It's easier to do that than to try to...
Because I think the challenge always with engineering is like,
especially in a startup setting, is you can try to predict and over-engineer things that you might need.
But then it ends up that you actually don't need it.
Or maybe we figure out, knock on wood, we figure out this plan is not even good and then we pivot.
Yeah.
So I don't know if we want to...
I keep talking about over-cooking.
Yeah.
So I'm trying to strike a good balance.
I don't really know if we need that right now.
But maybe tomorrow we definitely want to start looking at it.
Especially once the PRs start coming in.
I'll start looking and reviewing the code and seeing where agents are making mistakes.
And something I talk about a lot on X is this idea that your code base is a form of memory.
So how you design your code base in terms of your architecture,
the constraints that you impose with your text that go a long way in helping your agents to be just smarter by default.
I'm even tempted.
I don't know if we want to overdo this.
Maybe it might be fun to do it.
It's like we just try to pick the strictest text that possible.
Maybe rewrite everything in Rust.
Should we do it?
There's nothing that exists.
Should we do it all in Rust?
Maybe not the restaurant plan here.
Maybe not the landing page.
The UI might be...
I mean, there are ways to put it in Rust.
But I don't know if we'll want the pain.
I think certainly for some backend pieces, maybe we could use Rust or even Go, I guess.
Hey, I'm relying on my CTO.
My CTO would do it when they need CTO.
We do have some TypeScript already.
I think agents love TypeScript.
Agents love TypeScript.
I want to see if we can...
I actually don't like Go as a Go-lang to write.
I think it's actually a great language for agents.
Rust is also good, of course.
But then the compile times are really slow.
And I don't want to slow us down too much.
Let me just do some research as well.
My bot is asking for what our flyer headline should be.
So I'm going to get some crowdsourced opinions here.
Should it be A, one night October 15th,
two, SF pop-up October 15th,
three, dinner finds you,
or D, I'll write my own.
D, I'll write my own.
I think we need to start from what people want.
What are we selling?
I think it's easy to get carried away with the features.
Nobody cares about our pop-up yet.
We have to make them care about our pop-up.
So what is unique about this pop-up?
I think what's unique is that we're doing it live in real time.
This is a new experience.
You get to be a part of something that we're creating with AI,
but nobody really cares also that we're telling them that we're making it with AI.
Honestly, nobody wants to hear that.
So my thing would be, how do we make people feel like
they're trying something new?
Maybe headline, when was the last, this is, I can't, Darius Rucker,
when was the last time you did something for the first time?
I'm a total, you know, everybody's hating you for saying that,
but maybe when was the last time you were spontaneous?
Like headline, when did you last try something new?
And I feel like that would get people's attention.
And then follow-up, now is your opportunity,
unique restaurant pop-up coming in San Francisco.
Does that make sense?
I love it. Let's do it.
Interesting.
I feel like really try to evoke emotion with like,
oh, you know what, my life is boring.
I like it.
By the way, I also got an initial pass of the maps,
of the street corners, if you want to pull up Slack for a second.
Should we make the pop-up Grokbot theme?
Oh, I have some, I don't know,
it could be interesting to have some secret Grokbot merch
that will drop at this thing.
And maybe that's something you'd build into the platform as well.
I guess you have incentives for people to show up.
Because I think part of the appeal of a pop-up to me is the time factor,
and it's like exclusivity.
The whole point of it being cool that it's a pop-up is that it's a one-time, one-day thing.
Yeah, it's a do-it-time thing.
So there's this element of, there's time.
And there's something in limited supply.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I feel right.
Kind of like thinking that made,
could we think of unique things that we'd each want to bring to the pop-up
to make it feel like it kept to that?
Personally, I would love some cool Grokbot merch.
Yeah, merch.
Okay, so merch, yeah.
I think cool limited, limited time merch.
On a platform, people could tie that in with some other limited edition things.
And that could also drive a lot of traffic and interest in their pop-up.
I love social games, or kind of just like,
I think there's so many unique in-person interactions
that you can get out of an event like this when you bring people together.
And kind of think of it as a way we could even create some excitement ahead of time.
Or, you know, you're going to participate in a bit of an experience,
or a bit of a game, or something like that maybe when you're on site.
I kind of tease that.
So I don't know, I can play with that idea a little bit.
Okay, sick, makes sense. I like that a lot.
I'm still wiring up some keys here, so before I get completely distracted,
we're going to do it.
We're over here brainstorming.
Content switching is insane.
I'm like, I just forgot what this key is for.
Cool.
I think I have at least an early pass of our flyer marketing campaign, guys.
I'm excited for you to take a look when you're ready.
Okay.
I made a marketing channel on Slack for us, by the way.
Oh, sorry.
We need some organization.
Alright, you know what, I'm just going to stick with TypeScript.
I don't want to waste time.
Do we have a video of the...
I don't love the flyer attempts yet.
So let's get the video, and I'll share it in Slack,
and you can tell me whether you love it or hate it.
But there's something I really love about Cloud Agents
is that they produce, they can just produce videos for you.
It's so cool.
So I can tell...
And they post them talk automatically too, right?
Not automatically, but you can tell it too.
Oh, right, yeah.
They do, if they do create a video, they do post it,
they include it in the PR description.
So it's really nice because then you can just review
and you can get a really nice...
Let me see if it included.
It didn't include it here, so I may need to tell it.
And also I think our verification skill
hasn't told it to actually use this.
I'll include videos.
So I'm going to say, let's update our verification skill
to be the way it's applied.
I know this has a visual by power.
Sweet.
On my end, I got domain verification hooked up on Resend
so that'll be nice for checking DNS,
making some emails, getting stuff shipped out here.
Cool.
Do you want to see some of the designs I started cooking?
I don't know if I love this yet.
But this is cool.
Yeah, I like that.
Yeah, I like that designs, I really buy it more minimalist.
So what we might be able to do, just work on the flyer
and then once I have this done, you can just be like,
yo, pull the design from the repo.
So use the repo as the source of truth for the code system.
Is that already checked in?
No.
My very minimalist situation here is going to go live.
Awesome.
I just have to auth some GitHub CLI stuff
because I'm still having some weird issues.
Enter device code.
Wow, this prototype is really, is really prototyped.
It's not even, it's just vanilla HTML and JavaScript.
It's fine, we can refactor.
Important thing is to keep moving and to iterate.
So let's just get it, get it up and running first.
Agree.
Where do we think we're gonna land by like 230? I think the next talk is at 230.
This is a good call out.
Yeah, I think we're just kind of sprinting through some of these,
some of these kind of tasks.
It's mostly for me connecting things.
I'm still getting a little set up and then we're gonna iterate on the design.
And I think I might try like a manual, maybe by this talk, a manual like,
hey, I'm gonna call some people while we're off camera and just see like how hard it is to book some of these things.
Yeah.
That might be, that also might inform what we need to automate a little bit.
Well, I already have my prototype being built.
So maybe you can try that later.
Oh, okay.
And we can see, and we can iterate if it's not good.
You can tell me what to fix.
Cool.
And I'm gonna try and get at least like a bare, the bones of a marketing plan and like a gorilla marketing campaign set up.
And some flyers and designs and stuff too.
So we might have to, you're saying we might have to hire some people to put up flyers?
I think that sounds great.
Just ask, grab and have an MTP.
I actually know some people so...
Oh, great. Even better.
Does Matt have an MTP?
And how do we want to think about the limited edition thing that we show in addition to...
Oh, and the experiential parts of the...
Yeah, I can work on that too and coming up with the experiential thing.
I actually was working with the marketing, but we have a marketing section in Ocean now with all the ideas we can consider.
So merch is another one of those, right?
Yeah, sounds good.
What else can I do to unblock?
Can you talk me through like what you'll be thinking about when you are looking for venues?
Like what's important to you?
Yeah, so, you know, when I run an event, really what is an event?
But an event is like making people feel a certain way.
And so you want to think about all the things you can control into that experience.
So it's like, okay, I've got to find a venue that can accommodate our guests.
So we'd start by, I think, how many guests do we want to have?
I think 100 maybe.
Just sounds like a good spot to start.
It's like, okay, can we have a...
It's also like a nice round number.
Can we get 100 people together in San Francisco?
And the space should both accommodate those people and then also kind of allow us to control the environment and the experience.
That's a good point, yeah.
I know places.
Like we should start maybe with human knowledge.
Like in my neighborhood, the Pearl, really great spot for hosting events.
I live in like, Potrero Hill dog patch area.
Dog patch studios is also a really great event space.
And so what I would do is I would like pattern match.
Like I've walked around these places in my neighborhood.
Can I find places that look similar to these venues?
And what I noticed is that some of my bots even kind of recommended, hey, you should look at these venues.
So based on that, I might be able to kind of like bootstrap a skill or some sort of like some sort of context that my bots can start to use.
Okay, that helped.
Is that yeah, cool.
A lot of context.
I guess budget is also important.
Budget is an important, and we haven't talked about that.
I guess we won't know until we make the call, right?
We do not know.
I mean, you can do some market research on this too and just get a feel for like cost.
Cool. I mean, I'm putting all this stuff in Notion.
So I have like my host finder dumping all the research in Notion and I'm also looking at permits.
Oh, nice. Oh, great. Okay.
And so permitting, it seems like the hardest part would be getting some street closures.
And if we want to sell alcohol, which I mean, I didn't say it was that much of a party, but maybe it's not.
It sounds like we might be looking like several weeks to a month in advance.
So I think a month out is potentially tight, but I think we could be we could do it.
So maybe like as we start to evaluate dates, we think, OK, do we push this six weeks out?
Right. So we have time for some of these some of these permits, because even like I'm looking up here is like Fort Mason,
another really great venue to host events.
The initial review takes four to fifteen business days and a construction to weeks.
So like, I mean, that's like a public for Mason is owned by the park service. Right.
But that's like a good like bar.
I mean, this occurred to me. Yeah.
Well, like I'm kind of an optioning, but I guess now I'm actually thinking about the Notion use case.
That's actually usually you have your writer about because I'm thinking like there's so much context.
Yeah. That we were sharing right now.
Yeah. It's kind of just going over our voices.
Should we be recording this? Yeah, I don't know.
Like I would love for it to just go into our company notion so that I can just point my bots to them and just say, here's all the things that Matt's already looked at.
OK, it's like it's like there's a brainstorming meeting and because that is really good input for engineering.
So I can rather than me just interrupting all the time if you have that documented somewhere.
OK, what I'll do is I'm going to tell my knowledge base manager every five minutes, ping the active bots, extract all the most important details and drop it in notion.
So I'm setting up a job and I think that the struggle here is going to be make sure making sure we don't get a ton of like spam in notion.
But we'll try and keep it. Yeah, it's like like a get log almost.
OK, cool. And I'm going to talk to the host finder and I'll say what I just said.
So I think the most important thing when finding a venue is to start from what we know, try to pattern match on high quality and then work backwards.
So, for example, I know that the Pearl is an awesome place.
I know that Dogcrash Studios is awesome and you've recommended those.
And I would avoid government run or NPS facilities because we're going to need like a month.
So maybe start from things similar to the Pearl or Dogcrash Studios based on what I know from my neighborhood.
And then we can try to find venues with a caterer or venue that has an alcohol license,
because what I see my agents recommending me right now is we can't get the alcohol license.
We should push the caterer, the vendor to do that.
And then we don't have to worry about it.
And then based on some of these other considerations, maybe we can also start to to thin out basically all the logistics that we need to work through and focus.
Cool. OK, Matt, we never got your what you wish you could bring to the event.
But I wish I could bring to the event.
So we have experiential games.
We have merch.
We have to finish the trifecta.
What's your answer?
I mean, we got to have just good food.
Like, I mean, that's like I'm working on the restaurant.
Limited edition food.
Oh, so I mean, it is limited edition because it only happens once.
So I think the menu is really important.
So like maybe we have a grok bot that can I want to leave the creative freedom up to the restaurateur.
But maybe we can design some cocktails or design some fun menu elements or something that they can build in.
So we can work on the men.
Cool. I just recorded that and cut it to a box.
Being recorded. I love it.
Let's spin up a menu bot.
Come on, where is the video?
I always try this page up.
I might actually run with that menu idea a little bit.
I might.
Since I'm since I'm apparently the geoscraper guy, first of three quarters,
I think I'm now going to like just ping a bunch of like search for a bunch of menu concepts and see what we can do.
Thank you.
I'm sure I'll go what I'm doing with the video.
Cool. So I'm asking bot to kind of go through the Internet, like go through Yelp and a few other spots to look for top rated items from other restaurants.
And so I might give us some inspiration here.
Are we also set on the restaurant as the concept?
Could it be?
I think we're almost going generic pop up at this point, right?
Because I guess one complication is the restaurant is like you need to have a chef.
You have some staff or a caterer.
I think a catering company would handle that.
But that is complicated to your point.
Yeah. But if you're thinking like, I mean, if we could be like art exhibition, I don't know, it could be art exhibition sounds interesting because we could crowdsource.
Our crowdsource artists or something.
Actually, I think the art exhibition would be more interesting.
And we still like we could sell more than 100 tickets.
We could get people to submit art and like build us off.
We could have our bots review the art.
Like this. I like this.
Because I'm just wondering, like maybe the finding a restaurant is like hard and it's like all the food stuff.
There's a lot of food. Maybe it's like a whole weekend license.
We need licensing. We need licensing.
That's what I was just discussing with the bot.
So I'm actually fine.
I think pivoting like, well, let's like try to lock it.
If we're going to pivot on the idea, like let's confirm, like we're just going to like call it what it is.
I think I like an art exhibition.
And then we source local artists and then, you know, maybe there's a way that they can show off their art.
But then, you know, we have to think about the difference with a restauranteurs.
Like we just pay the restauranteurs and then we collect money from people.
Yeah. Now we're like paying dozens of artists to do a gallery or something.
Maybe instead of paying them, we're sort of like creating an exhibition space.
And then we're also doing some community art submissions where folks can submit art that they've created.
What I would really love to see is like, I mean, since we are doing Groff Bot stuff,
like a lot of people really love the Groff Bot avatars, the shapes and all.
They're really fun.
We could have artists that make art about, you know, like paintings or something about Groff Bot and feature them.
Yeah. And then we could even make like an interactive like on the website.
Yeah, that we can help them tell friends as well.
Yeah, exactly. Help them tell friends.
And you can like explore the art gallery digitally and then like come and see it in person.
Like see the real thing.
That'd be interesting.
I think that all sounds really nice.
Yeah.
Because at least that removes the hurdle of like licensing.
I feel like that's going to be by this like...
I really like this.
Food and liquor license.
Yeah.
Oh well, so just to be clear, like we just find a caterer that has those things.
I think all we really need is event insurance and then you just work with the venue and then,
you know, we're good.
So I think we can figure that part out.
Or we can, you know, call one of our event friends and get some advice.
Yeah, absolutely good.
Okay, I'm going to have to leave you guys now.
So it turns out the next talk is one that I'm presenting.
Oh my goodness.
So I'm going to jump down and get prepped for Grokbot for PM.
Amazing.
Where we'll like walk through some of this stuff live.
But I feel like I like where this idea session is.
Sounds great, Roshan.
Thanks for building with us.
Good luck, dude.
You've already done a lot of talking.
I'm excited for it.
Absolutely.
It's kind of crazy how much stuff we're doing live in this space.
There's like the stage downstairs.
There's this space upstairs.
There's like meetings back there that we keep hearing.
So yeah, it's a fun vibe.
Yeah, we're physically in San Francisco doing stuff.
And there are things happening.
Yeah, all around us.
All right, man.
Well, you just take off when we need to go.
Sounds good.
I will see you guys very soon.
All right, man.
Good luck.
So we can find venues for different types of pop-up.
For now, the only type in search for are,
I guess the nice thing about an art exhibition as well
is like any space would do, right?
Well, so again, those venues that I mentioned
that I've seen in real life, like when you took a look,
like they're very flexible.
And you actually kind of want more of like a warehouse space.
Mixed use spaces, I guess.
Yes, they're really just a big open space, I think.
Right.
OK, so I'm just telling Steve about our change of plan.
Cool.
But I'm still going to work on the venue finder
and then get it over to you.
Sweet.
And you can give me feedback.
Cool.
Yeah, and I'm just working on the,
right now I'm working on the UI.
So I'll have like, ship by Thursday will not look
like a horrible neon mess.
A horrible AI slot mess.
Well, we will have some SpaceX AI employees,
really cracked engineers who are really good at design.
We'll come and help this.
I'm not too worried about that.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
As long as it's not like, you know, too terrible.
If it's in term, we'll have something that looks a little bit more consistent.
Yeah.
OK, we have some PRs up that I need to review.
PRs are stacking up.
OK, nice.
Our verification skill is a bit more generic, yeah.
So that's PR 16.
16 has been e-valent.
And then PR 14, I guess we're still waiting on the videos.
What is PR 13?
We already have 13 PRs.
Look at that.
We have so many PRs.
Where are these coming from?
Oh, these are, oh, OK, I see.
There's a bunch of different prototypes that it's opening.
I have them now.
I forgot I asked it to make some prototypes.
So it's going to open a bunch of PRs.
I have a knowledge base bot that's like, updating our Slack and like,
Oh, really?
putting in all these different things.
Is it saying anything?
Oh, we got a marketing channel.
Oh my gosh.
That's top 50 flyer corners.
We're changing to consider doing an art pop up rather than some sort of dining experience.
We're changing to have an art pop up rather than some sort of dining experience.
I do like some of the top ones there.
But really, I think we should sort of optimize now for just a large warehouse space.
And I think actually, part of what I'm doing, the research could be good for your tool.
Because if your tool tells me the same things that I'm already coming to myself,
that's how we can know that it's working.
Yeah, part of me wonders if like the tool could just be a search like,
like maybe I don't know if we really need to build that.
I think the search part, we don't really need to reinvent the wheel there.
We can just use like, Google Map APIs for that.
But we can add like layers on top to find filter more by more specific criteria,
like the venue size and all that that's probably not available on Google Maps.
Which also means we might need to actually collect information.
So one thing actually will be interesting as you make your calls is like if there's a way to
do some data entry after, once you get the details.
Like CRM type situation?
Kind of like so like we have future info,
like the venue finder gets smarter as you use it.
As we will have information about venue and I don't know people call.
Yeah, I might have to take that down manually.
I have to check on call.
Yeah, yeah, take it on a manual for now and then I'll kind of see if we can kind of hook that up.
Okay, cool.
The docs are up.
I'm updating docs.
It's my job now.
My job now is updating docs.
Who knew it all ends with docs.
So my factory, mini factory is going at least.
I got my engineer bot working and my verifier bot very busy reviewing PRs.
They're missing videos and screenshots, which I want.
So I can actually see what they built.
So we're going to have Steve drive this to completion.
Sweet.
Still reading on, I think recent is we have email technically.
So we're going to be able to send like email from like hello,
I trip by Thursday when you sign up on the waitlist,
at least like some sort of confirmation email and then everything will still get
routed into your database.
So that'll be nice.
Just updating some of the copy.
We can merge that in soon.
So it looks like we have about three, four minutes left.
Oh, good call.
Yeah.
Um, we probably want to give a shout out for the
Grokbot challenge again.
Yeah, totally.
As we transition to the next talk.
Do you want to give a shout out for the Grokbot challenge?
Uh, sure.
If I remember the Grokbot galaxy challenge.
Is that on the paper there?
I mean, no, but I remember what the Grokbot galaxy.
Maybe you should do it because I'll probably say it wrongly.
The live stream challenge, which is that if you can,
can you pull actually up the challenge on x.
Oh yeah.
If you pull that up so our folks can see and probably go to the bot page.
Might have some details on there.
Oh my gosh, seeing tweets about us.
Yeah, we scroll down.
Not on the live stream because I'll get like, oh no, we're gonna.
No, I think it's on Grok.
Yeah, it's on Grok.
So the live stream challenge, submit templates for Grokbot.
And we're going to get you and the winner out there.
The winner and a partner out to Starbase Texas to see a Starship launch.
So you and a plus one, most creative template.
See some rockets, some pretty cool video.
Our team makes some pretty cool videos.
And yeah, we're going to announce the winner soon.
In roughly two and a half minutes, we got Grokbot for product managers
with someone who was just sitting right next to me.
I don't know how he's doing it.
Like building a business and doing a top.
I have no idea.
These are high achievement.
You can tell that was it he grew up playing?
He said, was it Age of Empires?
Yeah, he's just crushing.
Multitasking.
Yeah, so we got two minutes and we're going to head over there.
We're just going to keep hacking.
I think Lauren and I got a good approach in the meantime.
Yeah, reviews.
Because what my agents are doing.
We have a lot of PRs and agents.
Let me group by status.
And we have a that's not good.
He's all stuck.
No, I think they're still working.
On to the start thinking.
Rainstorm.
Thinking we need cool project users can.
It's been fun.
Are we on?
Get going.
Okay, let's do it.
Hello, everybody.
Welcome to Grokbot for product managers or PMs.
Very excited to see you all.
We got many on the live stream as well.
I'm Kevin DeParco from the SpaceX AI product team.
Joined by.
And I'm Roshan Sothani also on the SpaceX AI product team.
Really excited to be chatting with y'all today.
Cool.
We are going to be going through how we have been building
Grokbot with Grokbot.
Some of the tips, the tools,
the bots that we have found very useful across our product org.
And so I wanted to start with the backdrop,
which I think everybody in this room on the stream knows.
If you have been building software, if you're a PM,
obviously the craft is changing very rapidly.
It becomes now very easy to code, to build things, to prototype.
Way more accessible than it ever has been before.
And I like this quote from DHH.
The developer's developer, one of the creators of Ruby on Rails,
who says, software is product management.
What should it do?
Who should it do it for?
How should it do it?
How should it look?
What are the priorities?
These are questions that now every product builder,
whether you're formally engineer or designer or founder or product manager,
really has to grapple with as you start to build software for your customers, for your users.
Yeah.
So with that, we thought we'd spend just a second talking about the motivation behind
RockBot because in some ways, RockBot is the product we've also made.
And so there's a story to it having been built,
just the same way there's a story to every product having been built.
And I think if you think back to sort of what motivated RockBot in the early, early days,
it was realizing that, you know, at least internally within SpaceX AI,
there are so many folks who were starting to evolve beyond a chat box.
And I think there's been a lot of discourse about this,
maybe some of you all have felt this or read about it as well.
But really, it started to feel increasingly that agents weren't quite as home in a chat box as we
might have wanted them to be.
I think a lot of this was just a natural evolution of how we started interacting
with these large language models and sort of, you know, going from asking for a response
and maybe waiting for some text to asking agents to drive outcomes.
And so obviously, we saw a lot of this outcome-based agentic development happen
when it comes to things like coding agents.
But, you know, as more and more of us internally started thinking about that beyond coding,
it felt like the chat box was a little bit limiting.
And so we started exploring, you know, all kinds of ways that we might want to chat and
work with agents and have them complete tasks and have access to systems that
really go beyond the chat box.
And, you know, the most common thing that kept coming up in all of these conversations
was that we kept sort of treating our agents as if they were colleagues.
We wanted to be able to interact with them as if they were sort of these smart
colleagues that sat next to us at our desks or were messageable in Slack or had access to
linear to look at tickets or, you know, wrote PRDs with us in Notion or whatever it is.
And so a lot of the motivation behind how RockBot was evolved and kind of why it is the way it is
today is grounded in this idea that, you know, we should really have these agentic
colleagues that we can work with on all the great things we do when we build products.
And so that was really the motivation.
So really, I think there's four things that we kind of took as a brief based on that
colleague definition.
The first one is that colleagues, when you work with them, often tie multiple tools together.
They don't live in one system.
They work across many systems.
And those systems do different things, right?
So you might have a ticketing system, like I mentioned, linear or something like it.
You might be using, you know, CRM or CRM++, you know, something like Salesforce or more.
You might be keeping documents in Notion, designs in Figma.
And all these tools are really, really great at what they do.
But oftentimes your colleagues or, you know, yourselves are tying things together across them.
The other things here are that these colleagues often have long running context.
They learn and they don't just, you know, work on a task,
eject the task and then move on.
The best colleagues you work with, the best teammates you work with,
they learn on the job, right?
Maybe they start out with very little company context.
You teach them some tasks or teach them how to get some work done.
They kind of do some work.
You give them some feedback, right?
That wasn't that great.
They hopefully take the feedback and then get better at their jobs.
We think that model generalizes to agents too, where agents can really,
you know, the way that the models have evolved, get good at learning,
at sort of building memory for themselves, at realizing what's important,
and at taking and incorporating that kind of feedback.
The third thing, and I think this is a really big one, is independence.
I think for a lot of, whoops, we lost the slides.
Let's go fix that.
There we go.
For a lot of people we work with, they go execute things independently, right?
Once in a while, maybe you'll get asked for,
hey, I need some help on blocking a task,
or, you know, maybe someone gets stuck with access to a system or something like this.
But really, the defining property of a colleague that you work with,
one of the defining properties is that they can work on their own,
they can complete tasks on their own, and they have their own access.
This is really what motivated the need for GrokBot to have its own computer.
We decided GrokBot should have its own computer that I can do things in.
This is true, and this is how the product works today.
If you go in and use GrokBot, GrokBot has its own computer,
you can kind of help it when it gets stuck on that computer,
but it has its own surface where it can create the output
that you need to get assisted in your work.
The last and final thing I'll call out here is messaging.
Earlier, I mentioned that it felt like we wanted to move beyond
the chat box a little bit, but I meant that a little bit tongue-in-cheek.
The chat box that defines how you interact with a large language of model.
We think that the core premise makes a lot of sense.
Where it started to feel a little bit constrained is that usually when you're chatting with a
colleague, you're like rapid-fire messaging.
If you're like me in Slack, or maybe like us in Slack, you're constantly streaming out
messages, you're switching between threads, you're multitasking.
We found that rather than having to wait your turn for the next response, that it's a lot
more engaging if you can just really jump in, interrupt, drive, and interact with agents
in this way.
You'll see a little bit of this in a minute.
But really, I think those are the four things that we found as we built this product and
played with it internally that define how colleagues work.
I love those four things.
It's not just like any colleague.
It's like really trying to encode the best colleagues that you have worked with.
They have a ton of context about the organization.
They understand and can learn on the job.
They can move independently, make their own decisions.
They're not constantly waiting for you.
And so yeah, I think this is like the high level of how we think about what GrokBot is.
It's an agent with a computer at the end of the day, and it feels like texting a colleague.
Exactly, yeah.
And I think there's two things here that if you want to sort of take away with you as
to what GrokBot can do.
It's these two things on the slide here.
We want these GrokBots to be AI teammates that you can get real work to and then come back
with results.
They don't come back with text, or they don't come back with questions.
They come back with results.
And then I think the last thing here is that they really finish jobs.
We think that really being able to get the job done is a much more productive way to
interact with agents and come back when they need approval.
So yeah, I'm curious, how do we use these with products?
Absolutely.
So we are actually going to see GrokBot in the wild, a real demo of some of the agents
that we have built, the colleagues that we work with in GrokBot.
I think there are really sort of three use cases that we're going to see here.
The first is what we call the attention list.
So as PMs, you're constantly pulled in a bunch of different directions.
Maybe you're working across a bunch of different projects, or there's a bunch of contexts everywhere.
And it is very helpful to think about what are you currently paying attention to?
What have you been paying attention to this morning, this week, this month?
And then really diff that against your priority list and help you understand how the ways
in which you're spending your time and where your focus is relative to what needs
to get done across the team.
And we're going to talk about how GrokBot can help you do that as this helpful assistant,
this colleague that's always on your shoulder, being able to learn about the ways in which
you're working.
The next is research and building up customer contacts.
Obviously, this is where a lot of product work goes into doing the research, figuring
out what users and customers actually need and want and love, what the biggest bottlenecks
are, what issues are they running into, how can you better serve them?
And so being able to gather up all that context, learn from your users, be able to synthesize
data in new ways, GrokBot is actually really phenomenal for.
And we're going to talk about some of the data science and analytics and product use
cases that we turn to GrokBot for.
And then, of course, shipping.
You cannot be a product manager in 2026 if you are not focused on delivering software
products to your customers.
And so really thinking about how GrokBot can not only accelerate you as a PM, but also
the entire team.
Yeah, there's a stat on the slide here.
GrokBot represents for us internally a double digit percentage of merged PRs.
And I think that's a pretty wild stat.
It also, within the product organization, empowers all of us as product people to be
able to ship PRs into production as well.
And so you just really get a bunch of superpowers when you can set up this in
the right way.
Very cool.
So let us, with that, meet the GrokBot team that we will be working with today.
Some familiar faces and names that we can all learn.
So first is Cora, Chief of Staff.
You can think of this as sort of the person that you turn to,
have access to your email, has access to your calendar, maybe listens on Slack for
some of the messages that you're sending, and really builds up a model of how you
as a PM actually work.
Next is Emily.
Emily is an engineering manager.
Emily has been coached not to actually do the coding, but
just to manage a team of engineers that we have given Emily.
And so Emily has five different engineering colleagues in GrokBot that she manages.
It's very helpful to have Emily as sort of this one contact across
the engineering team to be able to give larger chunks of work, have Emily then
deconstruct that and delegate that work, actually run the verification loops for
the outputs of some of the engineering agents.
We'll have Ashley, the go-to for data science, for
analytics, for being able to ask and answer data questions.
I think as a PM, oftentimes throughout the day, there is a random conversation
that sparks an idea that would have previously required you to go write
a bunch of SQL and figure out where the trusted data sources are.
And very helpful to have somebody that you can just quickly message and
get an answer, a chart, a synthesis of the underlying data set
that will help inform some of your decisions throughout the day.
We also have PM Pete.
PM Pete is a trusted sidekick for the product team,
being able to draft up some product requirement docs,
synthesize some of the customer and user insights, and
be able to run some of the lower level product work day to day.
You wanna talk about Pixel?
Yeah, Pixel's one of my favorites.
Pixel is a designer and so has been trained on some of the best advice for
how to be a world class AI designer.
It turns out that there are ways to make AI design look really good.
If you instruct your agents and bots in the right way.
And so Pixel's been loaded with a ton of context on how to be an S tier designer
from some of the best and latest thinking on the Internet.
Amazing, and finally we have Ray who is a recruiter.
So anybody who's in product leadership or
building out the product function or building out your company.
Very helpful to have a colleague that you can turn to on the people and
recruiting side of the house to help with some of the sourcing and
managing some of the hiring pipeline.
And so these are some of the very helpful Grokbot colleagues that we have defined.
But it is totally up to you exactly what your team is going to look like.
And so throughout the course of this demo, use this as inspiration,
use this for ideas.
But at the end of the day, you can construct your team,
figure out who is most helpful, what are the sets of roles that will be most
accelerative for you and your product team.
Yeah, definitely.
And I think to that point, what we've seen a lot of folks do is they create many
agents and so I wanted to spend a minute just talking about why we think that's
effective.
One is that I think while agents might have massive context windows that can
store entire novels, our brains, or at least my brain can't.
And so oftentimes we just wanna know who to reference and
it feels like a really natural pattern to assign roles to these agents
that correspond to how you'd interact with colleagues as we've talked about.
So having a person who's in charge of data, maybe they do the job of five data
people or assist with five data types of tasks in your organization, can be really
helpful for you invoking and working with those agents to know their role.
And so I find this really helpful just to know which bot I wanna talk to for
a given task and then sometimes their roles merge and that's okay.
We'll show you this, but bots can also talk to each other,
which is really cool and that can kinda coordinate in channels and stuff.
So we'll show that as an example too.
But the other reasons for having more than just one agent is that the bots
do perform better because when they can scope their memory down a little bit more,
just going back to the idea of continuous learning and evolution,
that learning loop we found functions a lot better when a bot is typed or
cast into a specific role.
And then the final thing is I think it's a little more fun and
a little easier to parallelize your work,
which you can kinda hand stuff off to a bunch of bots.
And so one pattern that we see a ton internally is folks who will fire off
messages to six different bots, you'll see them all spinning and working.
And they kinda all go and do some work for you and
you kinda come back and synthesize the results.
So again, sort of mirroring how you might work with colleagues.
Let's say we're in a meeting together, we assign a bunch of action items.
We all go off and do that work and then come back together and synthesize,
say, a plan.
The bots can really mimic that behavior and
I think it's also easier for us as humans to kinda know how we're steering them
when they do that.
All right, should we hop into the demo?
Let's do it.
Okay, a quick show of hands for those in the room.
I know those in the stream won't see this.
How many of you all have used or have a rock bot installed?
Okay, 80% of the room.
So for the 20% who have not seen it, I'm gonna do a very, very,
very quick tour showing you what we just walked through.
So this is rock bot, this is the interface.
It's a bunch of bots on the left and
you can see we can pin some bots up at the top.
We can group our bots into sections and so
we have a section here for leadership.
We have a couple of pin bots and then we have our engineering team that we just
talked about down here, Einstein, Igor, Nova, Larry, and Eileen.
You can also hide bots or unassign them if you'd like.
And then there's an entire marketplace where you can connect the tools that you
use to these bots to give them those superpowers that we talked about earlier.
So really the bots we found are incredibly effective when they have access to all
the tools that they're working on.
So in this case, we've set up a bunch of tools.
We have Notion Slack, Figma MCP, Gmail, and a few other things that are installed.
And that S-tier design skill that I talked about earlier is also stored here.
So we have that as part of our setup too.
These bots all function and work as a team.
And so earlier I mentioned we had the ways to group bots together.
You can see some examples of that here.
We have our EngPod here.
So you could imagine our engineering team doing a stand up.
Actually really fun if you get the bots into a room and
tell them to do a stand up on a project.
We have our EPD teams, our engineering product and design team.
For those of you who are in product organizations, obviously this is
how a lot of them function is with these three roles kind of acting as
a triumvirate.
And then maybe we have a war room, for example, with a bunch of bots to triage
an issue or handle an incident.
And really the sky's the limit here.
These are just some representative examples.
Yeah, that's our overall setup.
And just to remind you, we have Cora, who's our Chief of Staff up here.
PM Pete, who's our Product Assistant.
And then Ashley, who's our Data Scientist.
And you can see we have some queries we were running the other day kind of
looking at some of the funnels and data funnels for our product.
And maybe a good chance to explain what the product is.
So everything you're seeing here is tied to a demo environment we have set up for
a business called Fly Low Airlines.
It's an airline, just like any other airline might be.
And so yeah, we'll be talking about the airline business today.
Very good.
So everybody in this room on the live stream, you are all now PMs at
Fly Low, this amazing airline.
And why don't we jump into maybe a few questions that we might have
about the business.
And so we can turn to Ashley, who is our Data Science colleague here.
And we can ask how many people purchased tickets yesterday on mobile versus web.
I like that.
Yeah, I feel like product funnels are such an important part of development.
Like where are sales coming from?
Yeah.
And so under the hood, Ashley is connected to our data layer and
data warehouse.
This could be Databricks, Snowflake, pick your favorite data warehouse.
And what Ashley is going to go off and do is actually go generate these queries,
run these queries against that external data store, and come back to us with
looks like 1,400 tickets were purchased yesterday.
So it sounds like we are a small boutique airline here, which is very good.
And looks like about 58% were on web and 42% on mobile.
And we can see how many families were flying.
Typos are OK.
Help us visualize these with charts.
And while that's running, I actually find this as a product-to-product person
to be one of my favorite uses of Grokbot every day is I now get data
queries and charts on demand.
We haven't shown this yet, and we can, but you can also set up routines with bots.
So if you haven't seen that, that's a really, really helpful thing.
I wake up every morning, and for those of you who like to monitor your favorite
dashboards each morning, usually you're used to opening up a web browser,
navigating your dashboards, maybe you have a bunch of bookmarks you load.
This can all be pushed to you.
And so I have many, many daily queries.
Perhaps you're in charge of this pipeline at your business.
You can get these insights pushed to you every morning or on demand.
And so one thing that we've done for really major product launches
is actually ask for hourly reports on how things are going live from our data
store so you can truly track the progress of a launch, truly track where
people are getting stuck, and sort of build these really great experiences
out the gate.
So it looks like we got some data back.
Cool.
So this actually has actually generated the charts for us,
helping us understand the distribution of who's going solo, who's a couple,
who's a family, who's flying in groups.
And then also helping us understand what is this family share of ticket purchases.
Looks like 25% of flyers are family.
And so, yeah, as Roshan mentioned, we can make this a routine.
Send me this as an update every morning at 6 AM.
This can be the first thing in GrokBot that I check.
And I can get an updated pulse of these purchase behavior
and how many families are flying, which is kind of cool.
Yeah, I like that.
Now, I wonder if there's something we could do to make that experience better.
I don't know.
Are there any issues with the product we could try to find?
Yeah.
We should look into the.
Let's scroll up.
Let's look at that funnel.
Yeah, I did this earlier today, kind of just exploring how ticket purchases
might look like.
And so, asked Ashley to pull for us kind of what happens for folks
who are buying tickets on mobile.
So this looks like a pretty classic product conversion funnel, I think, right?
Yeah, very good.
And it looks like there is quite a bit of fall off in this funnel.
Yes, but interestingly, it looks like the fall off is happening
when people pick their seats.
Maybe they don't like our seat selections.
But this might be an opportunity for us to improve the product.
And so as you're working on your own products,
one thing that often happens is you see an insight into data.
And then you say, well, wait a minute.
Like, what's actually happening in the product here?
What can we do to fix that experience?
And so maybe we should write this back.
Let's do it.
So you can thread in chats.
Here we are going to reply to this message
that we got yesterday.
And we're going to say, looks like a big fall off
when people are choosing seats on mobile.
Work with PMP to generate a product spec
to optimize our mobile funnel.
And as you notice, Kevin here is tagging PMP.
So this is where the bots will be able to chat with each other.
And you'll see Ashley should fire off a message to Pete.
Pete has a lot of product context on our business,
understands our customers, understands the previous product
decisions that have been made, and so might
have some insight as to why this is the spot in the funnel.
And between the two of them, just like any great product
and data science combo, hopefully they'll
be able to come up with some good ideas here.
And it looks like, yeah, maybe should
we click into that message and see?
Yeah, yeah, before we go there,
I do love Ashley corrected us.
We were actually wrong in our interpretation of the data.
And so it says on mobile purchase funnel,
the big leak is actually search to fare selection, not seat
selection.
So we had misinterpreted the chart.
Luckily, Ashley caught our mistake here.
And you can see Ashley is sending a message off
to PMP with some of the insights
that she has generated through this investigation
and then the specific ask that they're
going to start to coordinate.
Yeah, and I see Pete spinning over there.
So I think doing something.
Cool.
It looks like Pete has a notion PRD with some P0s and P1s.
Let's see what he came up with.
OK.
Very cool.
And talk about the skill that PMP is
using to generate this PRD.
Yeah, so PMP has learned that the best PRDs, the best specs,
are really crisp in their requirements
and that increasingly they focus less
on longevity of the document and more
on what helps us get to code and prototype really quickly.
Maybe we've heard a lot about how code is getting cheaper
and cheaper each day.
And so Pete has a bunch of skills
that are trained into Pete's context that allow him to,
in this case, really understand the business.
And then when we're asking Pete for a PRD,
specify a really crisp set of P0, P1, and P2 requirements.
So it looks like we got a list.
What do we think?
Amazing.
Looks like Mobile Fair results needs a redesign here.
Faster Compare section are some of the ideas.
Honest, fair proof on the card.
I think one of the important takeaways here
is that we are equipping our colleagues
with a bunch of contacts, but they may not know everything.
And it is often very helpful to do a level of human review,
layer on your own ideas and insights,
and iterate with GrokBot as it builds out product.
And so this is awesome.
We're going to one-shot this from here for demo purposes.
But there's often a lot more iteration
that goes into working with our agents,
working with each other to figure out
what is the right product shape that we should ship.
And obviously, there's a number of different ways
you can do that.
So one thing I like to do with Notion
is just leave comments in Notion.
And GrokBots can read Notion comments.
And so it really does feel like you're interacting
with a colleague.
You leave some notes here.
You say, actually, this feels wrong.
That number feels off.
Like, tag in the person.
That works really well with Google Docs and other
connectors, too.
And so, yeah, I think the iteration process has also
gotten a lot more fun.
But I guess next conventionally, we'd probably
start prototyping some of those ideas out, right?
Yeah.
How do you want to do it?
Well, maybe we ask Emily.
So Emily is our engineering manager
and has contacts on our entire engineering team.
So maybe one thing we could do is ask Pete to hand the PRD
to Emily.
And maybe she can ask our engineering team
to prototype some of these ideas and see how they do.
Cool.
Should we also get Pixel in the mix?
Oh, yeah.
Great plan.
And do a little design.
That's a good idea.
Yeah, yeah.
So we should probably get some design for each of our P0s.
Cool.
All right.
So let's send that off.
And while that cooks, we'll pull up the virtual machine, which
Grokbot has access to.
And as we talked about, these are colleagues with a computer.
And so it is very helpful to give these agents,
these colleagues, give Grokbot its own virtual machine,
its own computer in the cloud, where it can actually do work.
It can navigate the web.
You can log in, and it can use your credentials
across various services to actually get work done.
And you can see up here top right,
you can see Teach It a Task.
And so you can actually record your workflows directly
on this machine.
And Agent can watch and learn and be
able to replicate and reproduce the work that you are doing.
So we often hear our sales team, our go-to-market team,
have these very complex Salesforce workflows,
these complex processes that need
to be replicated again and again.
And it's very helpful to be able to teach an agent with more
than just words or more than just spoken word
to actually be able to record the work that you are doing.
And the agent actually, every time it uses one of those tasks
or goes through one of those tasks,
also has the ability to refine that skill
and, again, follow that feedback mechanism
that we talked about earlier.
Really, if you're working in bespoke systems
or custom systems, I think that's really invaluable.
Okay, very cool.
So it looks like we have two separate handoffs,
one to engineering manager Emily
to actually start going on some prototypes for the spec.
And then the other is over to Pixel
to actually start working on some designs and some mocks.
Yeah, and I think what's cool
about the design workflow here is Pixel,
I mentioned earlier, is trained on just how
to be a great AI designer, but also it has context
on our business's design system.
And so in this case, we use Figma,
and so the design system lives in Figma,
but Pixel also sort of has reference files in its context
that sort of teach it how to design for our airline.
And so what this does is it makes it so that
we're not starting from scratch every time.
The agent has a ton of embedded context
on our preferred fonts and colors, UI patterns,
no-nos, we thought it over time, for example,
like never make X buttons on the left corner
and things like this.
And that really kind of gives this designer
the ability to iterate really, really quickly
and then get things mostly right on the first try
versus having to start from scratch every time.
And it looks like we got some designs.
What do we think?
Those are some expensive tickets.
It looks like we have two different options,
option A and option B, which Pixel has designed.
What does the crowd think?
Option A, clap.
Option B, clap.
Okay.
Sounds like team A.
All right, so let's hand the first mock over to Emily
to update the prototype.
Cool.
And what you're also noticing here is that
these bots can really act sort of interchangeably, right?
Like earlier it looked like Pixel had handed something
to Emily and then we made a decision
and then we can say, hey, like go and update Emily
and you'll notice that these bots
can sort of like interact more asynchronously
or more out of band than you might expect
if you're just used to working with
more of a chat style interface.
And honestly, I think these make a lot more fun
to work with where basically you can continue to steer
and drive what the agents are working on.
Particularly in some cases where they're working
on something for a few minutes at a time,
kind of getting that input from you as you go
kind of helps you feel like you're being a part
of the process and also verifying the output too.
Cool, so let's check in on the engineering team.
You can see Emily here as the engineering manager
deconstructed the different priorities
into scoped work for each one of the engineers
and actually then went and had direct conversations
with each one explaining the work that they were to do
and also included a bunch of additional context.
One of the things that I think we have all learned
the hard way is that agents are really good at prompting.
Oftentimes better than we are at figuring out
what context to give to an agent.
And so oftentimes just giving your team in GrokBot
the context of what you were trying to achieve
and letting them work together and suss out
what context would be most helpful,
how to deconstruct work in different ways
can be very accelerated.
One thing we will hopefully see in action a second here.
These GrokBots also have the ability,
there we go, to kick off cloud agents.
And so when it comes to the actual engineering work,
what each of these IC engineers are doing
is they're creating agents in the cloud
that sort of run with a local copy of your code repository.
So when it comes time to make changes to the code base
or maybe they need to install some setup scripts
to be able to ensure that the repo is testable
and runnable, these agents come with all
of those batteries included too.
So in this case, it looks like you just said yes
when Nova asked about creating a PR, is that right?
That's right, yeah.
And so Nova has gone off, launched this cloud agent,
will continue to monitor its work when that completes.
You can also have an additional verification loop.
The engineer can review the work of the cloud agent,
can hand it back to either a QA team
or your engineering manager who can actually run
an additional layer of checks and verification
to ensure that the outputs align with the intended goals
that you gave your team to start.
Yeah, I think what's really cool about this too
is you can sort of choose how much human
you want to bring into the loop, right?
So maybe for some of these cases,
if it's a really easy change to say a documentation website
or maybe it's resizing something in our mobile app,
it feels like a pretty low stakes change
and sometimes we can just let our agents run with it.
But perhaps there's a more meaningful change
if we wanna make sure that this design was implemented
the way that we spec'd it out
or the way that Pixel helped us spec'd it out,
we might wanna jump in and ask for a demo or prototype.
And so one thing we found that's just generally true
when working with agents is that giving them an environment
to verify their own output in makes a huge difference,
but also giving them the tools to help you as the human
verify the output also makes a huge difference in outcomes.
And you can kind of work with those things together
and get better results, so.
Amazing, so I think our engineering team
is gonna cook on this in the background.
And so what have we seen so far?
We started with this open question about the business.
We started talking to a data science colleague, Ashley,
to help us better understand some of the funnel dynamics
where the biggest fall off was,
handed all of that context over to a PMP agent
who could actually help write the product requirements doc.
That was the first pass.
We then handed it off to our designer
who created a first version of the mocks
to actually go and implement.
And then Emily and our engineering team are off now
cooking it with our cloud agents.
Really cool system, and again, you can really adapt this
to whatever workflow makes the most sense to your business.
And so we've seen a lot of folks who wanna go
really deep on the requirements phase
and maybe work on really complex systems
where there's lots of knock on implications
for every small requirement.
You could imagine having a team of folks whose job it is
to make sure there's a knowledge base that's come up to date
and that those requirements are fed into the product.
Or maybe you have a really convoluted code base
with a bunch of different repos that need to stay in sync.
That's another workflow that you could build in
with GrokBot.
And so my point with that is just stating that
this is one example of how you might set up your team,
but really the tool is meant to be flexible
for you to adapt to whatever workflow works
for your own organization.
Cool.
Okay, now a few of the hard learned lessons
working with GrokBot, a few things to keep in mind
as you start to build out your own teams in GrokBot.
First is this idea of named agents having separate memory,
being able to learn on the job,
and really thinking about these as colleagues.
They're not going to be great on day zero.
There is an onboarding phase where you can give them skills,
you can give them context, you can teach them things.
And so over time, they actually build up that context
and intuition and can take on more and more work,
which is cool to see.
The other is really thinking about sort of reducing noise
in the system as PMs, like there is often a lot of pings,
a lot of emails, a lot of slacks.
One of the pro tips that we've learned is
when you set up a routine to ask your agent,
if this is essentially a no operation,
if there's nothing important or urgent for me to see,
you can actually just take the work on yourself
or you don't need to update me.
And so there is a bit of noise reduction in the system.
Agents are, and Grokbot is currently grooming my inbox
and will only tell me about the most important emails there
and can escalate things,
but generally I'm trying to reduce the noise in the system
so I can keep focused on what is most important
for the team.
And then agents all the way down,
this idea that you can have managers of agents,
agents are coordinating with cloud agents,
and Grokbot is a very helpful agent system
for helping you take on some of the most ambitious work
and accelerate your product teams.
Yeah, very cool.
So that was a very fun demo.
That was great being able to actually make some impact
at Fly Low Airlines.
We are going to wrap there
to those who are joining us virtually.
Check that with Matt, Lauren, and Roshan,
who are currently building a startup with Grokbot
over the course of these three days, which is very exciting.
How's progress going?
It's going, we have a really fun business idea,
and so if you're interested in following along,
we'll be streaming for the next 48 plus hours.
So, it should be great.
Very good, thank you all so much.
Very good, and for those in the audience,
we are now going to open it up to any...
Questions that are on your mind.
Before we do that, one quick thing we wanted to plug
is we are running a competition.
You could win a trip to Starbase, Texas
to go watch a launch of Starship, which is pretty cool.
Incredibly cool if you ask me.
If you show us how you've integrated Grok Bot
into your work, so follow at Grok and at bot on x.
And there's a post on the at Grok account
right now that explains how to enter and when.
The runners up here are also going to win a tour,
I believe to Hawthorne to go and see how some of the stuff
that helps launch stuff into space is made.
And so if you're interested in any role of that,
that QR code should help you get started
or you can just go to at Grok on x.
And that's our question.
Very cool.
Are we allowed to enter or no?
I don't know.
I hope so.
Okay.
All right, there we go.
Questions.
Oh, I will keep that up so people can scan it.
We can repeat the questions up here too,
if it's easier.
You can just shout it out and we'll repeat it, yeah.
Oh, put up the QR code.
Oh, get out of the way for the QR code.
Sorry.
We also want to hear your question.
Yeah, so I think the question is about what we've seen
in terms of bots managing context,
how it might overlap across teams or roles.
Is that the right idea?
Yeah.
So I think at the end of the day,
these act as sort of self-contained agents
that you can steer and control however you want.
So if I understand your question correctly,
the way that these agents, these bots are architected
is that each bot has its own memory.
But there's also a shared memory pool
that bots can contribute to in the cases when they,
you decide that there's something you should remember
from your team.
And so there's a bit of prompting we use
to kind of under the hood to tune how the bots
choose one or the other.
But in general, bots have a sort of individual memory pool
that they write memories to
and then refine memories from over time.
And so one of the reasons that we think
we really like the role-based version of this
is that you can get really strong memories
for how to become a really good engineer over time.
But then, we're also still experimenting
with this a little bit, the group chats interface
that you saw really allows you to kind of
bring those things together.
So there are multiple approaches.
For example, you could have a single builder bot
that is end-prod and design all in one.
It can also work, it's just that we find
for more complex use cases separating the roles
out can be helpful.
I'm not sure if that was your question or...
Great.
Yeah, I think one of the things which is interesting
is like we've been trained with early agents
to worry about context pollution
and context management.
And there's like a little part of everybody's brain
that is thinking about like, what does agent know?
What do they not know?
Do I need to compact?
And at what point am I gonna run out of context window?
And I think the ultimate goal is to make
this incredibly simple and incredibly accessible
for everybody to use.
And not have to spend a bunch of like metal work
thinking about what we can see about.
And we're back.
So hopefully you all enjoyed that session
on GrokBot for product managers.
We're back in the studio and we have a guest with us.
And this is Eric.
Eric is the co-founder and CEO of Carat Financial,
banking credit and payments built for creators
and growing businesses.
Before Carat, I believe you were product manager
at Instagram, is that right?
Yeah, I was a product manager,
joined Meta Instagram 2016.
Awesome.
And another life.
Awesome, welcome, excited to have you.
So Lauren and I have been at work here during the break.
We were just talking about like exactly what we're building,
what the direction is.
And I feel like we're still kind of working
on exactly what we want to build
and like what the software looks like.
And I think first it's an interesting kind of lesson
in how the hardest part of building
is actually aligning on an idea.
We're just talking about that.
And so I think we're gonna do since we have Eric's time
and he's built the business himself
and he's, you know, working sort of these things.
Maybe we've been workshop exactly what we're building,
we're finding ideal of it so we know exactly where we're
headed.
Matt, I kind of love that because people, my mom,
would always ask like,
what does a product manager even do?
And I told her, it always comes down to three things.
Number one is figure out what to build.
Number two is how to build it.
And number three is actually coordinating building it.
And I think people don't realize like AI makes the third part
really easy, but like parts one and two,
that's still like human brains.
And so when you're like, what are we even doing?
I'm like, yeah, this is perfect
because I also want to know.
So I think my first question,
so I tuned and I cheated a little.
I had some of the live stream up
when you were doing a theater in the very beginning.
So I heard it was like a website for pop-ups
and like, is this for restaurant owners to do pop-ups?
I'm trying to get a sense of like,
who are we doing this for?
What's the problem we're trying to solve?
Yeah, for me, I imagine like our main users
are people who want to run a pop-up.
So like you could be a restaurateur,
you could have your own Shopify store,
but you want this, like a pop-up to me,
like the whole business or the value proposition
of a pop-up store is that it's,
for one, it's like, it's in person.
It's IRL.
And the other part is there's this almost like
limited supply factor where it's like,
there's a time constraint.
There's like, you know, pop-ups are,
I mean, you're gonna have one, you gotta go.
So you have to go.
There's like this, you know,
there's a desire to want to show up
and then maybe when you show up,
there's a chance to participate in a once in a lifetime
or whatever, you know, experience or buy products
or merchandise that are only accessible through the pop-up.
So I feel like there's something interesting there
where, you know, actually it's pretty hard
to set something like this up yourself.
And so we want it where we're thinking of one,
actually creating a pop-up of our own.
Or maybe like a rock-pop thing.
Yeah, like, cause I personally love,
would love some rock-pot merch.
Believe it or not, I don't have any rock-pot merch.
Maybe some tater, tater merch as well.
Yeah, like a potato in the, or I don't know,
a rock-pot in the shape of potato or something.
Yeah.
And I think that by actually trying
to start this pop-up ourselves,
we will build tools that will kind of shape
the platform that we want to go to as well,
where initially the only user
of this platform is gonna be ourselves.
We're gonna use it to make, to plan
and organize our pop-up store.
And then we'll figure out how to actually
make it a little bit more generic,
make it accessible for other users
to actually reuse the same info,
to do bookings like finding venues,
you know, planning invitations and things like that.
Okay, so this makes sense.
So I have, one thing I really like this,
and then I have one push I wanna give.
The thing I really like is,
especially in a world where AI is eating everything,
IRL matters even more.
Like, the whole point of what we're doing
over the next few days, it's like,
we can even build an entire business with RockBot.
But the special part is, to your point,
getting to meet and interact with the business
in real time, if anything,
what we're describing now with software,
it's happening in brick and mortar businesses too.
Like, if you're a restaurant,
the big question you have to think about is,
how do I avoid just being commoditized
and put on as another icon on Uber Eats and DoorDash?
Like, how do I make sure I'm not just a cloud kitchen
that people are just ordering burgers from?
Exactly.
Pop-up, or if like I'm selling stickers online
and everyone is just putting out AI-generated stickers,
how do I make sure people actually know
what I represent and stand for?
Pop-up.
So like, my first thought is like,
I really like this,
because you're trying to recapture the essence of like,
here's something special about your brand
and how you can reach people
in a way that's become really valuable today.
My second, and here's a bit of where my push is,
I really think it matters who we're doing this for.
And I'm hearing you describe the initial target demo
of who we're building it for.
You said, let's build it for ourselves.
So if we're gonna build it for ourselves,
then the framing's almost people who wanted to pop up
that have never done a pop-up before.
Very meta.
And barely understand the business side.
And that's okay, because then I heard you say,
but okay, we're gonna later on go more advanced.
Because there's a totally different demographic
where I already run a restaurant or a merch shop,
and it's working,
but I wanna run a pop-up to get attention, right?
I think those are two really different demographics.
I'm super ready now to start with the first one.
My only ask is to, let's like narrow it a little.
So we're gonna start with people who haven't done it before.
You mentioned merch.
So are we gonna do what you're doing?
This is like a merch, like, hey, you run,
this is so meta.
But if you're in San Francisco,
it's like you run a venture-backed startup,
and to stand out against all of the other AI companies,
you wanna have your own IRL merch drop.
You wanna have your own plushies.
Like very meta.
Is that gonna be the initial least case we build for?
I think so.
That could be pretty interesting.
Yeah.
I mean, it could be interesting.
It feels a bit meta.
It feels a bit disconnected from just like maybe,
is there a simpler way to connect with our audience?
If I'm thinking about myself, like what I want,
I don't know what a pop-up is,
but most of the time what I'm looking to do
on like a Saturday is just go find something fun to do.
And you go with a friend of mine,
and I like art, I like checking out new things,
if there's something cool to buy,
I like buying these cool things.
So yeah, I don't know.
My thinking is like always simplify,
but I'm down for whatever, you know, so.
So, I mean, I think we have,
I'm curious for chat things.
Like this is a fork in the road.
We can either go a bit meta and really build
for ourselves, which is we're a tech AI brand,
and we want to get more of an IRL connection to our folks.
So like let's go and do merch or something,
or we can do something totally different,
like kind of like what you said, right?
So I'm curious, is there anything in chat?
These messages are so funny, the poor AV team.
Am I just like way too loud right now?
The sound guys are having a lot of fun right now.
Bro is proclaiming fully.
At least we can have fun with the chat
while we figure it out.
I feel like my problem is like I'm always louder
than everybody else.
And like when I do podcasts,
I just like amped down my sensitivity a little bit.
Okay, chat, let us know like
which direction should we go?
Or is there just a lot of lag going on right now?
No, very meta.
I think there's a bit of a lag between them.
I think there is a lag.
But I like where we're at.
I think we have a good direction.
So like what would help most?
Like maybe if we start wire framing
or walking through the user flows,
we can talk about it.
I think we gotta be specific though
on which one we're gonna do.
Like are we gonna be like,
hey, like let's do tech brand
doing a popup for your brand,
or should we do something to your point,
like very brick and mortar, very different.
Like I'm a restaurant owner
and I wanna do a popup to get people
to come to my restaurant.
It's like a special event.
I do think we gotta make a call.
Otherwise we're gonna build
the most generic popup site possible.
Which I fear is that it's too generic
to be helpful to anybody.
Yeah, I think I agree with that.
I mean like what are the constants, right?
The constants across all of these things
and what we want to do are that like
we need a date, we need a time,
we need a venue,
we need to collect a bunch of different people
who have a trade into that same place.
And so Lauren started working on some prototyping tools
for us to start doing those things.
And then what is specific to us?
Sounds like the merchandise might be.
Yeah, you know what?
Let's do like what every startup
has always pitched to every VC ever.
Guys, we're gonna start small.
The addressable market is everybody.
Maybe we start with merch for tech companies
because like, hey, we wanna have an IRL presence.
But once we start to build it
and figure out the primitives,
then we can expand it
to like maybe other sort of options scenarios.
So what do we think of that?
I would address chat,
but chat is like on a three minute delay.
So we're just gonna fly blind and say,
all right, you know what?
We're gonna try and start a Grok popup
and sell what, Grok pushups, tater plushies?
Sure. Grok hats.
Grok hats.
Okay, well, this is the easiest thing possible
if I put on my product manager hat, right?
It's like, you know, the classic framing is like,
what are the problems we have?
I think the first one is just like,
if we're really gonna build it for ourselves,
what do we sell?
Where do we sell it?
Coordinate the location time.
So it's what do we sell?
Number one, number two, where do we sell it?
Number three, coordinate the location and time.
The fourth thing I would say is like ticketing,
where you wanna make sure you have a social element.
I think Particle's biggest success
was you knowing that all your other friends
are coming as well.
Nice, yeah, I like that.
And so like, we wanna make this an event.
Like we can't have Elon tweeting out every single time
the popup is open, right?
I mean, that'd be huge.
That'd be amazing for any business to have.
So I think the first question is like,
what do we wanna make here?
Cool, yeah, so maybe we start with,
what do we wanna sell, merch?
It sounds like we're doing a merch popup.
Yeah.
Sounds like we need some sort of system for ticketing
or like, just basically like event registration.
We could probably find like an API or something
that like helps us with that.
Or we could just use our plan scale database.
We could do some like quick event registration,
make it social, so ticketing.
And we don't even really need to worry about time slots.
Like if we wanted to like do it across the day
or something right now.
So merch, we're gonna need to work on the merch
for the popup.
That should be integrated into the platform.
The registrations, I think, like that seems like pretty easy.
And then maybe something to help us like finding the venue.
Yeah, like venue.
Yeah, yeah.
So maybe you, I love it, you simplified it three things.
Just the merch, the ticketing,
with like the social piece, and then just finding a venue.
So yeah.
So you're totally right, time slots are as important.
Page one, what are you building?
But in this instance,
it's you're building a merch popup.
Page two is literally like what date is this thing?
And then it helps you like build and invent a booking system.
And then page three is like,
kind of like where you're having it.
And then you can start to figure out
the location and whatnot.
So here's my question.
As someone who's still learning in GrokBot,
what's the recommended approach using GrokBot
to figure it out?
Like are you gonna have each of those
like merch, ticketing, venue?
Is that a different bot?
Or are you gonna split it functionally, right?
In terms of like engineering versus design.
Like how are you thinking about this, Lauren?
Or Lauren is currently doing the actual work that I said.
Sorry, I'd like super unlocking.
Maybe Matt, how do we split this up?
I like to split these things up.
I think about bots as like different employees really.
So like in my bots right now,
I'm set up on my screen.
I have a growth engineer, I have a founding engineer,
I have an image generator bot,
I have a creative director, a chief of staff,
and then some of these other things,
which usually come from like tasks.
Like if I have a task, for example,
updating my documentation,
I'm gonna create a bot separately
to update the documentation.
And so you can see here, Lauren actually has been
just cooking on some like wire frames.
Yeah, so yeah, what I was doing in the background
and I was like kind of zoning out a bit,
but I'm not zoning out,
but trying to lock in on this was to start.
So I'm a very visual person.
And so I got my prototype bot
to start sketching out stuff for me in TLDraw,
which is pretty cool that the,
so one thing GrokBot does really well
is like you can actually control a browser
and it actually wins the TLDraw
drawing for me, right?
So we have some kind of very low fidelity mockups
that we can kind of just critique and think,
help us ideate what we're trying to build.
So I've just been prompting
and trying to get it to work on that.
One thing I'll say, I saw somebody in chat say,
merch, just merch.
You know, if we're gonna put on our true
like Silicon Valley satire hats,
I would say this is a community as a service
and a world dominated by AI.
We wanna help you figure out how to bring
the in-person vibes of your company back.
So I think if it less is merch,
this is a platform for you to have community meetups
around your brand.
And yeah, as a tech brand,
one thing that's really easy is to have a reason.
Merch is a great reason.
Sweet, yeah, totally good.
And I know some providers,
I know some APIs where we can maybe line up some merch
that we might be able to integrate into the platform.
Some ways we might be able to make that happen.
Sweet.
Well, when if you're working on that?
I'm not sure I think you are working on that.
I guess I'll ask the other person.
I'll clear up some time, Lauren,
do you feel like we have what we need to start building stuff?
I'll try.
Okay, cool.
I realize the two of you are like hosting and guesting
at the same time.
It's pretty hard to...
Incredibly difficult to be entertaining to actually build.
Well then I'll ask you, so like,
if we're gonna, fine, it's like,
hey, if you're a brand,
you're gonna have like a community pop up,
we're using merch as like the Trojan horse
to like something to start with.
What's like fun merch?
Because I feel like every tech startup ever has done,
I'm wearing merch for my own company,
like t-shirts and hats.
Is there something unique to Grok?
I feel like we could lean in the direction of cute,
like taters and potatoes,
because that's part of freaking her brand.
Is there something different?
I mean, obviously you only have the flamethrowers.
Like that is a unique type of merch,
what do you think about it?
Yeah, so we just have to figure out
flamethrower production in like 48 hours,
it sounds like.
No, I mean, I think when I think about the best merch,
it's similar to what you described,
which is like building for yourself.
It's like, hey, I dig hats,
but I dig very specific kinds of hats.
Like I like hoodies,
but like I want a very good specific kind of hoodie.
And so if you can like work backwards from that,
like in the clothing aspect,
it's kind of like what kind of stuff do you like?
One of my good friends gave me like a Snorlax plushie
at one point.
Are you a Pokemon fan?
I mean, you know, I have friends that are Pokemon fans.
So I play a pretty lousy kid.
And I love that.
And it was like very reminiscent of my childhood,
kind of like cool gift.
And something like that resonated with me.
So it's like, how do you find something
either sentimental or emotional
that you can connect with somebody?
So my two thoughts here,
the first one is like that could be a bot action itself
as we're exploring use cases to like go in research
and figure out what people want.
My second thought is basically you said,
I heard two things.
I heard one, an expressed appreciation for utility,
like not just a hat, a really good hat.
The second is a desire for novelty,
like the Snorlax thing.
This is a total tangent on the novelty piece.
This is not a utility piece.
Have you heard like,
I saw this TikTok the other day.
It was like, you know,
boys get girls flowers,
not to be gender normative.
Sometimes people in a relationship
like to get the other person relation flowers.
What's the other version of that?
Right?
Like a girl was like, what do I get from my boyfriend?
And somebody suggested on TikTok,
tungsten cubes.
Tungsten cubes.
Have you seen these?
I love tungsten cubes, yeah.
Why?
They're so heavy.
They're because they're cool.
They're so cool.
They're like, don't worry about it.
They're really dense.
They're really hard to pick up.
So I'm like,
Chat's gonna lose it.
I'm not saying we do this,
but if we're gonna go the novelty direction,
like in addition to the hats and things,
I don't want like tungsten cubes.
Yeah, 100%.
Yeah.
I mean, I don't know why we're,
I love he immediately understood what I was telling you.
Wait, can you get like a tungsten cube
in the shape of a graphite?
You could get a, that would,
I mean a spherical density cube.
That would be crazy.
You can absolutely do this.
A tungsten graphite.
Wait, that would, I would actually want one, guys.
Like I'm moving really hypothetical.
I would want one.
Yeah, I mean.
How much would you pay for it?
I would pay, honestly, I pay 80 bucks for that.
80 bucks?
And here's the cool thing.
It's so heavy, you can't even get it shipped.
I mean,
You have to go to the pop-up to get it.
I really don't.
Back off a little bit.
I think the one-inch,
one-inch tungsten sphere is $500.
So $80, maybe.
Now tungsten cubes, maybe with the Grokbot logo on them
are less expensive, but the tungsten sphere is $500.
So.
$500, that is an expensive piece of merch.
Okay, so we might have to pass on the,
this might be primo merch.
Maybe we have like three of these
for people to pop up or something.
Maybe one person, okay, I'm going totally off track.
Maybe one person out of every 500 that goes there
wins the tungsten sphere.
I hear you, I hear you.
Yeah, I can tell you like that.
Maybe we start, Lauren, with like the basics.
Like we can back into where we're booking,
what we're booking, some of these other things.
I know your cloud agents are working on it.
In the meantime, I've also been working on
some of our like site stuff,
just connecting email infrastructure.
I did want to take a moment and talk through like chat
because we've been getting some really great messages
about what people like, what they don't like.
We have these in Notion.
So from the JoyT,
if friends can use each other's bots,
do they inherit the bots previous training?
Can you remove past behaviors, retrain or reset it,
and then refine it in your own version?
So it's interesting, currently, the way these bots work,
like if Lauren sent me a bot, that would be a template.
That template basically allows you to copy the memories,
some of the context or what the bots worked on,
or like the instructions,
as well as like first party plugins and some other things
without carrying over sensitive data or like chat data.
So if you shared a template with me,
you wouldn't have to worry about sending me any passwords,
or number one, the bot can't see passwords.
We'll talk a little bit more about that in a second,
but any sort of chat information that's specific to you.
Related, bots store passwords securely
using like secure entry.
So you actually don't need to worry about bots
having access to any sensitive data.
You'll get like a nice little form.
And so basically, the answer to that is
when you get a bot template,
you're gonna be able to refine it as you go.
It's going to have a certain set of behaviors and actions,
and it's necessarily like your own kind of version
of that bot.
It's not an exact one for one copy.
I'll talk through a couple other of these while Lauren's
kind of iterating on these designs.
Interesting to see her process here.
How can you tell if you've given your bot too much scope?
What errors do you observe over time from Crystal,
and then a very long string of numbers?
I think you just have to observe kind of how they respond.
The parallel here, I use a lot of parallels to humans.
And it's like, if you ask a human to do too much,
maybe you're seeing some of this on the stream,
the human starts to get disoriented
and might say things like they're a little flustered
or they might not make sense.
And so you can start to observe in AI,
like is this making sense?
Are the outputs high quality?
And if we think more about why that might be,
how context work, how next token prediction works,
it can start to make sense.
But we won't go too deep there.
I would just say, does it feel like the bot is on target?
Does your AI feel like it is moving in a good direction?
And if the answer is no,
you might need to narrow the scope or clear the context.
The answer is yes, then maybe you're feeling better.
So interestingly, I'm noticing Lauren's bot here is like...
Yeah, my bot is really like literally sketching.
I love this.
Have you come up with a cool design for this?
Yeah, like right now, I'm just thinking,
well, I'm sort of inspired a little by Pokemon cards
and how they're a little bit shiny.
Oh, wait, so you want, in some ways,
the tickets to the first ever Grok Bot pop-up
are collectibles in themselves.
I mean, that could be pretty interesting.
That is really cool.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
So you already have.
So the ticket itself is a collectible.
Yeah.
And then you show up, and then you have a chance
to actually look around and buy more cool merch.
Yeah, because keep in mind, the whole reason
we're doing this pop-up is because it's special.
So I feel like having a really cool ticket, that's part of it.
So my question, again, is somebody
who's still learning about Grok Bot, right?
You have one right now designing the tickets themselves.
Are we able to have one figure out the merch?
Tell it, hey, we don't just want plushies and high quality hoodies.
We want that.
We want that for sure.
But we want something cool and novel.
Hey, we consider the tungsten cube.
And then we consider the tungsten cube
in the shape of a Grok Bot.
And we realize that would cost $3,000.
So does it have other ideas in this vein?
Let me just write that down.
So I'm curious if you have more cool ideas, like tungsten.
Is that how you spell it?
Yeah, that's how you spell tungsten cubes, which again,
he and I instantly, in the old usage of their tungsten cubes,
he rocked it right away.
Throw out more ideas that I can try to get.
I've tried another good novelty ones.
So some of what we're seeing in the chat, potato plushies,
a lot of people seem to like that.
Potato plushies.
Pictures from SpaceX launches, so rocketry pictures.
Oh, OK, pictures from SpaceX.
Limited edition Grok Bot stress balls
shaped in the different shapes of Grok Bots.
Oh, that's a really cool idea.
I like the stress ball one.
Probably not too hard to make.
What could be cool is how Grok Bot is spherical, right?
Like a hat, but the hat just has eyes on it.
The hat is on.
That's cute.
On your head.
Wait, I like this.
Or like a toboggan.
Oh, actually, you've probably just heard me say something
that sounds like a sled.
I'm from North Carolina.
Yeah, like a beanie thing.
People in the South call those toboggans.
Just completely sidebar on the channel right now.
I think toboggan is a sled.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
It's really crazy.
So I just had to go on a tangent there.
But anyway, basically like a wool cap of some sort, right?
So another one I'll add.
Wait, what about Grok Bot character plushies?
Like the whole point is you have
like a whole army of Grok Bots.
We can make like cool little plushies for each of them.
I also feel like it'd be really cool to have
the attendees of this pop up be able to like participate
by like, I don't know, submitting some ideas
and then we'll make them.
Because like in Grok Bot, you can create your own bot templates.
So I wonder if there's also something we can tie in there
where you can submit a bot template,
like we'll choose good ones, and then we'll
make some special merch for them, I guess.
I don't know, like our.
Wait, can I go one step beyond that for something even crazier?
I was thinking about it, right?
So what if you could create your own physical Grok Bot
that also has its own purpose?
Because you can code it, right?
Like for example, you can make a physical Grok Bot.
I'm just making this up because I'm
in a long distance relationship right now.
We have Find My iPhone turned on.
What if I like got a key chain?
And the Grok Bots, that bot's agent's sole job
is to track the location of my partner.
So I know where she is.
Or like you've seen this since on TikTok.
It's like she's x miles away.
I'm not saying use that as an example.
I'm saying what if you had people create physical Grok Bots
with specific things?
Or like the other classic Grok Bot I've heard used is like,
oh, if you're a startup founder, it
gives you the competitive news update of what's
happening in your space.
What if you had a physical one, you just look at it,
and it just tells you this is what happened.
Yeah?
Or maybe it tracks sales of your merch store.
And every time you make $1,000, it lights up.
It's like you just made another $1,000.
I don't know, because it kind of taps into the ethos
of you can customize it, and you can code it,
and we can make it.
I'm really just thinking out loud now.
Yeah.
I don't know, man.
Well, this is a first.
Someone commented, Grok Bot Build-A-Bear kind of thing.
Yeah.
Another person commented, don't do that.
There are two types of people on the internet.
Oh, yeah, right.
So this one's still working on the tickets, right?
So are we just not going to do the platform idea then?
Well, I figure if we build the tools to do it ourselves,
we can then make them scalable.
Yeah, I feel like the platform maybe is a stretch goal.
Yeah.
We'll build the tools for ourselves first.
I think we should focus on just getting the store design set up.
The store design, finding a place to do this.
Exactly.
As soon as possible.
Tomorrow and the third day, we have time
to actually both platformize things
if we feel like they're worth doing that.
But for now, yeah.
And then I have a merch bot set up already.
I do like this Build-A-Bear, Grok Bot thing.
If it's not impossible to execute.
And then in the course of doing it,
yeah, we can extend it later to let
anybody do their own pop-ups.
Oh, actually, I'm going to say ask Grok to use Grok, imagine.
Oh, that's cute.
Tamagrok, a Grok Tamagotchi.
Maybe that's what the story has instead of Build-A-Bear.
Maybe it's just the Grok Bot Tamagotchi.
Oh, yeah, we're telling Steve, like, hey,
don't just regurgitate.
Yeah, don't just tell me when I just told you.
I think it's really inspiring to come up
with something more and better.
It really does feel like you're just messaging
a team of your colleagues.
All right, I think one of our colleagues
is actually back from the class.
Hey, welcome back.
How's it going?
Good to see you.
It's a pleasure.
My name's Eric.
Hey, Roshan, nice to meet you.
Of course.
I caught some of the conversation, but what did I miss?
It's got an interesting direction.
So the thinking was, look, if we do a pop-up,
we should have a clear sense of who we're building it for
and what we're trying to solve, right?
And I think there's something very special
about getting to an IRL manifestation of what your brand
is, especially with AI software everywhere.
And then we're like, this is actually Lawrence.
I do.
Why don't we do it for ourselves first?
And then it goes well for ourselves.
We can expand this into a platform.
So then we started thinking through,
and this is actually Matt's point.
We're going to do it for ourselves.
There are only three things we need to figure out.
Hold on.
Let me maybe actually record this.
Should we feed this into a bot?
Have we done that yet?
No, and we can update our docs.
I have an outreach bot.
We have one working on menus.
Let's find my outreach bot.
OK, here we go.
Sorry.
Pick back up where you left off.
Yeah, go for it.
And so Matt had actually a really good point.
If we're going to do our own Grokbot pop-up,
there's really three things we need to figure out.
Number one is just what's going to be there, like the merch.
The second thing is the venue, right?
And the third thing is ticketing.
And again, all of these can later be extensible
until their own broader sort of pop-up things.
So we started working and thinking about the merch
and the ticketing.
So she has one Grokbot actually designing the ticketing,
which in itself could be a collectible item.
And we have another one thinking through merch ideas.
And Matt expressed that from a merch pew.
There are two things he cares about.
The first is utility and craft.
So a hoodie or a hat, a really well-done one.
The second one is novelty.
Exactly.
The second is novelty.
So you talked about how a friend once gave him
a Snorlax plushie.
He really appreciated that.
And I mentioned, as a guy, I feel like my favorite novel
toad is a tungsten cube.
And then Lauren Brown's some ideas actually,
where it's like, oh, maybe it's not just a tungsten cube.
Maybe it's a tungsten figurine in the shape of a Grokbot,
which then evolved into, what if you could actually
customize it?
Like, what if you had different Grokbot plushies,
because there's so many characters, which then
evolved into, what if it's going to be a plushie?
Why not program in some functionality into it as well?
Like, you could have one Grokbot plushie.
The job is just to update you what's happening in your Slack.
That's cool.
Honestly, I don't know if I would actually
want that as a funner.
I feel like I'm on my phone checking it all the time
anyways.
But there's something interesting here.
Like, if we're talking about pop-ups,
it's the manifestation of your company,
the Grokbot plushie could be the manifestation of the Grokbot,
right, where you can actually program it to do simple things.
That's where we left off, Don.
And then we were thinking more about how do we actually
leverage the bots to do this?
Like, one bot's thinking through ticketing,
one bot's thinking through the merch.
And then we got very lucky and you came back.
That's sort of catching you up.
I just recorded all that.
Yeah, of course.
So let me maybe feed that into a bot.
Maybe we spin up a merch bot whose job it is to help us,
like, pin a bunch of really cool merch
and figure out what's doable.
Let's do it.
Cool.
OK, cool.
I got my merch bot hooked up to Grok Imagine.
But I guess it doesn't really know.
It's got some random merch, which I wish I could kind of cool,
I guess.
But it's not.
It's kind of messed up the Grokbot logo.
I forgot to tell it to do that first.
So let me try and cook more on that.
Maybe we could also, like, would it
help if we found a supplier and then we, like,
grounded some of this merch and things that actually exist?
Oh, yeah.
Or like, we had a way to basically, like,
maybe feed via API or website, like, what merch options it has
and then Grok can, like, pick that merch.
You could, like, go to, you could, like, scrape Alibaba,
right, or like, Ta-Bao.
You could even have it, like, do outreach to, like,
Alibaba and Ta-Bao and spend, like, 1,000,
we're probably not going to do this, I'm just saying it,
tungsten-q manufacturers and be like,
how cheap can you make them?
I'll start doing some research on how we can do that using
Grokbot.
I feel like we should come up with, like, two or three
really just, like, perfect examples of merch, you know,
like, two or three, like, really well curated things
that we think we could actually get.
That might be a good way to, like, pare down.
Totally agree.
Yeah.
He's like, there are so many ideas.
He's being a good PM.
He's like, we got to only do a few.
Yeah, yeah.
That's part of it, right?
It's like, you want it to be, like, intentional, like,
sort of intentionally thought of, intentionally designed.
And I don't know about you, but I
feel like sometimes there's this bit of, like,
less is more where you really want to, you know,
like, knock it out of the park on one or two or three
key things, so.
Well, then I'm going to toss the PM hat to you.
We've discussed many, many ideas.
What do you think is the first one?
That you're most excited about?
For the merch?
Yeah, or for the products, or out of everything
we just mentioned.
Well, I don't want to scope creep too much,
but I think it could be really interesting when, you know,
maybe if you're registering for the pop-up,
you can choose your favorite merch item.
Like, maybe we could show you a gallery
of some of the possible, like, merch.
We could make a little bit of, like, a gallery
where, like, in the registration experience,
you can, like, you know, pick your merch item.
You can kind of see some previews
of what that would look like.
Maybe, like, something cool.
This might be a stretch goal, like a 3D interactive thing.
You can spin it around and see it in 3D space.
I know that the bunch of MCPs out there
for, like, 3D design and stuff.
That could be a really fun thing to do.
Or, you know, I feel like one of the things
that I always think about when I go to events
is just, like, wanting to know that I'm sort of,
you know, getting something unique
or getting something special.
And earlier today, we were talking a lot about how
we want this to feel.
We each want to bring something special to the event.
So I wonder if we can build that
into the registration experience,
and that could actually be something we can do.
You know, if we go in that direction
where we're going to leverage, like,
the graphic customization capabilities
and, like, show visualizations,
it really makes me feel like we should just lean more
into, like, for this IRL pop-up, build a Grokbot.
Like, you have characters for your bots.
You can, like, create a physical manifestation.
You can design it. You can visualize it.
You can see it. And you can assign it a function, right?
Like, kind of what I talked about.
It doesn't have to be slack updates.
Maybe it's just, like, the weather outside.
Although, technically, if you're outside
touching grass already, the fact that you would need
your Grokbot plushie to tell you what the weather is
is a little disservice.
I can always use an assist. I don't know.
Yeah, yeah, you're not sure.
It's like, Grokbot, things explain it.
But leaner, I put the world around me.
I like that.
But giving people the ability to customize,
literally, their own IRL Grokbot, like, that could be fun.
And you could visualize it using the tools you set.
Yeah, what are your top three?
I heard a bunch of ideas.
I think, I mean, to be honest,
after hearing you describe this visualization idea,
I think my favorite one is this, in fact, build,
which, again, somebody from chat,
it's like, build a Grokbot.
Yeah.
It's like, this entire workshop is us building
your own Grokbots to build a company
that will now build you physical Grokbots.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Very meta.
It is very meta.
But it's like, in a way, it's a loop.
A strange loop.
Yeah, I love that.
I love that.
Awesome.
Well, it sounds like we have some merch ideas floating around.
Well, yeah, I have a few.
I mean, I need to iterate a little bit.
But like, those could be some,
I mean, the eyes are a little bit off.
They're just very tight.
I don't know why you're like that.
But we'll just need to tweak it a little bit.
That was a cool comment in the chat.
And then I also have another bot
working on creating some cool ticket ideas.
Nice.
So you can actually like, well, I'll
probably want to find a printer.
We can actually put them.
Yeah.
The printer would be good.
I know some merch connections.
So we could start to research that.
I can start doing some research on like a printer for tickets
you think?
Yeah, tickets.
OK.
Because I think the tickets are almost like a collectible
in itself.
Yeah, you can maybe.
You sign up and then we'll like, mail it to you or something.
Well, we give it to you on site.
We give it to you on site.
So you come in with a generic ticket?
Like, a QR code or something?
And then you exchange it for like your collectible ticket
that you can carry.
Or maybe you have a badge or a name tag.
Now we're going a little crazy with that.
No, it's such a good idea.
It might be worth downscoping a little bit
and just focusing again on like the system
that we're building and like what we're trying to deliver,
which is an experience for which we need a venue,
a merch, and then the people that we're going to collect.
This is a good merch exploration.
Are you really locking in the venues?
I mean, you need to work on that.
Wait, let's get a bot to figure out the venues.
I have a list of venues.
OK, should I make a bot?
Do you have a bot template you can share with me?
A bot template for what?
Finding venues.
By finding venues.
I'm sharing my screen.
I guess I should show.
Yeah, absolutely.
Find the venue, my operator research here.
Create a template and I'll get that over to you.
To me, the best part of every hackathon
is when you get to a point where like, wait,
I actually want this to happen.
Like, I actually want there to now be this pop up
where I'm going to go and get my Grok Pop plushie.
Yeah, I love that.
And maybe you can actually do things as well.
Yeah, yeah.
This is awesome.
OK.
Wait, so who's going to figure out the venues?
I know you already have them pulled up,
but you have the screen share.
So which one should we go with?
Oh, the venues are in Notion, actually.
Oh, great.
Well, then maybe we should have a Grok Pop just
like reach out to all of them.
You could just be like, where's the Notion?
The Notion?
What do you mean?
The link mean the Notion.
OK, sweet.
I'll send you a slack.
To the comments, I am on X. I'm really bad at X.
I have very few followers.
If you Google it, you'll find it.
This is my name, some of you were asking.
I don't know about it.
What are these?
OK.
No, no, no.
I'll say it.
Yeah.
It's a little more interesting.
Well, that's cool.
I think it doesn't really know how to.
Yeah.
I like how the bot just threw these up
on a local URL on its computer.
Oh, did it?
So you could just go and check them out.
I think it's also funny that your merch drop bot is named
Drop, and I asked to create a merch drop bot that also
got named Drop.
And so I guess you could add some convergent evolution there.
This is a total side note, but I feel like you
know how you have templates right now for the bots
you can share around?
I feel like one day you could have a whole theme where
you can spin up an army of bots, and they all
follow one theme, like potato named puns,
or Sonic the Hedgehog themed ones,
and spin up more bots with those names.
This is cool.
Lauren, I just sent you some of the venues,
and then I'm working on getting a little template for you.
Oh, I'll figure this one out later.
I kind of want to sign in this stuff.
Yeah, see, someone said if you genuinely
sell drop bot plushies, I would buy one.
Yes, good.
Someone told me to get good at X.
I'm trying, guys.
I'm trying.
I really like this build a drop bot plushie,
but maybe you can program an actual functionality.
Or if that's too complicated, maybe it
can do one of three things.
Also, I feel like it's just good for the drop bot brand,
even people around San Francisco and the world
carrying their actual drop bots.
I totally agree.
Yeah, a little back change or something.
Yeah, it's not just an AI interface.
Yeah, very cool.
What else did you guys cover while it was gone?
So it sounded like there was a bunch of discussion on merch.
How's the rest of the building going?
Well, she's got ticketing designs.
We just talked about figuring out venues, which I assume
would be outreach to the venue owners.
That's pretty much it.
So it's what we've done so far.
I love it.
Love it.
Awesome.
And we're also coming up on our next session, I believe.
I've got my little papers here.
So we'll have in about five minutes, six minutes,
rock bot for founders.
Let's show.
Awesome.
One of our very own startups, growth folks.
So we're going to cut over to that in about five minutes,
just to head up.
Cool.
One thing, Eric, that I wanted to just pick your brain on.
So I know Carrot is like a platform for creators
and folks who are creating content, right?
And one of the things, these guys
are going to hate me for this,
because I've been harping on platforms all morning.
But we've been talking a little bit about how we're
going to go run this pop up.
But maybe some of the software we build
is generalizable for other people to run their own.
I think that's the goal.
I'm just curious.
What are your thoughts on just platform businesses
as your experience being a founder of one of these?
And I'm curious, obviously, there's
a stretch goal for us coming out of these three days.
But just given your experience,
I would love to hear what some of the ideas
that we've been cooking up.
Actually, what parts of what we've built,
do you think, with generalize?
It's a brilliant question.
I'll say two things.
The first thing is applying to my own company.
And the second is, for example,
when I used to work at Instagram.
So for our own company, the one-liner I gave
when I came on is we do banking and credit for creators.
Over time, that's actually expanded,
because yes, we initially built for YouTubers.
So some of the biggest streamers in the world,
like Alex Botest, a trust streamer,
or like Ludwig, they actually use us.
But when we built all of the primitives
to help these creative entrepreneurs bank their businesses
and get credit, at a certain point,
you're like, why can't I extend this
to other types of businesses too?
And so now we've gradually expanded
to other types of founders,
and small me and businesses.
What are the things that creators
love the most when it comes to that?
Like, it's such a unique user to be working with.
So today, banks generally suck,
because they're just dumb buckets for you
to put your money in, and then nothing ever happens.
The dream is you build a bank
that actually helps you grow as a business.
That's what we're releasing next year.
But for creators, an example of that
is we put them up on billboards,
because for creator, when they're featured up on a billboard,
that's content for them,
or we put together events
where they meet each other and they network.
And so for me, I think of a bank
as an archaic term we had to have in the 1950s,
when you needed a brick and mortar
institution holding your dollars.
And now we, in this new age, have to think about is,
here's a company that's licensed and regulated
to hold your money,
and has federally guaranteed insurance,
by holding your money and seeing the inflows and outflows,
combining that with AI,
what can it now tell you about your business
that you didn't know before that would help you grow?
That's the direction we're actually moving.
I love that.
And like for those of you who are on the stream
who saw Cody Sanchez earlier,
I think there's some callbacks to that
in terms of like, helping,
really it comes down to helping people
grow their businesses, right?
So for creators, that's a creator business
where they're like pouring their heart and soul into it,
and they want to be able to grow that.
For maybe folks who are coordinating events,
maybe that's an angle we should think about
with a platform here,
how do you really focus on helping them grow their top line,
their bottom line,
like really just like bring revenue into their own business.
For me, and I've had Cody on my podcast as well,
and I think of it as the exact purpose
of what we're doing right now
is also the answer to your initial question.
Crock-Pot might initially be adopted
by all of us in San Francisco who are very AI-pilled.
But the broader goal for AI
to truly have a beneficial effect on the economy
is for everybody to learn how to use it.
And what I think you've done with Crock-Pot,
you've built it in a user interface
and with familiarity such that we hope one day
all small meme business owners would use it, right?
Like Joe Plummer might want to use that.
That's why I think it's really interesting
to your initial question.
We're building it for an initial use case,
which is like us.
But if we get the primitives right,
it should be able to expand to much bigger demographic.
That's what we're doing at Carrot.
That's also what we're doing right here, right now.
We're doing the pop-up for us,
but eventually it could be a platform for others.
Yeah, I love that.
So I think we have three minutes left.
One thing I'm curious about before we cut over to Shub,
when it comes to creators and Crock-Pot,
what do you think, for any of the creators
who are watching and listening on the stream right now,
what are some cool ways creators could use Crock-Pot?
Just from your experience,
kind of having played the product a little bit
and kind of having hung out with us for a bit.
So my main thought is AI is most useful,
and this actually I believe comes from Cat GPT.
AI is most useful when it generates output
that is both correct and verifiable, right?
The main issue today is when it's not verifiable,
you don't know if it's good,
that's how you get quote unquote slop.
I think for creators, what's correct and verifiable
is actually less the creative part of what they do yet.
It's more the monetizable piece.
So if you're a creator, brand deals, right?
Today you're traditionally, once upon a time,
in Hollywood, depending on agents and gatekeepers
to figure that out.
Now anybody can build a brand online
and then go and monetize it
by finding the right brand partners
by having four different Crock-Bots, right?
One to figure out which are the right brands
to reach out to.
The second is actually go and reach out to them.
The third is to negotiate the race.
The fourth is to come up with content ideas.
Like that's just one example for a creator.
I think there are versions of that for every business owner.
You just look at your workflows and ask,
what is a workflow and loop that is verifiable?
Like I can look at it and know if it works.
Like coding is an example of a loop that's verifiable.
That's where you should go
and have Crock-Bots just go crazy.
I love that, I love that.
Cool, well with a minute left, I guess,
I know you said you're not super active on X,
tons of love in the chat.
Where can people find you?
Where can people learn more about what you're doing?
On X, sadly, it's just my company, Hount, Tri-Carat.
It's like not very large.
I am so sorry.
If you Google-
It might be larger after this.
It might be.
If you Google in me, you can find all the other places
that I'm online and bigger,
but I would never dare say their name
while we're here on X
because that's the main platform we're talking here about.
I love it, I love it.
So I just wanna say it was so much fun coming on
and like to all the folks listening.
Look, you can see the excitement.
We're just like, oh my gosh,
look what we can do with RockBot.
I think that's really the tick
we want you to take away as well.
And yeah, this has been a lot of fun.
Unfortunately, in a few seconds, I turned into a pumpkin.
It's been lovely getting to say hi.
Awesome.
Yeah, it was so nice to have you.
Yeah, you too.
Thank you so much.
Awesome, next to Howard from San Francisco,
we got RockBot for founder, Chubuar.
Take it away.
All right, hello everyone.
Welcome, really excited you all are here
and thank you for letting me interrupt the cooking session
that's happening on the live stream
and also for joining this workshop
about RockBot for founders.
I'm Chub and I spend a ton of time with founders
helping them optimize their RockBot setups
and ship quickly.
And so I'm very lucky to be pushing this product
to its limits and today I wanna share some of those learnings
with you guys and hopefully get into some live demos.
So let's get straight to it.
I'll start with what we're gonna talk about
over the next 60 to 90 minutes,
we will run through some really quick context
around RockBot, why it's particularly useful for founders.
And then finally, obviously some demos,
we gotta have those.
We will close out with some tips for power users
that people seem to love
and then also try to do some Q&A
for at least the folks that are here with us present live.
The final bonus piece I will add
is that I'll be sharing one of these bots at the end
so you can steal it for yourself.
I wish I had like a call now number, but we'll make do.
Also, there will be a few of you in this session
that are not founders, you will have snuck in,
which is awesome, kudos.
A lot of this will still apply to you,
especially if you are head of X at your company.
So stay posted.
And for those of you with RockBots watching this session,
this is the time for you to probably watch it live
because we got some cool stuff going on.
So let's get straight to it.
A few of you have probably already seen some version
of an AI maturity curve.
Everyone is freaking out about this these days,
but for us, we are really optimistic
with how the world of AI is changing.
As models improve and the tooling improves,
we are able to scale our productivity quite a bit.
And so you'll see that we started with chat bots,
moved on to ephemeral agents that finish a task,
and then you kind of throw them away.
And now bots are kind of this next iteration
of what we're really pumped about,
which is bots that automate your jobs
and bots that you can have around for a really long time.
The key part is that these bots actually compound.
And I think that's the most important piece
is you let them do a task, but you don't throw them away.
You keep them around, you invest in them,
and they get better with you the same way an employee would.
Finally, what we're aiming for is this world
where you can just fully automate a staff function
for yourself and scale yourself with a team of bots.
And we're getting pretty close to that internally.
We've seen some external examples of that,
and I wanna share some of that today.
But we're really excited about what RockBot can do.
I know this is all very high level,
so maybe we get into the specifics really quickly.
How many of you here have used RockBot before?
Just quick check, live at least.
Perfect, most of you it seems.
So I will blaze through this.
RockBot is obviously a new tool
that you can talk to just like a coworker or teammate.
You basically text it like iMessage,
and it can go off and do a lot
of really cool things for you.
It is very proactive and very ambitious.
And the reason it can do those things
is because we have armed it with its own computer.
So unlike traditional agents where they don't have the MCP
or the API or some sort of direct connection
to what they need to do,
RockBots can go off and do things on their own
even if they don't have the perfect level of access.
And we'll get into how that works
in the demos really quickly.
But they learn from you, they're proactive, like I said,
and they have their own device.
And so they can not only connect
to other products directly,
but they can use your tools the same way you would.
And I'll explain what that means in a second.
But overall, what you need to know
is you can assign RockBot's tasks completely end-to-end.
So for you, all you need to do is delegate to them.
And the mental load of having to check on your agents
and make sure they've done their work is gone
because in the ideal state,
a bot just handles the full end-to-end flow for you
just like a colleague would.
And they just figure it out, as I like to say.
Okay, with that, obviously a ton of founders in here.
And so you probably know what RockBot is,
and you're wondering what can this thing do for me?
And so there are a few things
that are really important to understand.
First, you all know your responsibilities as founders, right?
You have three key execution pieces
that either make or break your company.
And those are, one, you need to preserve your focus.
You have a trillion things hitting you all day.
Two, you need to do that while maintaining velocity
across all of the things that your team is shipping.
And then finally, you need to really protect your ability
to make great, high-quality insights all day.
That means good decisions and planning for the future.
And RockBot is uniquely positioned
to make all of this way easier.
You'll see some features appear on this slide,
but I think most importantly,
RockBot can handle all of the distractions
in your day-to-day work.
The stuff that is necessary,
but not necessarily the most important,
you can just hand off to RockBot.
And that mental load that it saves you
is probably more important than anything else
I'm going to talk about today.
And so it's worth you taking the time to audit
what that means for you.
The second is, like I said,
it can get its tasks done end-to-end.
And so that means you really want to prompt your bots
to do all of the work for you.
Not just parts of it the same way you're used to today,
but really do all of it.
That includes the execution
and the verification of what it's done.
And then finally, I think there are large amounts
of information that we're all consuming every single day.
My screen time on X today is very embarrassing,
and I'm sure your guys hopefully is too.
And what that means is
there's just a constant flow of information.
In order for you to maintain the same level of quality
on your insights,
you need to find a way to triage that entire fire hose.
And RockBots are really well positioned to do all of that.
Okay, with that, it's pretty clear to most of us now
that this is the best time in history to build something,
especially in software.
And Lingji, who's one of our engineers,
he was talking earlier,
mentioned that he can ship way faster with RockBot
than he ever could before.
I'm sure all of you have seen this at this point
by kicking off cloud agents.
There is this ability to delegate these full tasks
that I will harp on forever.
You can automate a lot of the pieces
that you have to think about constantly with routines.
So you can have them set on schedules, on web hooks,
on signals, so that once they're taken care of once,
they can just happen forever.
And then finally, and I think most importantly on this
slide is you can do things that don't scale,
except you can actually scale them, which is really cool.
I'll get into a demo around how that works,
but we've all heard the stories
of how most startups win their first customer.
There's some sort of hacky approach
where you build some very niche, super-
We're a janky prototype and just hope that it works for them.
And then when they finally sign that contract, you breathe a sigh of relief and then you do
it a hundred times again.
And so with this and with Grok Bot, you can now make all of this happen without the constant
headache that comes with it.
And I'll get into a demo about that in a second.
But we're very excited about what this means for founders specifically, because you're all
generally the most high agency people out there.
And so if you have a product that enables that agency, we get to some very, very cool
ships coming out in the next few years.
OK, let's get into some use cases that I'll be harping on today.
Obviously, you all experience your own unique pain points, but these are a pretty good reference
point for how you can use Grok Bot in your day to day.
And the four I'm going to talk about are first, closing customers.
So this is the do things that don't scale part.
It is way easier now than it has ever been to take your customers and go with them end
to end without you having to do a lot of that hand holding and the intimate conversation.
You can really focus on just getting your bot to handle most of it and then step in when
absolutely needed.
The second is product changes.
As you know, engineers ship way faster now.
You're probably shipping way faster.
And staying across that many people shipping that quickly can sometimes leave you with
some pretty embarrassing moments.
There were actually times when I was demoing Grok Bot in its earliest forms.
We removed a certain feature that was in the sidebar.
I was so used to pointing at it.
When it was unshipped because I was busy that day, I didn't see it.
I was kind of demoing and pointing at nothing, which was really embarrassing.
I hope someone else has gone through that experience because it is not fun.
But this will go through how you can stay across all these product changes.
The third is adapting to competitors.
I think this is the most fun demo we're going to do today.
And also one that's been pretty useful for me at least.
So basically, there is now an opportunity because these bots can work as you to go through
other products and other competitors and get a lot more insight than you ever could manually.
And then finally, shipping feedback quickly.
We all get feedback all day.
Believe me, we get more feedback than probably anyone and a lot of it is not very nice.
So please be nice to us.
But shipping feedback quickly is super important.
And so I will go through how you can do that as a founder.
All right, without further ado, let's meet my squad here.
We're going to go through four bots today.
The first is the closed bot.
That is the one that handles my customer.
The second is prod bot, which is what figures out what's been shipped and helps me stay across
all of it.
The third is stock bot.
That is the competition stalker.
And the fourth is protobot, which is pretty fun.
It makes some designs for me, but it also turns feedback into PRs.
And then we have a little guest star that I'll talk about in a second.
Okay, with that, let's get into the actual demos.
All right.
Here is my Grokbot interface.
I'm on a demo interface right now.
Usually there's a lot more mess on this screen, so hopefully it's a little cleaner and easier
to parse for you guys.
The first bot I'll start with is closed bot.
And there are two key things that I want you guys to keep in mind while I go through this.
The first is remember that your bots can compound.
So you can constantly be feeding them insights and information, and they will store it,
reference it when necessary, and get better over time, which is really important.
The second thing is, like I said, they can use your computer and work with your tools,
which gets really important as you start to try to do things end-to-end.
So closed bot here, and I'll leave a little cheat sheet on the side for you guys,
does a few things.
It focuses on prepping calls.
So when you need to talk to a customer, it will do a ton of deep research on them.
It'll look through our telemetry and what we've done with them, and
make sure that we have complete insight into how they work.
And then it will finally do a walkthrough of what they're building and
their site in case it's relevant to what we talk about.
There are a few other steps, but I'll start by asking my bot to prep the call.
And in this case, again, I'm in a demo environment.
I don't wanna leak anyone's personal data or any company's personal data, but
this bot will go off and basically prep a call for
this company that we're calling Northwind.
And the way it does this, and the way I actually do this right now,
is it pulls all of the data for its usage.
So if you are a founder and you obviously have that telemetry, it is very good for
customers that are just trying out your product on a free trial to understand
what they're actually doing within your product.
And then also to understand who they are.
Those are probably the two most important things before you get on to
a customer call, because that is how you resonate with them in the quickest
manner possible.
Again, you don't have that long with these folks.
You generally have around 15 to 20 minutes with your customers.
And so what's really important is you get to the crux of what they need and
match it with what you're doing.
And bots help you do that really quickly.
And so right now, it's going through essentially some demo prep.
But what I'll show you is an example of what I tend to use day to day when I
talk to founders.
This is a call prep HTML file.
Obviously, it doesn't look perfect and that doesn't matter,
cuz I'm not sending it to anyone, it's just for me.
But basically, the goal of this is to really understand who these people are
that I'm going to be talking to, what their product does,
which Crockbot will research on its own, and then walking through their site.
The reason the site is really important is actually because the site tells you
a lot about what they care about, first and foremost,
which is why I like including some screenshots of what they're building.
But more importantly, I am constantly finding bugs on people's sites.
And it is so nice for me to just be able to go to them and say, hey,
fix this thing.
Look, your cookie banner is on top of your submit button and
that sucks for everyone, so just go fix it.
And for them, it's really nice cuz they get some feedback that's super actionable.
And so my bot has gotten very good at figuring out what will resonate with
folks, and so I have it do this every single time.
And without fail, it has found some issue that comes up with some site,
which is a really cool way to open a call.
So just one of those quality of life things.
As we keep scrolling, you'll see these are placeholder numbers, but
you'll see that you get a lot of the activity that's really relevant to
what you want to talk to them about.
So we know in this case that these folks already have some seats.
They already have done some meetings.
This product is like a meeting tool.
They have some sort of arrangement.
And because I can look at this graph, I can see what their usage looks like.
And so I look at this every single time when I talk to founders to try and
understand, are they really accelerating?
And is there a specific feature that I need to work with them on?
Or are they declining and there's some sort of objection that I need to get into?
With you guys, you will all have your own versions of this use case.
But it is so, so important to just spend five minutes before the call figuring
this stuff out.
Now, for the really cool part that I'm a little conflicted on, recommendations.
The bot has gotten very good at figuring out what I need to talk to founders about.
And in your case, what you will probably need to talk to customers about.
And what that means is it will give me a few key recommendations
about what I should do with that founder or customer on that call.
And so the most important piece for you guys is you have your customer
conversations is to come in armed with some sort of knowledge.
And this automates getting some of that knowledge.
There are a few other pieces here.
It talks about some risks.
And I think the most important part is that you come in prep.
You don't have to spend the hour and a half of your time doing this.
And it does it on a routine.
So every day, it will look at my calendar and look at the meetings that I have and
just prep them.
And I can trust that five minutes before I can go in and read that stuff.
So that's part one, which is prepping the call.
Part two is what happens after the call.
We want to go end to end.
We don't just want to stop there.
And so the same bot also does a little bit of the compounding for me.
And what that means is after every call, it will review the granola transcript and
figure out what that person resonated with or didn't.
And you can do this with all of your customer calls as well and
arm your teams with it.
You basically have your bot look at every single transcript.
And for example, if in this case, I was talking about some new note taking feature
that they didn't really care about and they express that within the call.
For the next one, for the preparation document,
this tool will get better at making sure that I'm not talking about
that feature again unless it's really relevant.
And so over time, if you give this two or three weeks,
it becomes really, really powerful.
Because not only do you not have to go through other people's calls and
you can leverage theirs, but your calls just get way better.
And you stop tripping over yourself when you talk about the same things.
Okay, that's part two.
Part three is support.
Basically, we have a lot of customers and a lot of them need support.
And right now, there are not enough people to support all of those customers
on their own, just one on one.
And so you need to be able to scale up your support.
And a lot of founders leave this to the very last thing.
Believe me, I've been there.
And it makes your life very, very tough to handle both getting new customers
through the funnel and then also supporting the pre-existing ones.
And so you have a real opportunity to automate this with RockBot.
But the most important part that makes this really work well is that you spend
the time empowering your bot to actually support your customers.
And what that means is you not only connect it to your data, but
you connect it to your billing.
And you connect it to the risky pieces that you're scared to give,
because that is where most of the support struggle happens.
And so that in combination with the compounding piece leads us to
this really cool fourth section, which is activation.
And so a lot of you probably know your wow moment at this point.
You know when your customer is activated.
You know when they're going to stick around.
And so how do you incentivize more of that?
How do you decrease time to value?
One of the easiest ways to do that is to give people money so
that they get there.
And it doesn't have to be much, right?
But just getting them across that hump is what turns people into great customers.
And so I have hooked up this bot to actually do the work and
when an activation event happens.
Where in this case, again, I'm using a note taking app.
If a template is shared with your teammates, we have $1,000,
which is a crazy example, ready to send.
And it will automatically send that email with those credits so
that that user or that customer can leverage those credits and
they feel rewarded in that moment.
And so instead of you having to monitor every single customer's journey and
do this manually, or taking a tool and building it from scratch,
you can just offload it to your bot and not think about it again.
And it will run the campaign on its own.
Okay, there are a few other pieces that are pretty obvious around the end to end
customer journey, right?
You want them to sign contracts, which you can get GrokBot to go back and
forth with them on.
You want them to figure out your pipeline and
actually generate it without bound, which GrokBot is very good at.
And then you want it to actually make sure that your calendar is filled.
And it can access your calendar and do that every single time.
So these are all things that happen autonomously, and
I no longer need to worry about 99% of this journey.
There are cases where I want to step in with a customer and
I want to understand, hey, why didn't this call resonate?
I want to go deeper.
And for now, what that means is I spend my time doing that,
which is actually very enjoyable.
I actually enjoy talking to customers.
So that's what I meant when I was saying this is a little emotionally
complicated for me, and that some of this is really fun to do.
And so I have to intentionally go in and
steal some of this back from my bots rather than letting them do all of it.
But it is a very, very cool time to be able to scale to thousands of
customers with just your bots instead of you having to go do this yourself.
And that way, like I said, you can focus on making good decisions consistently,
maintaining velocity, and maintaining focus.
Okay, that was bot number one.
Let's go to bot number two.
This is prod bot.
I mentioned that example earlier,
where as you start to have more and more engineers shipping more things and
unshipping more things, you're doing it yourself,
you get confused around what's live and isn't.
So prod bot is basically a bot that does a lot of this work for
you in terms of staying across what's been shipped.
And so I'm currently asking it to give me a daily rundown of fly low,
which is the demo surface that we used earlier in the PM conversation as well.
And fly low is a tool for flights and airlines and booking travel.
And what I like to have this bot do in my actual day to day is not only go
through all of the PRs and the linear issues that come in,
but also walk through the product end to end itself.
Remember, your bots have their own computer, so
they can use whatever surfaces you use.
And in this case, that means going through the site that the bot is assigned
to, figuring out what has changed, and then mapping it to its experience.
So if it has a login for the specific site, it can do a lot of this work for you.
You can see some of it popping up right now.
What you'll notice if I scroll through this is it's giving me a rundown.
So it gives me, here's what's shipped.
These are some examples of things that have shipped recently.
It also gives me things that were unshipped, so I avoid that embarrassment again.
And most importantly, it will give me some decisions and
some key things where now that we ship quickly,
we don't intentionally make all of these micro decisions all the time.
And so it tries to catch some of those that we want to be a little more
intentional about.
And so overall, what you end up with is a bunch of screenshots of the site.
So the bot is going through it.
And then also, you end up with a video of the bot basically running through
the site itself, and so that way you can see what it does without having to
do it yourself.
So if you ever want to get in deeper, you can always ask your bot to take a
video of the surface while it's doing its work, which has become the fastest
way to verify if something is done well or not.
The other piece is that you can connect this to your data.
So you can actually see what the results of different ships are because you
connect it to your metrics.
And that way, instead of you having to view that dashboard all day,
you just see it here.
And it is proactively given to you, which I think is one of the most
important parts about bots, that they will surface information to you as
relevant and as necessary.
And so I think, again, what's really important is as long as you enable them
to have all of the right data, they can help you make great decisions and also
help you stay across what your team is shipping.
OK, now for my favorite bot, Stockbot.
Right now, everyone is probably distracted by their competitors,
and it is very easy to ship things.
But what's not easy is checking what other people are shipping.
And so what Stockbot does is it basically will go find your competitors.
It will sign up for autonomously and go through their product.
And then it will give you a full rundown of basically everything they do.
So that includes what they've shipped, their change log, what they're posting
on X, who they're hiring for, which is actually a really good way to get
signal on what people are building, and finally, just who their team is
and what they're prioritizing.
And over time, this also compounds.
As they learn about more and more competitors, your life becomes easier
because you start to get more signals into how to position yourself
in the market and also how to counterposition to what they're shipping.
And so what I'll do right now is kind of ask it to do a competitor pulse
right now.
And basically, I want it to check on Notion and Craft.
Those are the two hypothetical competitors we have with this note-taking
app.
And so it will go off and do all of this in parallel.
And it has been doing this for a while.
So it is constantly running pulses.
You see some of its routines on the side here.
And what you'll notice is that these routines run relatively often every few
days.
But what that also means is I don't have to do this myself.
They will run the routine, come back to me
if there's something relevant, and if not, it will stay silent and do its thing.
And so this is one of those ambient bots that's really important to just
have around because it will get a lot of this work done for you around
competitor analysis.
And you don't really need to think about it.
And as you get exposed to more and more of these decisions
that these companies are making, you actually
start to build the muscle around why your decisions are different.
And you start to understand truly what your positioning is relative to there.
So you'll notice it's cooking and doing some of the research work.
What we see here is let's start with Craft, which is a note-taking app.
Basically, it has created a little tear down in HTML if this thing loads.
If not, we can just look at it here.
Again, just created a video where it's going through, and it will sign up.
It'll put in its information.
It'll use a throwaway email address and then basically go
through the entire flow.
So this is the onboarding flow.
And it's looking through, hey, what is different about their onboarding
versus our onboarding?
And it gets you to the start page.
It will also start to actually test it itself.
So it will write in Craft, which is, again, this note-taking app,
and tell me what went well and what didn't.
And then give me a little overview of how it works.
Craft is not hiring actively right now.
So that's good for us to know.
And then the final thing that I've done with this one, which
might be corporate espionage, but do what you want with it
and be responsible, is basically I have it email people
that have churned off.
A lot of you have insights into where your customers are churning.
So you know from Salesforce or whatever your tool is
that x customer left to y tool.
And so you can actually go and have your bot reach out to them
and understand why that is.
You don't need to go win them back in that moment.
But just getting that insight is really, really important.
And so if you have that signal, it's another good way
to course correct your positioning versus others.
You can see the same thing for Notion.
Notion has a bunch of hiring.
And so I've kind of asked it to truncate
because they're hiring a ton of people.
But it's still important insight to get.
And so I'm showing you these two examples.
And this is one where it's signed into its own Notion
account.
It authenticated via email and is basically doing work in it
and giving me what that experience looks like.
As it starts to see the differences in what's shipped,
it will focus on those specific things.
OK, enough about this bot.
But what I will say is I will share this bot after this.
And I will toss up a QR code.
So if you want to steal it, you totally can.
All right, let's move on to bot number four.
So bot number four is my ProtoBot.
And this bot is basically really good for just thoughts
that I have in my head when I want to get them prototyped.
But also, it's really good for when
we get customer feedback.
And we want to just explore what
this would look like to ship.
And so what ProtoBot does really well
is it actually has right now its own version of GrokBot
running on its computer.
And I think I've shared this a few times before.
But I've given it its own account that is not it.
It has its own separate entity.
And it runs through a lot of different bots,
tests them out, and helps me with some of my prototyping
and also QAing.
But I think most importantly, and the reason this matters,
is because it has access to its own product,
it can do a lot of this prototyping
with the context of what the product looks like today.
So if I say pull the most recent customer feedback,
it will find some demo feedback, pull it in,
and then it will probably just start working on fixing it.
And so you as a founder can probably envision yourself
and your product piping all of your feedback channels.
So that means things like X, your support inbox,
or any other signals that you see in your emails,
and putting them all into a single pipeline that
goes to a bot that just kicks off PRs and solves them.
That's kind of how some of our engineers work internally,
which is very cool, because you'll
see the full feedback loop of feedback to ship to deploy
happen in hours, which is awesome.
And it happens automatically and organically,
which is very cool.
So I think you guys all know that adapting to feedback
is really important, especially in the early stages.
You still need to make the choice about which feedback
to take versus not, because you're the visionary.
Your job is supposed to be to figure that out.
And in this case, the fact that you can move this quickly
means the main bottleneck should be your decision making.
It should be whether this feedback should be shipped
or not.
And so it will basically do the work.
Right now, it's saying that the customer thinks
that the Share button for bot templates
isn't exciting enough, and they want it to pop.
So it'll probably end up working on that for a little bit,
which is very fun.
In the meantime, though, what I will show off
is two final bots.
One is my Yap bot.
So this bot has one purpose and one purpose only.
It is built and exists to talk like me.
So it looks through my emails, Slack, iMessage, any other form
of communication that I've done.
And it learns from how I talk.
And it doesn't just learn once.
I think this comes back to the compounding piece.
It learns over time.
So every week or so, or you can set it
to whatever schedule you want, it
will take everything I've sent for the day
because it has access to all those tools,
and essentially learn from them and get better over time.
So now, I can trust this bot to go and talk as me.
And what you'll notice is these other bots
are actually coming in and asking it for help.
So they are proactively bringing in Yap bot
to go talk like me across all of the different surfaces.
And I don't need to do this myself.
After they do this a few times,
I encourage them, like I said, they
learn to loop in the other bots as needed.
And this bot might seem like a small one
because it's very simple.
But it's so important, especially
if you're trying to do any sort of outbound or move quickly
on communications.
It's nice to have a bot you can just trust to do this
stuff.
Obviously, you have some emails
that are really sensitive.
So you might ask it to just keep them as drafts rather than
just sending them right away.
But even then, it will learn from the delta
between the draft it created and what was actually sent
and get better and better over time, with the end vision
being that you don't need to think about it at all.
OK, final tip, I have a miscellaneous bot.
And this bot has one job, which is basically
to be kind of a trash can for all of the random requests
I have.
Today, I wanted to see if Drake's album dropped.
It is not yet, sadly.
But what's really cool about this one
is I can just ask it random things
without polluting the context of the other bots.
And if it ever has any important tasks
to do where it needs to transfer that context,
I can just ask and say, hey, you learned about XYZ.
Go tell ProdBot about what you've
learned so that it can get better in the future.
Sadly, Drake's album isn't out.
It checked Instagram.
But who knows?
We'll get there maybe later tonight.
OK, those were all my bots.
I think ProdBot is still going.
It's kicking off a cloud agent.
And hopefully, it finishes sometime soon.
But you'll notice, because it has access to GrokBot,
it can actually just take a look at the interface
without needing to go find it anywhere.
And it can drive it and QA it.
And as these tests happen, it's very easily verifiable,
whether it's shipped the right thing or not.
And so I think all of these bots are very powerful.
And most importantly, they're all powerful in conjunction.
So when CloseBot gets some feedback,
it can pass it to ProdBot.
Or when ProdBot is trying to get across some of the key product
decisions that we've made, it can pass that context
off to CloseBot so that it can sell the right stuff.
And overall, I think the key framework that you folks
need to keep in mind is you want
to start to try and productize yourself as much as possible
and give away all of your LEGOs, no matter how delightful they
are, so that you can focus on the highest leverage thing.
Because that is what helps you win in a world where everyone
is shipping just as fast, if not faster for now.
So keep all that in mind.
But those are my bots.
Let's go back to the presentation.
OK, some final pieces.
What we learned, let your bots run free.
I am going to say this forever.
Give them access to as much as you are possibly
comfortable with, because that is the only way they
will be able to do work end to end.
You want to invest in them.
So you might find times where you need to course correct
a bot.
And with an agent, you might have the instinct of, man,
I spent too many tokens on course correcting it.
The context is polluted.
Let me just get rid of it and start a new one.
In this case, your key advantage is
that your bots get really good
as you spend more time with them.
And obviously, as the team has learned internally,
the more time you spend, the better you do.
And so it's really important to really believe
in your bots the same way you would with employees.
And the other piece to keep in mind here
is the other way to invest in them
is by giving them really good skills and tools.
So it's very easy to say, hey, make this cooler.
And that could be your prompt that you
want your bot to execute on.
But obviously, it's not going to do a great job.
And it's going to probably get stuck somewhere
and ask you a few questions.
The more intentionality you put behind that task
in the first place lets you repeat it over and over again
without that many hitches.
And then finally, it is worth you taking one to two hours
and just thinking about your day.
I know that sounds dumb.
I know you're like, I need to move quickly.
But it is so, so important to just take the time.
I don't care when.
Just do it and figure out what you want to delegate.
Because doing that intentionally will save you so many hours
versus just spinning up bots and hoping they do things
for you without having a true intent
around what they should do.
Now, I have a bonus round with some tips and tricks.
I was watching the livestream earlier.
And some people were like, this is expensive,
which is true in some ways, not true in others.
And we're working on it.
But there are some really easy, high-leverage tips
that can make your life a lot easier.
The first is that browser use is super powerful.
And it unblocks your bot from doing a lot of things
that it couldn't do if it didn't have
MCPs or APIs or some other connection.
But it's also expensive to run multiple times.
And the easiest way to solve for this
is to bias towards using APIs and using interfaces
that people have already built, or to actually kind of hack
it a little bit.
You can ask your bot to look at network requests
while it does a task once, and then figure out
which APIs are being hit while it's doing that task,
and then go and start to just hit those directly, which
takes way less time, first of all.
And it's also way more token efficient,
because you are no longer needing to go through the browser
interface.
And you can just do it all directly.
So ask your bot.
And this is true for all optimizations, by the way,
that you guys have probably been thinking of or taking notes
on.
Always just ask your bot how to do it,
because it will figure it out for you, which is very nice.
But be wary of browser use more than once.
And if you can get around it and scale quickly,
you absolutely should.
Second piece, routines.
When I was looking through some of the data
around the frequency of routines that people set,
I was a little shocked.
And it freaks me out how often you guys are running things.
But I think the most important part about routines
is to audit them.
And you don't have to do this yourself.
Again, get a bot to do it for you.
But the most important piece is be very intentional about how
often your routines are running.
They're really powerful, but most people
over-index on how often they need to be running.
And they think, this routine is so important.
I need to run it every 15 minutes, which comes out
to 100 times a day.
So that is a very expensive routine.
See if you can be a little more nifty with them.
So it's not just running them fewer times.
If you really need a routine, try and run them on webhooks.
Or try and run them with some sort of inbound signal
that will let your bots actually take in an input
and then run it, rather than just having it blindly
run on a schedule.
So those two things alone will probably
save you a bunch in tokens.
I know there was some demand for that.
OK, even more final tips before they came me off stage.
Make a voice bot.
Obviously, I love mine.
Please do this for yourself.
It is the most underrated way to get words out to other people.
It's have a bot that copies your voice.
Import your cookies.
This lets you stay signed in across a lot of different tools.
And it also stops you from having
to constantly take over the bot's computer and help out.
Group bots by expertise.
This is kind of a personal preference thing,
but I love having my bots grouped by what they do.
And so if a bot is really good at just handling a customer,
I will give it everything customer related.
And if a bot is really good at data analysis,
that will be its sole job.
Because sometimes there are weird compounding pieces
that happen that we don't even know about.
And so when you're giving it to what
feel like completely different tasks,
you can still get some of the compounding benefits
as long as they all fall under the same expertise.
There are a few more on here, like Great Skills,
which we talked about how bots can learn from you.
And then auto optimization routines.
But I think the last one is also pretty important.
Having a bot that just exists to optimize your other bots,
that means better routines, figuring out
where they went wrong or where you had to ask multiple times
for something, and then making sure that doesn't happen again.
And overseeing how the other ones work and improving them
is way easier than having to do a lot of this yourself.
So save yourself the time.
You set it once, and then you forget it, which is really nice.
And I don't see enough people doing that.
OK.
So that is close to the end of what we've been doing here.
Thank you for your time and attention.
I am going to leave a QR code for Stockbot.
If you guys want to steal it, it's a fun one.
You should try and use it on us.
I think that would be cool.
I want to see what people come up with.
But I really appreciate everyone being around.
I think one of the coolest parts about these bots
and where they're headed.
Is just how creative you can be. The amount of different bots and different combinations of bots that I've seen has really blown me away.
And I think founders are the perfect group to figure out the edges of this entire thing.
I don't think we've hit the limits yet. And as we get closer and closer to figuring out what these bots can actually do and what they can't,
we're going to be looking for signal from you guys. So really appreciate it.
If you are on the livestream, we're going to send you back to Matt, Lauren, and Roshan to go and continue cooking.
So appreciate it. Thanks. OK. For those of you here, we will take 15 minutes and answer some questions you have.
So we'll have some facilitators who maybe have mics, if not, just yell really loudly and we'll go from there.
So raise your hand if you have a question and we'll get after it. Yes, up here.
The idea of treating bots like humans. So you said you should spend one to two hours setting bots up.
Do you have a framework or suggestions as to how you actually do this?
What's the way in which you create jobs or roles and responsibilities for bots?
Yeah, the question is, like, what's the best way to set them up essentially? Right.
I think when you're trying to be intentional, there are two things that matter. Right.
One is figuring out what you need them for. So like actually inventorying every single thing that you need to do is pretty important,
because then you can start to group those things. And like I said, I like my bots to be experts.
And so they will have a very specific domain that they're good at.
And then they will expand their scope as I have more questions for them outside of that domain.
And so I trust them to do things outside of what they've been assigned.
But for the most part, I try to group them in, you know, your finance bot or your job is dealing with customers or job is like marketing generally.
And that's worked for me. Some people really like having the chief of staff
bot that manages the others. I personally am not a fan, but it really comes down to personal preference.
Right. If you're someone who just wants all of the work abstracted away, you just want to talk to one.
It's a good way to go. But if you really like being a little control freak and getting into the weeds,
I think having multiple bots that are all experts that you can then train up is it's kind of a good way to go.
And I would love to give them little XP bars for something as you go. But, you know, we'll see. Yes. Right here.
I just I just had a question about managing robots on multiple computers.
Is there any tips for that to work kind of and not get confused in the whole ecosystem?
Yeah, yeah. So I think like a week ago, bots would get pretty confused across multiple computers if you have them.
That is something that we're actively working on making better.
I know there are a lot of folks that used to be on other setups and had stacks of Mac
minis lined up and they want to utilize all of them. So it's something we're actively investing in.
Right now, that should actually work a lot better. So if it doesn't, we should chat.
But yeah, thank you for the question. Great. Hi. Yeah. When it comes to like serious enterprise use
and you have actions and decisions. So is there a way of putting those,
having those decisions follow a certain deterministic rule or policy that is outside the model?
Like, you know, like to ensure everything is safe. It doesn't do anything without going through that rule.
Yeah. So the question is, like, how do we make sure that models act deterministically in this tool?
Well, they inherently don't, sadly. But the easiest work around there is probably to
make sure that your models just write code and code itself is inherently deterministic.
So as long as you kick off cloud agents to write in code and you give it a little decision tree,
it can basically play the deterministic part. And then you just tell the model to call that
function every single time you need it. You can you can tell bots to ask other bots for
permission if you need to. But I think the better way to go about it is just to
give it a rule and say every single time you need to make a decision related to this,
look at this flow chart and then execute it. And as long as it has some sort of code to execute on
that is verifiable, it will be able to cosplay being deterministic. Yeah. Cool. Yeah, yeah.
Two answers to that. The question was, is there, like, a good way to import all of your setup from
other tools? One, working on it right now, I have pretty cool bot that I want to share in
the next few days that should make this a lot easier. But two, I think part of this is
making sure that all of your connections are interoperable, right? Like, there's,
you have your collection of MCPs and APIs that you already access. And right now, they're probably
dispersed among a bunch of different tools. And I think the easiest way to bring them all together
is the same way you're kind of doing it with agents and skills, right? Like,
where you either have them Simlink or have a direct source of truth to handle all of them.
On the Linux piece, it makes it a little more difficult. But I think there's some cool
integrations you can use. Like, one password is an easy one, where if you just import everything
in and then use the MCP, it does a really good job of figuring all that out for you. And then
the other is cookies, like I talked about, where you can import all your cookies from
Chrome or your browser. And then you just use those sessions within your box. Yeah.
Yeah. So there are a few authentication pieces that we're still figuring out, right? And then
the other piece is, we have some companies who are like, hey, we don't actually want
bots on our platform. Our goal is to be good ecosystem players overall. And so those are
challenges that are going to exist across any tool in this ecosystem. But it's something
we're actively working on. So it's a good question. Yeah, it's when we're asking ourselves.
Yeah.
So, I think, so the question is like, hey, this kind of isn't working for me, right? Like,
I'm trying to authenticate into this tool. And it's asking me for all this stuff. Like,
how do I deal with it? I think it just depends on your setup, right? And I think one of the
best ways to use GrokBot is to just ask it to figure this stuff out and not be super
prescriptive on the tool. So for me, the reason I landed on granola in the end was not because
I'm a huge granola fan. It's literally because it was the easiest form factor for GrokBot to pull
transcripts and get me the insights I needed, especially for things that are happening on
device. Over time, that might change. And my bot that is working on optimizing my other bots
will probably figure out like, hey, wait, this is now a first class, like first party
integration. And I want to use that instead. So I think being less prescriptive on the tool
should help. But also your point is heard, right? Like, it is really frustrating when you're trying
to connect a tool and it just doesn't work on its own box. So I think parts of it are just getting
more creative right now as we're in the early stages. And the hope is eventually we are able
to handle all of this demand across all these different tools as we start to introduce more
plugins in the marketplace. Great question. You, yes. Not yet. Yeah. We'll see. Yes, right here.
Yeah. Hey, so a lot of legacy services either don't have APIs or have API access that costs
much more than the UI access. How fast is GrokBot going to get where kind of the answer that we're
looking for instead of using APIs, it will be just as fast as kind of going through the UI flow.
Yeah. So the question is like, how do we make sure that going through the UI flow
can eventually get just as quick as using an API? Yeah. Are there things that we can do to
make it? Cool. I think there are two things that help optimize here. One is trying to go headless
as much as possible. So using a headless browser to do a lot of this work quickly for you. And
that way you don't have to navigate UI. You just basically give it commands to click pieces in the
DOM instead of having to look at it, screenshot, make a decision, rinse and repeat. And the second
thing is we're doing a lot of work on our model to make them faster and better with computer
use. So I think overall the promise of being faster than an API is a little tougher, especially
as you add more layers to it because inherently the performance is worse. But our goal is to get
as close as we can. And over time that's kind of where we're headed. Cool. Yes. Right here.
I have a question about how do you make sure that you can also choose the right one?
Yeah. So the question is like, how do we optimize for multiple GrokBots? And then if we're trying
to be really aggressive with them, how do we make sure they make good decisions on themselves?
Is that right? And also token optimization. Okay. So the first thing is right now we have this
feature that you all can use that is like putting bots in a group chat. And that comes with pros
and cons. The pros are that you get a bunch of bots that are really eager to do a lot of work
for you and they can work together, which is cool for very complicated tasks where you
loop them all in. The con is that they will all talk. They all love to talk. And because
they're all proactive and ambitious, when you put them in a group, they will start to speak over
each other and they will work really hard, but they will also get really expensive as they start to do
more and more. And so I think the part to be cautious about is whether that's the right form
factor. Right. Sometimes you just want a bot to tag two other bots once and work with it
separately versus having them all in a group chat and watching them all respond like crazy.
So I think that's one that you probably want to stay away from for now. Two is on the token
optimization and model optimization. I think we're obviously constantly working on making
sure the bots are using the right model for the job across everything like browser use and even
internal bots. But I think the harder question is what happens when you're shipping, right? And
which models you use. The way that gets solved today is just by using cursor or Grok build
and using those cloud agents. You can specify which models they use yourself if you want to
tune it. And you can even give them defaults if you just ask the model, like, hey, I want you to
use XYZ model for this specific task every single time. The final piece I'll say is not many people
know this. You can just message your bot and tell it to forget things. So if you're finding out that
it's, you know, referencing a piece of context way too much, you can just say, hey, forget all
things about how we generated your profile picture. Just don't ever think about that again.
And it does a pretty good job about clearing that out and becoming better, which also helps
with that token efficiency. Yeah, thanks, man. Let's go back there. White shirt. Yeah, the question is,
how would I rate or rank? Okay, how do I rate the bots on the marketplace? Yeah. So how do
how do I evaluate whether a bot is valuable on the marketplace? So we have our internal marketplace,
x.ai slash bot slash marketplace, I think. And that marketplace is really cool and useful
because it is all hand audited by us right now. And so we have a lot more bot templates than you
can imagine. But we're making our best effort to go through and find the actual most valuable ones.
And then if we get consent, we try and optimize them for folks. And then if they're good enough,
we put them on our marketplace. The easiest way to check whether a bot is doing a good job
is honestly, just try it yourself, for the most part. And most of these bots,
you can ask it an initial setup question, say, hey, what do you do and how do you do it without
actually having it run through the whole process. And that way you can do a little bit of that
self selection early. But the one thing I can say is at least for our marketplace,
you can probably trust the bots in there. So they've gone through a pretty thorough review,
which not only includes human review, but also we have bots that review the bots, as you guys
saw, which is pretty fun. Cool. Yes, right here. Got it. So the question is how do bots
talk to each other across people? So across people and across accounts? It's something
we're working on. And we're trying to see what the best form factor is across all of it.
It does not exist in our capabilities today. But it is a very cool use case. And we're excited for
that one. Yeah, back there. First of all, he said codec, so everyone get him. I think good answer.
Okay, so the question is, how do we use local and the bots computer at the same time?
The first thing I'd say is go to your settings and turn on local execution. So you can just allow
it, allow it by default, if you want. That's kind of the easiest way to go. And that lets you do
some cool stuff. It lets you send messages from your computer directly. It lets you drive your
browser if you really want to. And so you can do local execution. The reason we bias towards
moving so much of this to the bots computer is because we think that's the future. We think
models get better and faster. And obviously, the computers get stronger. You get a lot of your work
done and delegated off of your device. And there are a few reasons why doing things locally
is kind of janky, even if it's convenient in their near term. And those are, one, especially
for certain apps, unless they've been solved for, they will just pop up on your screen while
you're working, which means you can't do things in parallel. You know, people are trying to fix
that, but it's not a perfect solution. And then, two, they use up your computer's resources,
which gets really annoying if you're doing some high intensity stuff. But it's definitely heard,
and you can use it right now if you really want to. Just go to settings. Yeah, good question.
Yes, all the way in the back. I could not hear that. Sorry. Got it. Okay. So the question is,
do all the bots share the same memory? They do not share the same memory, but they do share
the same file system. So a bot's computer is actually one VM with a bunch of different instances
for each bot, the same way you would have different desktops on your computer. And
they share files. So you can have them read each other's files, and they will actually proactively
do that if they need to for a task. But their context window is obviously not the exact same,
if that's what you're asking. Cool. Thanks. Yes, right here. Got it. So the question is around
the interplay of cursor cloud agents and then Grokbot, right? We actually have a first class
integration, which is kind of a perk of having Grok and cursor be together, where you can kick off
cloud agents and Grokbot can transfer only the relevant context to them. And that means that
they can work independently as a cloud agent and then come back with the results. And then what
Grokbot can do, as long as it has access to the environment, is it can actually go and QA it,
it can test it, it can even look at the PR or whatever has been shipped and work with it
directly. So I think the most important part is actually figuring out when to use a cloud agent
versus when to just use Grokbot. And I think anytime you have some sort of complicated task
or something that you want to ship and you want full control over which model is being used,
and you want to be able to go and really change things, that's when you use a cursor cloud
agent. But I think trying it out a few times will actually get you the intuition you need
to answer that question for yourself. So highly recommend just like spinning up a few and getting
them to ship things and you'll find that it does a surprisingly good job with the orchestration
piece when it hands things off to cloud agents. You just have to specify once. Cool. All right,
that seems like all the questions we had. A few more really quick notes. One, Starbase.
You can win a trip to Starbase, which is very cool. I don't know if I'm eligible for this or
not, but I hope I am. This is a pretty simple challenge and it is a very cool like once in a
lifetime opportunity. So highly recommend trying it out. I don't know how we got this approved,
but basically we have a challenge post that went out already.
Okay. Yeah, can you hear me? Okay, awesome. I can't hear them. I can't hear their sound yet.
Hopefully. Okay, I can hear you. I just can't. Yeah. Oh, I hear sound now. Okay, you got us, Jenny?
Yeah. Okay, cool. Awesome. I got you. We just gave an intro, but we'll do one more quick intro,
I think, just to catch everybody up and then we'll jump into the conversation if that sounds right.
Sounds awesome. Cool. Jenny, thanks so much for joining us. You lead an incredible community of
women building and exploring with AI. You have a background spanning venture capital, technology,
and community building. And from what we see have developed sort of an incredibly thoughtful
approach on building a media business across platforms, channels, and formats. We're obviously
building a business today. And oh, I see we're joined by a special guest too. So thanks for
bringing on. Yeah, we got our first, our first rock baby. Oh, I love it. I love it.
Gotta teach them young. Well, we're excited for you to join us. I think we're, we might have some
sound issues in the stream, but we'll see if we can fix those. Okay. We're building a business
today. I don't know how much of our stream you've caught over the course of the day,
but we're working on building a business powered by Grokbots. We know you're a really active
Grokbot user. And so maybe we just love if you could start off by telling us a little
bit about yourself and how Grokbot has been useful to you. Yeah. So as everybody can see,
in addition to being a BC, being a full-time creator, building an entire media empire,
I also have a brand new baby. And so I have been able to basically double down on building
all of my companies because I have Grokbot. So most recently, I just built out my brand
new media agencies. So I have an agency called Gemma Media, where we basically build executive
brands. And I've got 22 Grokbot employees. Oh my God. So it's such a really interesting time,
because you normally wouldn't be able to do this kind of thing. And now, because I've got all of
these Grokbots running, I'm actually able to build businesses while raising a baby at home and doing
simple things all at once. So yeah, it's been pretty incredible. Tell us a little bit about
these bots, 22 of them. I'm really curious. Yeah. So, um, I have seven different businesses that I run.
Ranging from real estate to VC fund to my media business, to my agency. So we've got,
we basically, Chef did not like the chief of staff model, but we do have a chief of staff.
We have to call him master chief. My husband named that. And so master chief basically is the
chief of staff that oversees all of our different businesses, ranging from, you know, overseeing
like our tenants and guests in our rental properties, all the way to managing our agencies,
all the way to even like managing inbound, you know, brand partnerships, things like that.
And so it's basically one chief of staff that is running everything. Jenny, co.
You've set up, it sounds like a bunch of bots. Like are these sort of specific to specific parts
of the business? Like, yeah, I mean, how, like, why, why so many? And like, what are they all
working on? Yeah. So basically we, we have them all doing kind of an individual task. So,
you know, we've got like, for instance, boxy is like just the inbox monitor. We've got scribes,
scribes in charge of like every time we whisper flow every single meeting that we do. And then
that note taker intakes it. And that's in charge of taking every single thing from every meeting
and delegating it out to sub agents. We've also got like an entire CFO set up on there where
it's doing all the different bookkeeping finances, keeping a drug in my receipts. Like when I'm out,
for instance, it, they basically all kind of do a core function. And then we use the chief of
staff to spin them up and do essentially that group conversation. The shop was just talking about,
like they literally jump in on a project altogether and essentially, you know,
chat and get everything spun up. So I love some ideas. We've been pivoting a little bit as we
kind of figure out, yeah, kind of, we're going to build a business in 72 hours. And obviously you
have some experience there, both building and advising. And so we're really keen to just like
learn from you a bit and think about how we should improve our idea or kind of change our idea.
So I think we're working through a couple of things on our side around virtue, you know,
like an in-person pop up, thinking about how we might allow folks to connect to local businesses.
That's been a really interesting angle as part of the day. Also exploring some ideas around how
we might let folks who aren't located near us, maybe jump in and join the fun, perhaps virtually
in some way too. And so we'd just love to learn from your experience around events, businesses,
and, and like, you know, planning these types of things. Like, you know, what comes to mind when
we're like, we think we want to build software for pop ups. Great idea, not great idea of
things that might work, things that we should keep in mind. Yeah. So I saw you were just on
with Eric, my buddy, and you know, he had a lot of great ideas. So the last thing I saw that
we were like walking through the inventory of merchandise. And so I think what would be
really cool to understand is like, right now, where are we at with like the actual pop ups
and the scheduling and everything that we actually want to execute? Like, can we get up to speed on
where you left it off with him? Yeah, yeah, we're like very behind. Yeah, we have a list of like
places we can reach out to. We haven't actually done any of that work. So we could start thinking
about that. But that's where we're at. Okay, so do you guys mind just turning it up? Can
the producers turn up the volume a little bit, you guys, your mic is still down a little low.
Okay, cool. Can you hear me all right now? Yeah, now I can. Awesome. I'll speak up a little bit.
Basically, we still have to reach out to places, we have some good venues that we can check out.
But we don't really have the logistics of how we work this thing out.
Okay, so the good news for y'all is that in addition to, you know, building a VC fund,
I also built one of the biggest pitch competitions in the world. So I'm very familiar with venue
selection. So in terms of the venues that we're looking at right now, we're focusing on SF, right?
That's right. Yeah. Okay, so have we done any sort of like putting together a criteria
with one of the bots of identifying what we need in the venue? Yeah, so loosely, like, hey, we
want about 100 guests, we want kind of a warehouse space, we want it to be nice and open. So we can
have like sort of a gallery inside that in that space, maybe a little bit more than 100, I think,
but that's about the extent of that. Okay, so the first thing I can tell you as an event
producer is like, we need to think through venue logistics to add to it. So before we have a bot
go search out for venues, we need to get a little bit more detail. So number one, what's
the timing we want to do? Thinking sometime in the next month, maybe next month, maybe a little
bit longer, maybe a little longer to have to get some permits or something. Yeah. Well, so that's
the next question I'm going to say. So as somebody who's produced a lot of big conferences, permits are
a big thing in the state of California. They love permits. My last conference had more than
a dozen different types of permits. So are we thinking alcohol is involved? We'll say no,
just to make things really simple. What if we said no? Okay, you do streamline things quite a
lot. Do we want food? Okay, yes. Yeah. Okay. We want served hot food or are we doing grab and go?
We're thinking serve hot food. Yeah. Okay. So these are all the details that we're going to
want to put into a bot to do our venue search, right? So venue searching used to take event
producers like hours and hours and hours to scan the internet and put in all this different
criteria. But the best thing we can do is build basically like I call mine scout. Like this is
like the search bot that can go out and identify which of the venues in the county of San Francisco
meet this. So what I would do is like sketch out our capacity, which we've got. Do you want
this to be in the evening? Okay. So let's do we want the timing, because not all venues,
some venues are nine to five, some venues are closed in the evening, right? And then we're
going to want to put like what types of food we're going to want available. Do we want kitchen
facilities on site? So I was thinking originally that some of the prep would be able to be done
on site, but I can see how that would add another logistical later versus if we like hired a catering
company that then brought the food in, right? Okay. So if we're doing a catering company,
then you need to make sure that our venues are going to accept our catering companies. So a lot
of venues in the city of San Francisco are going to have preferred vendors for their catering.
So are we trying to do like bespoke or do we want to just kind of lock into what someone's already
working with? Ultimately, we probably care more about having a brand of working around the
kitchens might give us. I don't know if that's a great way to think about it, but I think,
you know, look, we want to create like a really fun environment. And I think have that be the
leading thing here. And then, you know, if there are things like preferences that we need
to consider, maybe that's like something we could ask a crockpot to help us go research and
figure out is that kind of where you're going with that? Yeah, I think that makes the most
sense because the way like the more specific we can get in the venue search, the faster we can
actually get to a result of like the availability, right? So the city of San Francisco, beautiful
place, 49 square miles. It's a very hot spot to find a venue. And there's also a lot of legality
when it comes to the city of San Francisco. So I think putting together a bot that does like our
venue scouting specifically would be like the next step here. And that bot can work in conjunction
with the other details of the event. So for instance, do we have an event planner bot yet?
Ooh. What would we do with an event planner bot?
Well, so how many pop-ups do we want to do? Just the one?
Yeah, do you want to start with the one and then kind of figure out what we do from there?
Okay, so then what I would want to do is it's almost like the chief of staff model, right?
So we basically reverse engineer an event producer.
So we have an event planner that works over top of what would be their coordinators and staff underneath,
but then we build this as a bot model.
I like that. So it seems like we should maybe start thinking about a team of bots
that could help us go and do all this work.
We have sort of like an event planner with context in the event,
and then maybe split out some bots that are more task.
I'm curious, like, what, you know, do you think like, is it email? Is it phone?
Like, should we think about giving our bots like the ability to call places?
How would you think about that, like the actual bot interactions with these venues
and like, you know, tying that into the AI and what we've done with RockBot so far?
Yeah, so I would definitely integrate it by email.
So like, for instance, I've got a bot that runs reselling all of my clothes across like Poshmark,
Depop, Markery right now, Interfaces.
One of my bots right now is reselling clothes as we speak
and negotiating bids with potential buyers for me.
So I set a framework around how to negotiate.
So we can not only have a bot that goes out and asks for RFPs for venues and availability,
but we can even prompt it further to be able to negotiate and go back and forth
because we'll give it parameters around what our budget is, right?
So that's one of the best things that I've been able to do with MyRockBot is it knows how to negotiate.
Totally. Okay. Okay. How did you teach your bot to be an A-plus negotiator?
And what tricks can we steal so that we have a really good, we have good luck with the negotiation part?
Well, I think that we need to first off establish our budget. Have we budgeted out the actual event?
We have not. And so I think what we need to do is we probably want to establish a baseline first, right?
Like establish a baseline for what venue rates look like, what maybe food rates look like,
and get a sense of how all the things can tie together.
And so maybe we kicked off some market research on ideas earlier today,
maybe you also should kick off some market research on kind of the price lines,
or maybe you have some knowledge you can share with us.
Yeah. So I have done this quite a while.
SF is one of the pricier cities for this type of thing.
So I think that an event planner bot would be great for this.
So you can actually ask the event planner bot to create the first production budget, right?
So we want to have the F&B costs in here.
We want to have the marketing costs.
We want to have any actual production costs for staffing.
Even though the Grokbots can get us like most of the way,
you are still going to need human beings doing the registration and the security.
So I think that starting with the event planner actually making a production budget
as a template and saying you are a senior event planner in the city of San Francisco
creating a budget for an event that meets blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
And then with those details, it can then go out and request RFPs to the venues
that actually meet those qualifications.
Okay. I'm going to go into a Grokbot right now.
You're a senior event planner in the city of San Francisco creating a budget for a hop-up
that will have 100 to maybe 200 guests.
I'm going to make that up. We can always change it later.
Let's say a pop-up event. You want to specify event.
Okay. Pop-up event.
Because a pop-up could be outside too.
And we need help with a budget that includes venue costs.
So it includes venue, includes food and beverage.
Yep, food and beverage.
We also want to make sure...
Yeah.
We're just getting a screen share up here real quick so everyone can see the content.
Roshan is getting up my work to make it a little bit bigger once we get the screen share on.
Yeah, I see. Hopefully I'm erring and we can get that up in a second.
So we'll let the team take care of this and we can be important to this problem.
Yeah, okay. So we need help with budget.
Totally.
With a budget that includes venue costs.
And sorry, go ahead.
So let's go venue, F&B, so food and beverage, right?
Yep.
We're also going to want to know staffing costs as well.
So some venues are going to provide staff with it.
Some venues don't. Depends on where you're working.
We're also going to want to find, are we baking the marketing budget into the event?
Or is the marketing budget a separate line item we're using for the entire event?
We'll just talk about a separate line item for now.
We just want to focus on the logistics of actually throwing the event.
And then we can figure out marketing separately.
Okay.
Okay. So event promotion typically would go in the event budget too.
So if you're doing any sort of like invitation design, meta ads to promote for signups or anything like that,
you can either house that in your marketing budget for the company or in the event budget,
depending on how you structure the business.
So both of them work.
It just depends on what you see it.
Do you see it serving only the event or do you see it serving the broader startup?
Cool. Okay.
I'm going to just say let's ignore the marketing budget for now.
And hopefully that like helps us simplify the problem a little bit and kind of get to a baseline maybe.
And we can always add that in later.
Yep. Sounds good.
And then some other basic costs like do we want music?
Do you want a DJ?
Do you want AV?
Okay.
Yeah.
My understanding is a lot of venues will have different options there too.
And so maybe we need to like, let's plan for AV needs as part of this, but we don't need to be too complex.
Yeah.
I think we need entertainment.
No, but I do think you want the ability to like have a microphone so that because we want to,
we want to speak to the audience, right?
Yeah.
Part of this is teaching them about this launch.
So you're going to want at least some basic AV.
So like a microphone and speaker in the very least, maybe we don't need a whole stage,
but you'll want something with basic AV victim.
Cool.
Okay.
So I have, I literally, I've just said, we want Mike's to be able to speak to the audience.
Maybe we'll just have the bot figure out what to do with that.
Cool.
Yeah.
Because it'll say often once it starts negotiating with the RFPs, it'll see who has AV because
the goal here is the most vendors we can get in one venue because otherwise we're going
to have to create a bot that goes and scouts vendors separately.
Okay.
Awesome.
So let's go across the spot and maybe we'll see what it comes back to us in terms of budgets.
I know we don't have a ton of time with you today, Jenny, but I'm just curious.
What we just did was really helpful for like one portion of how we might want to run this
pop-up, right?
Like let's go get a bunch of research on venues, for example.
Could you give us like, what are the two or three other big things that we should maybe
create equivalent bots for?
And we can go up with some of those prompts separately, but just curious.
So we have our venue budget bot.
We're creating two more bots to make sure we really don't mess anything up.
What would you recommend?
To make sure we really don't mess anything up.
I might be the first person to ever say this.
This might be the first GrokBot, a permit GrokBot.
So I would say, can you hear me now?
Yes.
Okay.
So I might be the first person to ever say these words, a permit GrokBot, like red tape,
GrokBot.
We need a GrokBot to go research and see if there's anything legally needed for the execution
of this event.
Because SF, they run a tight ship.
We don't want to skirt the line.
So I think a permit GrokBot would be great.
Yeah.
So, and this is a great tip for anybody that's doing any sort of event.
Like regulatory research like this is such a pain in the butt for anyone that's ever
doing an event, especially if you're doing them in different cities, because every city
is going to be different.
So having a GrokBot that can just check policies for anywhere where you're executing on something
is a great idea.
You can also obviously build like a GrokBot that's doing other things internally like this
that would check like employee policies or any sort of policy related work.
I think a bot would be a great source of truth for that.
Okay.
So yeah, we definitely have a policy bot maybe that helps us navigate a lot of that and
can maybe even help us review some contracts.
Well, I don't know.
We're going to get like an actual, some actual advice there.
But yeah, at least your first pass so we know what we're reading that can be helpful.
Yeah.
Cool.
Any others?
Yeah.
I would say, well, I was going to say in terms of the, I've got a lot of friends that are
attorneys and they say that you should treat the AI as kind of like a second year law student
level of review.
So it's somebody that knows what they're doing, but they don't necessarily know the
nuance of how things operate.
So it can read the legalese of what the law says, but like, what's the going rate
in the city and in the industry of how things shake out.
Right.
So it's not great for a first pass at contracts, but we would want somebody with
experience to overview beyond that.
Cool.
Awesome.
I think that makes a lot of sense.
Yeah.
I think that actually gives us a lot to work with for the rest of the evening.
And we're getting close to the industry, but it is actually really great having you
on and talking about some of these things that, you know, honestly, you have to be
kind of an event planner or have gone through these experiences like you have,
right, to know about.
And maybe that's the power of being a human being and like having the experiences that
you know, how to direct the AI and what to get for.
Yeah.
So the thing that I tell people, the reason why I've been able to build out this
agency on such a lean budget with all these AIs like do it yourself as humans,
build it out with what humans would do and then kind of reverse engineer.
So I think for what you guys are what you guys are getting towards is is a great
direction.
I'm curious then.
So how are you how are you thinking about this as we wrap up the day, like going
into day two, like what we're what do we want to execute on?
Yeah.
We were actually just thinking about that right off camera a minute ago.
What we want to do to kind of close off the stream is figure out like what long
running agents that we should try, you know, just like executing on tonight.
So I think this budget agent is definitely one where maybe we could exchange
an email to make some progress.
Any other sort of long running agents you think we should try getting up
tonight and like working while we sleep as maybe some parting some parting
thoughts.
Yeah.
So I definitely would say like the scout venue searching.
I think like we should definitely make sure that it is searching,
identifying and drafting emails for in the morning.
We can review everyone it wants to outbound to.
So that's like my favorite thing.
Like I constantly just have like the agents drafting emails for me that are
waiting in the morning and I just have to hit send.
I also would say like we we also need to start kind of like figuring out how
we're going to get people there.
So an easy thing to do is like I give my agents access to meta and like
they log directly into my Instagram.
So like let's start sourcing an invite list.
Like that's the most like basic thing is go through all the people that are
verified that follow you.
You can even source like I'll tell my agent find the 50 accounts that
follow me with the highest amount of followers that are in this city.
Let's start making that list and then we can pre-draft to them outbound
so that we can get the most important people to be coming to the event
and also sharing about the event.
I love that.
I think we're fortunate to have a really large audience on X today too.
So that might be a great source for us to go and book after but I guess
with that, Jenny, thank you so much.
This is incredible.
Thank you for being such a great rock-pot user too.
I saw a screenshot of your boss earlier.
We're trying to get the screen share working and I wasn't able to get it
working, but we just make sure we post that somewhere.
It is.
It is a masterpiece in terms of how you set up the sidebar and have all
these different agents kind of running your businesses for you.
Absolutely.
Yeah.
I'm super excited to come to this.
Like you guys are going to have to do this.
You're going to need to make the merge.
Like this is happening, right?
I think it's happening.
I mean, I feel like we're, yeah, hopefully we can figure out all the logistics
in the 48 hours we have left, but yeah, we're, we're, I think we're going to
have to figure this out.
There you go.
Yeah.
Thanks so much.
You're doing awesome.
Thank you.
Awesome.
All right.
Thank you again.
I'll see you guys.
Awesome.
See ya.
Cool.
All right.
Well, I think we have Jenny honestly super valuable, super great and charismatic.
And I think we have about like 10 minutes left in the day.
Yeah.
Kind of rapid at 5 30.
So kind of update like where we're at really spend the first day, I think,
kind of flushing out these ideas.
We aligned shifted a few times.
Yeah.
We might still be shifting.
We brought the whiteboard in.
There's some things written on the whiteboard, but we still have a long
ways to go.
And maybe before we close out, we could talk a little bit about what we
learned from Jenny or where we think we're going to take things in the next
next day or so.
Yeah.
Kind of just reflecting on the day and then maybe we could all end with like
a few thoughts on the day.
My immediate thoughts are one is I think idea generation is really hard.
Yeah.
I think we've definitely spent a lot of time today poking around different
ideas.
And I think the other thing is there's a lot of wisdom in the crowd, right?
Like everyone we've brought on has had some unique perspective.
And so kind of what I'm excited to think about, you know, while our agents are
running overnight, maybe we should do some of this too is like, you know,
what, how to really lock in on sort of one of the one or two things that we
want to really ensure we can build in the next little while to make this all
successful.
And so, yeah, I think figuring out how we get to some of that clarity will
be really great.
Yeah.
I'm just, you know, I think the we've done a lot of like broad idea brainstorming.
And so I think kind of like, how do we focus that into some of the fun for
people with sort of what what's up with my opinion?
Well, I mean, it was cool to see like, you know, we got our slides spun up.
We got everything connected, got boss right into notion, got GitHub set up,
got Vercel set up, started with a dashboard or started with like a very
V1 lander kind of iterated on that a little bit, started moving forward.
So I feel like we have a lot of like set up stuff done, but we definitely need to
kind of lock in.
So I feel like we're going to have to have to do that.
Maybe start tonight.
Honestly, I don't know what you feel.
I think I feel like after talking to Jenny, I feel like it's quite eye
opening how difficult it is to do a start pop up in SF.
Yeah.
And I wonder, I guess I'm trying to think about like, is this the right
problem to go after?
Yeah.
So, yeah, a lot of thinking I think we need to do.
But hopefully we'll come back tomorrow refreshed and we'll lock in tonight and
think about what we're going to build.
But, yeah, I think we learned a lot from my guests.
You know, so yeah.
Cool.
Awesome.
Yeah, I mean, it was a busy day.
And again, we're in San Francisco, our goal is to build a business today and
the next two days as a part of Dreamforce at GrokWokGalaxy.
Just a wrap before we close it out, the Galaxy Live Build Challenge, the
GrokWokGalaxy challenge corresponding to the live stream.
If you create a template, you submit it, go to at Grok.
We looks like we might have lost video and you can submit your template
there.
But thanks for joining us.
And I think we're out.
See you tomorrow.